<question id="20140608162419AAwr1N9">
	<title>What candy should I get ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I 'm going to the movies and I do n't know what candy to get they 're all just SOOO good !! What would you get ?</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402269955000">sour patch kids or M&M/ORGANIZATION 's</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402269987000">If u are stoned : Sour Patch Kids If not : Anything else .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402270276000">They are expensive anyway , just buy some from the candy store and sneak some in</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402270358000">movie theater popcorn on average costs about 5 bucks . you could go to the dollar store and get 5 different types of candy for that price !! you could even buy a big ass bag of candy at walmart for the same price as one puny butterfinger at the movie theater and have plenty to share with friends : -RRB-</answer><suggestions>walmart/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402270486000">M&M/ORGANIZATION 's : -RRB-</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402275174000">twix</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402280743000">Some candy that you can eat silently without disturbing the movie . Jolly ranchers ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140623233101AAWshFC">
	<title>why are n't the regi caves opening in pokemon emerald ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I am having trouble making the earthquake occur -LRB- the one that opens all the regi caves -RRB- at the second part of the sealed chamber . I used dig at the first wall and went through the opening . When I got to the second wall , I put my wailord at the first slot of my party and relicanth at the sixth slot , then used dig -LRB- at the front middle -RRB- . But no earthquake occured and I just ended up back underwater . Am I doing something wrong ?</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403592698000">You did everything else right , but at the end you do n't use dig again . Just have the pokemon in those slots then read the braille on the far back wall and the caves should open .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140619113940AAko4f7">
	<title>What kind of phone do you have ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I have an iPhone 5s 64 GB -LRB- I have a ton of games on it -RRB- .</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403203248000">a crappy cracked one</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403203281000">My phone has buttons on it , I bet you think I 'm a hipster now .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403203326000">A rotary dial</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403203363000">Palm Pre -LRB- 2009 -RRB-</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403203377000">iPhone 7</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403203385000">I currently have the Galaxy S2 . I 'm about to get a new phone . . still deciding between an HTC/ORGANIZATION , iphone 5s , or a galaxy s5 ...</answer><suggestions>htc/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403203446000">iphone 4s</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403203454000">Are you trying to make us eat our liver out ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403203476000">I have a black one . With numbers and stuff .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403203492000">Samsung/ORGANIZATION Galaxy Note 2 ...</answer><suggestions>samsung/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403203516000">Three year old Samsung/ORGANIZATION flip phone that I rarely ever use . Not even sure where it is at the moment . I may have left it in the car yesterday .</answer><suggestions>samsung/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403203676000">I have an LGG2 . It 's a really good Android phone . Its camera is amazing . I suggest you switch to Android after your iPhone 5S will crack .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403204091000">Samsung/ORGANIZATION Galaxy S3 ... . . !!</answer><suggestions>samsung/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403204139000">iPhone 5S . It plays games ? : - -RRB- I have a weather app on it .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403799907000">I endorse the 1st answer .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140622210819AARJGLW">
	<title>Anime Drawing Request ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I 'm writing a Manga -LRB- Anime Comic book for ones who do not know -RRB- . I cant really draw from my mind . I would like to have multiple people send me drawings and for the information of the charter -LRB- s -RRB- please send an email to arcticwinter385@yahoo.com OR zonicrules@Gmail.com OR both thank you i will responed quick an i Can thank you very much everyone .</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403535074000">Well , if it 's not paid work I do n't think you 'll find much ` quick ' . Have you looked into artist groups near you that might want to have portfolio work added to their resume ? If you 're in the US/LOCATION try meetup.com and put in ` artist ' or ` manga ' and your zip code .</answer><suggestions>us/LOCATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140619101954AAAy1Zi">
	<title>What are your favorite snapchats ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>Snapchat is a phone app to send pictures to your friends with captions : -RRB-</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I like to keep some of mine , because I crack myself up . And I always screenshot other people 's good snapchats . Show me either the top 3-5 snapchats which YOU SENT and\/or the top 3-5 snapchats which YOUR FRIENDS have sent . BEST ANSWER GOES TO WHOEVER MAKES ME LAUGH : D I 'll be playing too ! Not that I can give myself best answer -LRB- or can I. . ? -RRB-</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>.</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403198559000">What you mean like crisps and Doritos ? I ca n't eat Crisps -LRB- diet -RRB- but i can eat DORITOS .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403198764000">what 's that ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403213283000">Hi</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140614004826AAWj9IB">
	<title>GOOD MOVIES FOR ARTISTIC TEENS ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>Hi , I love movies . Not all , just the good ones . Here is my list of favorites Somersault - about a young girl finding out the diff between luv and sex Martha/PERSON Macy/PERSON May/PERSON Marlene/PERSON - a girl escaping an abusive cult Albatross - a girl who has an affair with an older man Phoebe/PERSON in wonderland/LOCATION - an autistic -LRB- i think ? -RRB- girl who escapes in her wonderland/LOCATION Violet and Daisy - two girls are assigned to assinate a man Cruel Intentions - the ending oh my god , so good , about a guy constantly using girls and finds a girl he loves only his past to jepidise it Thirteen - a messed up girl befriends a coolish girl only for her life and relationship with mother to turn upside down There 's more ! I love how these are about young girls -LRB- i 'm a teen -RRB- and they 're not typical but artistic , could you suggest any more ? : D</content><suggestions>martha/PERSON macy/PERSON may/PERSON marlene/PERSON phoebe/PERSON wonderland/LOCATION daisy/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402735917000">Across the Universe - a trippy musical abut the Vietnam/LOCATION war and a relationship between an upper class girl\/lower class boy The Art of Getting By - a boy who makes it to senior year without ever doing school work suddenly has to complete all of the assignments from the year to graduate Benny/PERSON & Joon/PERSON - a girl with mental health issues and an eccentric man fall in love The Bling Ring - a bunch of high school kids begin breaking into celebrities ' homes Boys Do n't Cry - follows the life of a FTM transgender teen The Breakfast Club - a group of students have to spend their Saturday together when they all get weekend detention Easy A - a virgin girl begins letting guys pay her to pretend she had sex with them Ferris/PERSON Bueller/PERSON 's Day Off - three friends take a day off school Girl , Interrupted - follows a girls time in a mental institution after she attempts to commit suicide Heathers - a girl gets in a relationship with the schools ` bad boy ' and they begin murdering fellow students whilst making them look like suicides It 's Kind of a Funny Story - a relationship between a boy and girl in a mental institution blossoms John/PERSON Tucker/PERSON Must Die - three girls find out they 're all being cheated on by the same guy , so they get him to fall in love with another girl with the plan to break his heart Just My Luck - an extremely lucky woman kisses an unlucky guy at a party and they swap their fortune Legally Blonde - after her boyfriend breaks up with her because she does n't have a future , a sorority queen goes to law school to attempt to win him back Love Actually - a girl ends up stuck on an island with her favorite rockstar and attempts to make him fall in love with her Material Girls - two rich girls suddenly become poor when their fathers business is involved in a scandal My Sister 's Keeper - follows a young girl who was only brought into the world to supply organs for her sister who has cancer Nim/PERSON 's Island - about a girl who lives alone with her father on an island and has to survive on her own when he goes missing on a boating trip She 's the Man - a girl goes to school pretending to be her brother in order to be a part of the soccer team Sydney/PERSON White/PERSON - a retelling of the Snow/PERSON White/PERSON story , but set in a college</answer><suggestions>benny/ORGANIZATION &/ORGANIZATION joon/ORGANIZATION ftm/ORGANIZATION ferris/ORGANIZATION bueller/ORGANIZATION john/PERSON tucker/PERSON nim/PERSON sydney/PERSON white/PERSON</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140621032104AA5LQDd">
	<title>What is the name of this -LRB- possibly communist -RRB- movie ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I watched this video on youtube/ORGANIZATION called The Greatest Speech Ever Made . It was a speech delivered by Charlie/PERSON Chaplin/PERSON and it was a montage of emotion-stirring scenes from various movies and tv shows . -LRB- not spamming , but here is the link : https:\/\/www.youtube.com\/watch?v=WibmcsEGLKo -RRB- One particular movie which captured my attention was one I believe is possibly some 1984-like movie . It shows scientists staring ahead and studying something while a projector beams behind them -LRB- 0:52 -RRB- and men mindlessly marching on a catwalk in a factory and falling -LRB- 1:23 -RRB- . Machines move below them and their shadows cast a Communist symbol on the walls -LRB- 2:07 -RRB- and pink meat comes out of a meat grinder . THE SCENE I SEARCH FOR THE MOST is one where it shows children taking off masks and jumping up and cheering . -LRB- 2:47 -RRB- at some school or gym . Keep in mind , I only think those scenes are connected and part of the same movie because they are all gray and depressing . I have been searching for this movie for a long time now . Could anyone please tell me what it is ?</content><suggestions>youtube/ORGANIZATION charlie/PERSON chaplin/PERSON</suggestions>
	<content>No , it is NOT the Great Dictator . The movie I speak of if WITHIN the video . One of the many scenes taken from OTHER . Its a montage of videos and I want to know the source of one of those videos .</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403346187000">The Great Dictator .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403348034000">It is The Great Dictator .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403349866000">The movie name is The Great Dictator .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140622212808AAkLGsg">
	<title>Used Epiphone/ORGANIZATION Electric Guitar is it good \/ worth it ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>http:\/\/www.guitarcenter.com\/Epiphone,Electric-Guitar-Guitar,Used-Gear.gc?extup=50-100&ipp=25 http:\/\/www.guitarcenter.com\/Epiphone-Used--Epiphone-2006-SG-Special-Bolt-On--Cherry-Solid-Body-Electric-Guitar-110121991-i3792846.gc http:\/\/www.guitarcenter.com\/Epiphone-Used--Epiphone--Explorer-GT--Black-Solid-Body-Electric-Guitar-110247962-i3810742.gc</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403505022000">Why not , if thats your budget . But try before you buy , or bring a friend with guitar expertise to check the guitar 's general condition .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403528371000">No way to know without playing them first . For instance I 've played American Strats that were great and ones I would n't own if you gave them to me . This holds true with most guitars , especially import models like Epiphone/ORGANIZATION . One of them might be a gem and one might be a turd . Never know until you try it in person . That is the only way to buy a guitar .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140613124917AAp8Kiq">
	<title>JYP\/CUBE entertainment ... and School ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>Hi everyone ! I 'm 15 years old and i live in Italy/LOCATION , i want to try to make an audition , but ... SCHOOL ? what can i do ? i 've this problem ... . pls help me !!! THANK YOU !!!!</content><suggestions>italy/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402689044000">GET FREE League of Legends RP & Skin Codes 100 % Successful With PROOF Here : http:\/\/lolfreecode.asia Free Over 500 champion Skins and a lot of 10 $ , 25 $ RP Codes . More than 300 gamer got code successful !!!! All you have to do is some quick and simple steps to get your free Riot Points ! Get Code Free Now : http:\/\/lolfreecode.asia</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402892223000">Can I have more info on this ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140621194648AAv7Pxb">
	<title>Which attack on titan character is the best ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>My favorite is bertholdt/PERSON</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403408050000">bertholdt/PERSON aka the armored titan ? Mikasa/PERSON is my favorite</answer><suggestions>bertholdt/PERSON mikasa/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403408737000">Sasha/PERSON the Potato Girl</answer><suggestions>sasha/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403412966000">i go for levi\/rivaille/PERSON . . if you have read the birth of rivaille manga , you 'll love how the worlds strongest human weapon was born ! Hehehehe ... and the seiyuu is Kamiya/PERSON , Hiroshi/PERSON . . the seiyuu for both Akashi/PERSON Seijuro/PERSON -LRB- kuroko/PERSON no basket -RRB- and Orihara/PERSON Izaya/PERSON -LRB- Durarara ! -RRB-</answer><suggestions>kamiya/PERSON hiroshi/PERSON akashi/PERSON seijuro/PERSON orihara/PERSON izaya/PERSON durarara/PERSON</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140620190356AAdnQme">
	<title>what is a gangster or mob flick ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>Please leave a few examples thanks a bunch</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403317612000">The Godfather , Goodfellas , the Departed , We Own the Night , the Untouchables , Drive , D-ck Tracey , Scarface</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403325131000">The departed Goodfellas The godfather The godfather part II Scarface Pulp fiction Reservoir dogs Casino Mean streets</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403332946000">The Mob -LRB- Docudrama & Fiction -RRB- = = = = = = = = = = = = Al/PERSON Capone/PERSON Nitti/PERSON St. Valentine 's Day Massacre Lucky/PERSON Luciano/PERSON Lansky/PERSON Bugsy/PERSON Dillinger/PERSON -LRB- 1947 & 1973 one -RRB- Bonnie and Clyde Machine-Gun Kelly/PERSON Boss/PERSON Of Bosses Gotti Mobsters The Valachi Papers Hoodlum Casino Donnie/PERSON Brasco/PERSON The Untouchables -LRB- fact and fiction mix together -RRB- Scarface -LRB- original , to a certain point much better then the 1983 one , The mob do n't sell drugs -RRB- Little Caesar Public Enemy White Heat The Godfather The Godfather Part II Mean Street Once Upon A Time In America The Last Don Eastern Promises -LRB- Russian Mob -RRB- Street Gangs -LRB- aka Gangbanger -RRB- = = = = = = = = = = = = Boyz And The Hood Juice Menace II Society South Central Bound By Honor -LRB- aka Blood In Blood Out -RRB- American Me</answer><suggestions>al/PERSON capone/PERSON nitti/PERSON lucky/PERSON luciano/PERSON lansky/PERSON bugsy/PERSON dillinger/PERSON bonnie/PERSON clyde/PERSON kelly/PERSON gotti/PERSON donnie/PERSON brasco/PERSON little/PERSON caesar/PERSON america/LOCATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140618161505AAlxyko">
	<title>What do you think of thunderstorms ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I think they 're badass .</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403133380000">amazing , my car was blasted by lightning once</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403133424000">annoying</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403133473000">I Like them , the Lightening is even Better : -RRB-</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403133526000">A bit scary if they 're close , but otherwise they 're not so bad .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403133592000">I love them</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403133799000">I love the wind and atmosphere before one hits , but not being out during one .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403133861000">without lightning they 're nothing . NOTHING !</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403133951000">I love the wind and atmosphere before one hits , but not being out during one .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403134363000">I am really afraid of them ...</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403134373000">I love watching the dark clouds roll in on a hot summer day . Hearing the thunder in the distance . It gives me the feeling of impending doom !</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403146415000">Storms rock ! Lightning and thunder rule ! It reminds me of mankind 's eternal struggle against the elements . How nature is bigger than all of us . I love to watch enormous billowing cumulonimbus clouds and supercells . Like gigantic pieces of masterful architecture in the sky . A commanding presence .</answer><suggestions>mankind/LOCATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140615222209AAOSKxY">
	<title>what is your favorite thing about your iPhone ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I have a galaxy note 3 note 3 now , but what I think I miss most about my iPhone is when I would wake up every morning , my iPhone would be freezing cold , feeling brand new : -RRB- What 's your favorite thing ?</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402896229000">my favorite thing is that I do n't own a cell phone .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402896392000">that i have a Sprint LG/ORGANIZATION phone . it is a survivor . i 've dropped it , washed it , dried it in the clothes dryer . Little kids have smeared it with all sorts of food , and still it works . it 's a miracle phone and the sturdiest phone i 've ever had , but honestly i 'm ready to get rid of it .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402896432000">that i dont have one ... yayyyyyyy</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402896448000">Its awesome apps .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402896592000">My favorite thing about my former iPhone was the camera it took high definition resolution pictures beautifully . my least favorite thing was when it froze on me when I made phone calls . : -LRB-</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402896661000">I do n't have a iPhone but I do own a iPod touch I like the games and music</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402896676000">randomness</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402896855000">Mine got stolen .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402898332000">The built-in iPod</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402900329000">Everythinggg :3</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140604202844AAigI4l">
	<title>A beautiful sad song about being torn between loving two people ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>It just needs to be almost sad with beautiful vocals . No pop songs though . Think The Fray . Any suggestions would be greatly appreciated and I do pick best answer . Thank you !</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401938998000">Wayne/PERSON Brady/PERSON - You & Me .</answer><suggestions>wayne/PERSON brady/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401939095000">Can not help you in this one , as not a song I would be singing , so go with the other one , sing this to yourself you will forever be in these tangles . ~ \*</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140606053450AAtepIb">
	<title>can you please answer my questions ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>please answer my other questions : -RRB-</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402058122000">I can .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402058130000">Hej ! Lycklig/PERSON fredag/PERSON !</answer><suggestions>lycklig/PERSON fredag/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402058219000">Okay .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402058284000">ca n't you take the hint ? Smokin ` !</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140617203632AANuG3B">
	<title>How to start reading Comics ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I 'd also be grateful if you guys\/gals could write recomendations and stuff like that in lists and explain why so its easy for me to understand ,</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I would like to read comic books but I do n't know where to start . I have already read some of the Modern batman stuff but there is so much and and it seems like it does n't matter anymore now that new 52 has been out for a couple of years . I am also interested in reading marvel comics but have never read any of those and am completely clueless which series I wa n't to read . So my main question breaks down into multiple questions . Should I continue reading the modern batman stuff ? It would take a long time to buy and read all those for me and I do n't know if it 's worth it . If it 's better to start with new 52 what are the '' main '' series in the DC universe I 'm mainly interested in the '' batfamily '' comics and the justice league ? what are some other series I should read from DC ? How do I get caught up in the story in the most simple way possible ? I am also interested in reading marvel comics and pretty much have the same questions for those except I 'm not sure what heroes or teams to read from them . So what are the '' main '' series in marvel ? where to start how to get caught up to the most recent events in the most simple way ? After getting caught up with trades should I continue reading trades or start getting singles ? I like trades better but then you lose the community of going the shops and stuff like that and also I have bad anxiety so going to a store will probably be super terrifying for me . thanks for reading and please help me . Thank you !</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403196592000">Just start with the newest issue and just try and keep up . You should pick up batman eternal -LRB- although for this one start from 1 its uber confusing -RRB- and futures end is another one id start form the begining with those are the biggest story arcs in comics right now , the really important ones . Another one that would be handy to know about is an arc that affected all DC/ORGANIZATION comics and youll hear about it alot futures end and its refered to as the battle of earth 1 or the invaders from earth 3 its called forever evil .</answer><suggestions>earth/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140604093657AAnN7Gq">
	<title>Name for song ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>It is made by a mix black and white guy for his soon to be wife . In the video it is home videos of his blonde wife . I ca n't remember the song it is killing me !!! It was made around 2010-11 . It 's a love song was n't that popular but a good song .</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401900162000">https:\/\/www.youtube.com\/watch?v=EyByG2WJ4_M&list=UUUDxi73R5mVN_Yqqj5oGSug</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140618141409AA9yzif">
	<title>Is it a sin to listen to and\/or play blues music ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>And by blues music I mean artists like Stevie/PERSON Ray/PERSON Vaughan/PERSON and B.B./PERSON King/PERSON</content><suggestions>stevie/PERSON ray/PERSON vaughan/PERSON b.b./PERSON king/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403136965000">No not at all , but remembrr anything can always affect your heart .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403143004000">That depends what particular form of religious bigotry you subscribe to . Most people would n't consider the artists you mention to be sinful .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403305401000">Yes , and that 's what makes it so great .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403490831000">Blues was the `` devil 's music '' back in the days of Robert/PERSON Johnson/PERSON . Some of its themes alluded to sex , to be certain . But then there 's country music . In the old days of people like Ray/PERSON Price/PERSON and Porter/PERSON Wagoner/PERSON , country was all about a `` God , mom , and apple pie '' image . It still tries to sell that image while singing songs about how much better your secret lover is than your spouse or fooling around with your best friend 's mate .</answer><suggestions>blues/PERSON robert/PERSON johnson/PERSON ray/PERSON price/PERSON porter/PERSON wagoner/PERSON</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140605040256AAru12G">
	<title>What style music are these bands ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>1 . My/PERSON chemical/PERSON romance/PERSON 2 . Iron/PERSON maiden/PERSON 3 . Green/PERSON day/PERSON 4 . Linkin/PERSON park/PERSON 5 . Kill/PERSON Hannah/PERSON 6 . Fall/PERSON out/PERSON boy/PERSON 7 . Bowling/PERSON for/PERSON soup/PERSON 8 . Breaking/PERSON Benjamin/PERSON 9 . Incubus/PERSON 10 . Anarbor/PERSON 11 . The/PERSON cab/PERSON 12 . The 1975 13 . All/PERSON time/PERSON low/PERSON 14 . Panic/PERSON ! At/PERSON the/PERSON disco/PERSON Feel free to write the number then the genre or whatever . I just want to know peoples opinions and what you think the styles are ^_^ And if you 've never heard of the band them idk lol</content><suggestions>linkin/LOCATION park/LOCATION hannah/PERSON benjamin/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401966782000">punk rock , pop punk :-RRB- my fav bandsss</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401981305000">all the sound the same type .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401998572000">Iron/PERSON Maiden/PERSON is metal . The other bands I guess are some emo shit .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402017916000">Alternative Punk Rock or what I like to call `` really good music ''</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402038335000">Why is Iron/PERSON Maiden/PERSON even in this list .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140617222051AA6Qnkk">
	<title>Where to watch Answers to Nothing Movie 2011 ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>Its an old Movie that I want to watch online , Its probably HD by now . Answers to Nothing Movie was release 2011 .</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403069054000">I found it here : http:\/\/movies.fbzone.us\/watch-answers-to-nothing-online-2011\/</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140619132551AAMKLtQ">
	<title>Have you ever lost where you parked your car ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>Wandering around the lot with bags of stuff .</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403209567000">nope</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403209608000">what car</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403209647000">No , it was there , i just forgot where there were .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403209719000">With the power of Xenu I never lose my car !</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403209725000">No , But I have lost my spacecraft .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403209804000">No because I park nearer to the store but I get familiar quickly with car park layouts so I can easily identify where I need to go to locate my vehicle .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403209878000">I ca n't find my 747-400 . I landed it at the Strawman/LOCATION Festival and have n't seen it since .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403209881000">Lol , yes I have , a few times I 'm ashamed to tell ! I often forget which floor I 'm on when I use the multiple story 's . And also when I 'm in an unfamiliar place . Lol , it 's not that hard to loose</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403209942000">Yeah , long time ago after a large fireworks display . Gal pal & I looking , and cop on an old 3 wheeler pulled up . He took her riding around looking for it , and left me standing there with a bottle of gin & some tonic water . They found it , she drove back and picked me up .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403210019000">I dont drive yet ... but whenever my dad or mom cant find their car ... they just make that beeping sound come from the car using their keys . So then they remember where they parked ! : -RRB-</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403211069000">Yes I have ,</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403212407000">A couple of times I have looked on the wrong parking level and started to panic a bit . Once , many years ago -LRB- and there was some alcohol involved -RRB- I reported my car as stolen to the police only to have them find it in a different street to where I thought I had parked it ,</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403307307000">Flippin ' think is possessed . It keeps moving itself around when my back is turned .</answer><suggestions>flippin/PERSON</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140606075218AAmnm1s">
	<title>Do your parents speak English ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>It 's very annoying because I am the only one in my family who was born in the U.S./LOCATION and does n't have an accent but my parents immigrated here about 25 years ago and know English , but they never speak it . They always speak another language which I do n't understand at all and worst part is they speak that language with me as much as I tell them I have no idea what they 're saying so it 's very hard . What about you ? Anyone else in this kind of situation ?</content><suggestions>u.s./LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402066417000">Yes they do .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402066422000">yes lol sorry about that . maybe you 'll need a translator to understand them . .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402066431000">No , but they are fat .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402066450000">My mum is south/LOCATION African/LOCATION , she used to all the time speak to me in Afrikaans , not any more though .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402066481000">Yeah , but if you think about it , maybe they 're trying to keep their culture alive because its what they 've known their whole lives . My parents , like your parents , speak our native language & I enjoy it because it makes me feel a part of something I 've never known . Cut your parents some slack , babe . Maybe they 're keeping that culture alive for you as well .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402066493000">So are you to say that you have never understood them ? Im sorry , i cant help !</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402066591000">With age , it is harder for the brain to keep data inside and thus you dont often see older people picking up a new language . They could have worked on learning a language or work to provide you with internet access to ask questions here . You could have been in Eastern/LOCATION Ukraine/LOCATION right now , living in a basement without water so be patient to them . Be patient to me patronizing you and be patient in general . My grandparents do not speak English , but they always try to teach it to me . It 's extra annoying but meh ... Not like we can do anything about it , right ?</answer><suggestions>ukraine/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402066629000">Yeah , it 's the only language they can speak .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402066978000">Mom and bro hardly understand it and speak it while my dad and I speak English veeery well .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402067405000">no but some of my older relatives spoke Ukrainian . Never really picked it up , but the language is beautiful .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402068793000">Yes ,</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402069059000">YES</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402070549000">That 's the only language anyone in my family soak fluently</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402078369000">Yes .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402079416000">Yes .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402082037000">Yes .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402083127000">Yes .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140626102952AA5eUxY">
	<title>Simile for a singing voice . ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>They 're voices sounded so peaceful and beautiful as ...</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403804765000">. . as angels . . as a wind 's lullaby</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140625192132AACp46H">
	<title>Best Beginner Ukulele to buy ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>So i 've been looking around lately for a Ukulele because i have been wanting to learn how to play one for years . I have seen a ton of brands that have been recommended but I 'm not sure which one is the best to buy . My price range is really anything under $ 90 . I 'm looking for a soprano uke and I would love something that will last and have a nice sound for quite a while . Thanks !</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403789824000">The under $ 100 category is a tricky one . There are tons of poorly made ukuleles in that price range . One that I have found to be a consistently good product is the Lanikai LU-21 . It 's a basic , entry-level uke but it has a good sound , plays well in tune , and is a consistent product . That 's important if you are buying over the internet . Other brands are pretty hit and miss , with some good ones and many bad ones , but Lanikai gives a consistent good product . The most important things to avoid are painted ones . The pain ruins the tone and painting a pretty design is a common way to sell a junk ukulele that no one would buy . If you want a very decorative instrument you have to spend more money because they have to start with a good ukulele first and then add all the fancy stuff .</answer><suggestions>lanikai/LOCATION lanikai/LOCATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140605140138AAyDVJY">
	<title>How do you like my lyrics -LRB- 1-10 -RRB- ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>Whats the value of money when you always in debt controlled like a pet dont have They stuff ? Well you a target easy to detect . my account below zero , i was out in Alaska/LOCATION for 2 weeks . So to speak the chilling factor not knowing What to do next made me weak begged on My grandparents for the short time Being , had no resources so they took care of me . Still nothing much changed , no new clothes in months Im going derranged barely got enough to eat i feel so ashamed Then fake friends dead ends , this is the poor Life time that i spend . Centuries , Tendencies , of this happenening to others probably had influenced me Forget this i aint got nothing to the world to teach Find anything in arms reach think ill take a SIP of this bleach But nah , i got to find a different alternative I need an inhale of What hey call gods herb Its imperative I Was mentally distraubt , Ironic i need it to function Dont need no disruption , Im not trying to get caught Until i got caught in the crossroads one day , maybe gods way to say you got ta get your green a different way Spit aqua flows mixed with others remedies , that the solution I Didnt have to graduate chem class to know My music May be against all odds but imma get even Im not fantasizing and Im getting mines from believing I was hidden but Im emerging you wont see me coming But ill be there claiming glory , when i say it Means something Put complex rhymes everytime I do it so simpily when Im gone i leave my imprint in thé sand , just remember me</content><suggestions>alaska/LOCATION imma/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402003039000">I only listen to jana/PERSON barros/PERSON</answer><suggestions>jana/PERSON barros/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402008538000">Really good .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402038201000">Googol .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140613023120AA7XyZ8">
	<title>Poll : Can you relate to this ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>> I was only nine years old > I loved Shrek/PERSON so much , I owned all the movies and merchandise > I pray to Shrek/PERSON every night , thanking him for the life I have been given > `` Shrek/PERSON is love '' , I say , `` Shrek/PERSON is life '' > My dad hears me and calls me a faggot > He is obviously jealous of my devotion to Shrek/PERSON > I called him a cunt > He slaps me and sends me to my room > I am crying now , because my face hurts > I go into my bed and it is very cold > I feel a warmth moving towards me > I fell something touch me > It 's Shrek/PERSON > I am so happy > he whispers into my ear , `` This is my swamp '' > He grabs me with his powerful ogre hands and puts me on my hands and knees > I 'm ready > I spread my ass cheeks for Shrek/PERSON > He penetrates my butthole > It hurts so much , but I do it for Shrek/PERSON > I can feel my anus tearing as my eyes start to water > I push against his force > I want to please Shrek/PERSON > He roars a mighty roar as he fills my butt with his love > My dad walks in > Shrek/PERSON looks him deep in the eyes and says , `` It 's all ogre now Shrek/PERSON leaves through my window Shrek/PERSON is love , Shrek/PERSON is life ''</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402651977000">You have a nice day , why rush TO GROW UP ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402652128000">Present tense or past tense ? Choose one !</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402653634000">No . I do not love Shrek . I do not like a dam thing ! ~ ~ ~</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402653810000">My friend joined me and another friend while we were playing cod and read this to us . When he finished he left the lobby . It was very awkward .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402654304000">You have some WEIRD nightmares .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402658677000">the word PERVERT comes to mind</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140617112511AAZ4ux3">
	<title>What to do if I 've been Accused of ... ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>Knowing how to make a woman feel good , and happy . . ` ; - D</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403029616000">Impossible because you never directly tell the truth</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403029622000">Not guilty</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403029665000">Remind them , that goats are n't really women .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403029673000">tell the Y!A community about it , obviously . So exciting . . Edit : and email me `` you mad ? '' for this answer . What an interesting life . .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403029685000">duck and run</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403030557000">wake up from that dream</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403030731000">Make a business out of it Since you 're good at what you do ! But I know that wo n't last for long ; - P</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140613124158AAH0KXB">
	<title>Who else is doing a sailor moon marathon 4 the new uncut series ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>Who 's doing a sailor moon marathon I so ca n't wait 4 the new series as well a dub that we should of had a long time ago I 'm doing the dub version of the show cause this is how I got into anime btw this is going to be a dvd \/ blue ray release right ? Oh and here r my predictions for the english Va : michelle/PERSON ruff/PERSON as Pluto or Neptune stephenie sheh as Serena/PERSON Darien/PERSON Johnny/PERSON young Those r some predictions that probably will happen plus I think Neptune fits michelle/PERSON ruff/PERSON perfectly also what r your hopes for the new dub will it be a success since there dubbing everything and relationships will b uncut which is really exciting :-RRB- or will it b Dic all over again with parts cut off cause of younger audiences</content><suggestions>michelle/PERSON ruff/PERSON pluto/LOCATION stephenie/PERSON sheh/PERSON serena/PERSON darien/PERSON johnny/PERSON young/PERSON michelle/PERSON ruff/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402688660000">GET FREE League of Legends RP & Skin Codes 100 % Successful With PROOF Here : http:\/\/lolfreecode.asia Free Over 500 champion Skins and a lot of 10 $ , 25 $ RP Codes . More than 300 gamer got code successful !!!! All you have to do is some quick and simple steps to get your free Riot Points ! Get Code Free Now : http:\/\/lolfreecode.asia</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402754521000">same i do marathon and i buy sailor moon stuff : -RRB-</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402894039000">try google/ORGANIZATION it also</answer><suggestions>google/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403058696000">Redub will be all uncut and everything will be like the original sailor moon anime Including the original names -LRB- Usagi , Rei , Ami etc. . -RRB- So basically it will all be the same as Japanese anime except it 's going to be in English</answer><suggestions>usagi/LOCATION ami/PERSON</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140611084109AAK6h31">
	<title>Do Americans like Canadians ? -LRB- I am going to Ohio -RRB- ?</title><suggestions>ohio/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>I am going to a 5 day music fest in Ohio/LOCATION called the gathering of the juggalos and i hope i do n't get treated wrong just because I am from Canada/LOCATION .</content><suggestions>ohio/LOCATION canada/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402504658000">lmao what ? Americans are n't devil worshipers , we are normal people just like Canadians . Just meet new people and hangout do n't be nervous .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402507775000">Of course I love Justin/PERSON Bieber/PERSON and sometimes Drake/PERSON</answer><suggestions>justin/PERSON bieber/PERSON</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140617041235AAokv04">
	<title>What is this pinao\/cello soundtrack ?!!!!!! could it be a film soundtrack ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>What is this pinao\/cello soundtrack ?!!!!!! could it be a film soundtrack ? The link to the soundtrack is here : https:\/\/www.youtube.com\/watch?v=M0HAW8Neqho 10 points for correct answer ?</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403005208000">It does n't sound very classical so I 'd say it is a soundtrack .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403006403000">I agree with Arabella/PERSON . It is definitely not classical music - soundtrack\/instrumental pop is what it is . Try in ` rock and pop ' to see if anyone recognizes it .</answer><suggestions>arabella/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403752640000">I sa a blog post on this the other day , give me 5 min to check browser history .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>

