<question id="20140616141511AAlZZIn">
	<title>Birthday in NYC ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I want to celebrate my birthday with my friends in New/LOCATION York/LOCATION City and I want to be able to wear a fancy dress and heels and not feel out of place . Any suggestions ? Iv ' e heard maybe Carmine/LOCATION 's or The View</content><suggestions>new/LOCATION york/LOCATION city/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402953342000">Sounds fun</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402962628000">Carmines/LOCATION is great !</answer><suggestions>carmines/PERSON</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140610083106AA7AAUT">
	<title>What foods can you name that use hickory or other wood chips to add to the flavor , that are available at restaurants ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>i.e. Hickory flavored anything - Jerky would not ordinarily be offered in a restaurant . so I 'm curious about foods that are served like hickory flavored ribs or whatever .</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402417181000">Ribs/ORGANIZATION and/ORGANIZATION Steaks/ORGANIZATION !! : - -RRB- \ \ \/ \/ \/ \/ \ \</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402540545000">Did you try to do a search on Google/ORGANIZATION ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402576804000">search on Google/ORGANIZATION</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140601101734AAAYp2K">
	<title>Sixteenth birthday in NYC with a couple friends ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>For my sixteenth birthday , I want to go into the city with four or five friends and go to a nice restaurant -LRB- where we could dress in heels and nice dresses without looking out of place -RRB- . I 've heard of other girls going to Serendipity/ORGANIZATION 3 , Max/ORGANIZATION Brenners/ORGANIZATION , or the Sugar/ORGANIZATION Factory/ORGANIZATION for their sixteenth birthdays and I was wondering if you had any other suggestions</content><suggestions>max/PERSON brenners/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401643141000">Www.resto-past.blogspot.ca checkout third link on</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401679571000">If you are looking for a tad more casual but fun , go to Lucky/ORGANIZATION Cheng/ORGANIZATION 's for dinner and the show .</answer><suggestions>lucky/PERSON cheng/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401790983000">dinner</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140625170104AAXx2TO">
	<title>At chipotle is it illegal to give friends discounts on food . ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>Im about to work at chipotle and i wass wondering if it is illegal to give friends or family a discount on there food</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403740963000">It 's not illegal per say but you could be fired for doing that it 's not allowed .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403740984000">most restaurants allow you to use your employee discount for family . using it for friends is less common , but it does happen . check with your manager . : -RRB-</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403740986000">Yes , unless you have specific permission from the owner -LRB- not just your supervisor -RRB- .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403741050000">Do n't lose the job before you start ! you ask the manager the rules , and you follow them , your friends and families should not try to make you give them discounts .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403741496000">No , as long as your friends are white .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403747284000">It 's stealing from the company and would get you fired if\/when you get caught .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403802302000">It is not against the law but it is against company policy to give out discounts randomly to your friends .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140623125518AAtlQpd">
	<title>Do I have to pay if I say `` want to go out for lunch or dinner ? '' ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>So , I have not seen this girl for a year . She liked me before but I was not really into her . She still messages me for petty talks . I was going to say if she wants to catch up while lunch or dinner , but do I have to pay for everything ? I am university student so money is bit tight , also when she want to go out we used to split the bill . If I say if she wants to go out and eat , do we split the bill or do I pay for everything ?</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403554106000">id pay for the bill if i were you , as you havnt seen her for a whole year . you need to look as if your making some kind of an effort . if your tight with money dont take her somewhere really expensive but somewhere decent .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403557600000">Yes if you 're inviting her you pay but I agree with the other answerer go somewhere you can afford or another option is lunch , the prices are always cheaper then .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403588433000">Well not always but you havnt seen this girl in a while so pay for it .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403593048000">girl in a while so pay for i</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140610190716AAGOR0h">
	<title>when was the last time you had a burger ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>1 day for me . _ .</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402452714000">I used to live on burgers but these days I have them only seldom . The last time was only two weeks ago , but before that you 'd have to go back months ! I was on a long motorcycle ride with a friend of mine , and when we got back , close to her house , she wanted to go to this cool old place that 's been there since the 1940s . The city has literally grown up around this place ! We got burgers and sweet potato fries -LRB- they sure did n't have THOSE in the 1940s ! -RRB- The burgers were charcoal-broiled and very good !</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402452888000">Im having one right now haha</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402452922000">I 've never had a beef burger before . But the other day I had an awful chicken burger .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402452937000">1 hour ago . A big mac</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402453054000">This past weekend</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402453143000">Few months ago ... : -RRB-</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402453581000">Only last Monday ! ^_^</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402453972000">Saturday</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402454690000">Today :-RRB- haha .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402457313000">About two years ago due to health reasons .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402465928000">Last night . delicious one ! lol .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402471367000">last week</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402477545000">a day ago ... one big mac !!</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402483266000">about 1 week ago</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402498701000">So long ago I do n't remember when . I kind of crave one , though : -RRB-</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402821817000">1 hour ago</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140616190348AA6nheU">
	<title>Burger king paycheck question ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>So i started working at burger king like two weeks ago , and everybody got their paycheck Saturday -LRB- June 14th -RRB- . I did n't get mine , and I 've worked 17 something hours so far , plus the 15 my manager has me scheduled for . So all in all i am gon na have around 32 hours worked but no check . Do you know when i get my paycheck ?</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402971049000">I doubt that anyone on this forum knows the answer to your question . But you know who you should ask ? Your manager .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402972143000">How could anyone outside of your work answer this ????</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402995099000">You get it in the second cycle . They could give it to you in the first cycle , but that would require them having to work at making it look like you were hired on earlier then you were like every legitimate business does . Like walmart/ORGANIZATION does that so you get it the first time . You will get your first check on Saturday , not the next one , the one after . And not two checks , they hold the first one like a deposit and you always are behind one . Then when you quit you get the extra check . Because they do n't hire accountants , they force the managers to do all that stuff for them .</answer><suggestions>walmart/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140613111207AAD5YgE">
	<title>Is Ronald/PERSON Mcdonald/PERSON John/PERSON Wayne/PERSON Gacy/PERSON in disguise ?</title><suggestions>ronald/PERSON mcdonald/PERSON john/PERSON wayne/PERSON gacy/PERSON</suggestions>
	<content>Does McDonalds/ORGANIZATION want to fatten people up to EAT THEM in disguise and John/PERSON Wayne/PERSON Gacy/PERSON escaped ! CONSPIRACY TIME</content><suggestions>mcdonalds/ORGANIZATION john/PERSON wayne/PERSON gacy/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402683370000">You know too much . It 's Big Mac time for you . Nothing personal ; it 's just business . Fast Food business .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402684609000">Big mac time for you</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402685532000">McDonalds/ORGANIZATION is a successful business like any other . I do n't believe there is a `` conspiracy '' behind their business of any kind , and to compare them with serial killer John Gacy is really not fair . If you do n't like their food , do n't go there . There are a lot of people who do like it .</answer><suggestions>mcdonalds/ORGANIZATION john/PERSON gacy/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402685608000">no of course not if it was gacy they would have arrested him by now but its not gacy .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402692771000">Mind blown :0</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402694946000">the nuggets are turds . that 's the only secret I know .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402700165000">I always thought so</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402700298000">Holy \*\*\*\*</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402707081000">So a clown called ronald/PERSON mcdonald/PERSON aka john/PERSON wayne/PERSON gacy/PERSON is the one you founded mcdonalds/ORGANIZATION ? That is what youre saying ? Lol ... i love mcdonalds/ORGANIZATION so i think not</answer><suggestions>ronald/PERSON mcdonald/PERSON john/PERSON wayne/PERSON gacy/PERSON mcdonalds/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402708655000">Kanamits . To serve man . Twilight zone . My favorite episode</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402709565000">no of course not , ,</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402738184000">nope</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402764143000">Mind blown</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402910455000">Big mac for you .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140623122455AAmdQZw">
	<title>Why are n't the tips I leave showing in my bank statement ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I ate out a few weeks ago and my meal was $ 10.44 . I wrote $ 3.00 in on the tip line and signed the slip . Now that the charge is no longer pending on my bank statement , it 's still reading as $ 10.44 . This is n't the first time that 's happened . It 's probably happened 2 or 3 times in the past year or so . I 've made sure I 'm signing the restaurant copy and making the tip clear and writing in the total as well , but it looks as if the servers are n't getting their tips . Does anyone know why that 's happening ?</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403552110000">Check your statement for other unauthorized activity . It could be that someone is skimming the card numbers before the receipts are returned for the final amount . That happened to me . I always make the total a whole dollar amount , like the 10.44 charge I might make 12.00 total , with the tip being 1.56 . I noticed that the charge did not end in 00 as is my usual practice , then noticed a $ 500 charge shortly thereafter at Game Stop -LRB- I 'm not a gamer -RRB- . I called the restaurant , and they asked me to look at the server 's name on the receipt . When I told them , they acted like it was what they expected - perhaps they had trouble with her and already fired her . Anyway , the bank straightened it all out , and I did n't lose a dime .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140605151444AA6EqVP">
	<title>Steak n Shake Hostess Interview ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I have an interview at steak n shake tomorrow . My first interview within months . What questions might they ask ?</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402006502000">i want it to be 1750 fps or more make sure it is not pcp hook up and under $ 550</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402008710000">say youre chrisstian n that u r better then evry1 . this is wat i did mi last intervew n they got bak 2 me n 1 days</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402013353000">Ask someone</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402037795000">If you have experience for those food , they might ask about your experience if you are Lerner they mention about what sould you do and how to do that Job .</answer><suggestions>lerner/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402044949000">someone</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140608075953AADKMro">
	<title>Traditional english food in London/LOCATION ?</title><suggestions>london/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>I am going to London/LOCATION , what english food I should try ?</content><suggestions>london/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402239741000">Roast beef and Yorkshire pudding Bangers and Mash Pie and Mash Fish and Chips</answer><suggestions>yorkshire/ORGANIZATION pudding/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402240721000">FISH AND CHIPS . LIKE ACTUALLY REAL FISH AND CHIPS , LIKE THE OFFICIAL ONES WITH MUSHY PEAS !!!!!!!!! ^ - ^</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402244589000">kidney pie\/fish and chips</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402250834000">You should review the British newspapers for those type pf restaurants</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402254617000">Fish and Chips Roast Beef and Yorkshire Pudding Pie and Mash and Mushy Pease Steak and Kidney Pie</answer><suggestions>yorkshire/ORGANIZATION pudding/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402255549000">a nice curry lol</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402260271000">Bangers and mash -LRB- sausage and mashed potato -RRB- Sunday roast fish n chips with mushy peas Pot brownies -LRB- available everywher but hey weeds good anywhere -RRB-</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402265990000">tea</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402306443000">Baileys Fish and Chips - this is awesome and typical english !</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402339516000">Fish and chips</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140616160015AAkjHsB">
	<title>Where is the best place to eat in Miami at affordable prices ?</title><suggestions>miami/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>Can be anywhere in Miami or Ft. Lauderdale</content><suggestions>miami/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402959645000">McDonalds/ORGANIZATION</answer><suggestions>mcdonalds/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402971140000">Grazianos in downtown Miami or in Weston in Broward county is unbelievable . They serve 16 oz Cowboy Ribeyes that melt in your mouth with a side of mushrooms and fries for $ 18.95 . Anywhere else the same steak is $ 79 . This is assuming that $ 18.95 is affordable for you . La Caretta in Miami has been serving scrambled eggs with ham and potatoes , Cuban bread and Café con leche for $ 4.95 for decades . . They are also located in Pembroke Pines Florida on University and Pines blvd. .</answer><suggestions>miami/LOCATION weston/LOCATION broward/LOCATION county/LOCATION la/LOCATION caretta/LOCATION miami/LOCATION pembroke/LOCATION pines/LOCATION florida/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403005271000">THAT BUS STOP i forget where . . you know miami face eater bus stop</answer><suggestions>miami/LOCATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140618152135AAfsqHx">
	<title>Where in NYC can I enjoy strippers and eat sushi ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I am trying to take the beau out for a special bday celebration</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403130206000">There is this great spot in Queens . It 's called Tempura Tits . You can literally eat sushi off of strippers . . .</answer><suggestions>queens/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403130254000">i do n't know but if such a place exists and you find it , you have an obligation to tell all males ... ever</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403139177000">If you cant find the place ... let me know . I will order some california rolls and twerk in your faces while you enjoy ur sushi rolls . I have fair prices .</answer><suggestions>california/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403139281000">Your mums house</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403140514000">Anywhere ! Just order a stripper in and eat her .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403159151000">I guess I 'm a little taken aback that you want to take your beau out to see strippers . Why would n't you want to take your beau to a nice restaurant where you can enjoy some sushi and some other form of entertainment ? For a big celebration , why do you want to do something sleazy ? Not a fan .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403175616000">moms house</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403196127000">I want to know</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403266393000">Try Vegas</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140610172137AA9hoaq">
	<title>when does the sugar factory open up in chicago ?</title><suggestions>chicago/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>Ok so i live in Chicago and i been to the sugar factory restaurant in Las Vegas and loved it and i heard that their making one here where i live but when i look for the info about when it 's opening i cants find it and i want to know if anyone knows when it 's going to be opened here</content><suggestions>chicago/LOCATION las/LOCATION vegas/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402455863000">The owner of the Sugar Factory American Brasserie selected Rosemont as the company 's first Midwest location due to the owner 's fondness of the greater Chicago area . Formed in 2009 with operations on both coasts and in Las Vegas , the Sugar Factory for the first time will expand to the Midwest opening its candy-themed restaurant and retail space in MB Financial Park at Rosemont this summer . Company spokesperson Jessica Murray said there are also plans to open a Sugar Factory in downtown Chicago later in 2014 . `` The reason Rosemont was selected is because the owner loves the Rosemont and greater Chicago area , '' Murray said . `` She especially likes the Rosemont space and is very excited about expanding to the Midwest . '' Murray said the owner , Chrissa DaVidovica , has two young daughters and designed much of the Sugar Factory restaurant 's candy theme from a child 's viewpoint . The restaurant is known to draw celebrities . Murray said they expect the same in the Rosemont location . The hours are not finalized for the new 8,000 sq. ft. location or are the number of employees to be hired , but Murray said the restaurant will be serving lunch , dinner , brunch and a variety of menu and bar items along with the candy offerings . Once the Sugar Factory opens in the former `` My Big Fat Greek Restaurant '' space , all the available spaces in the entertainment district will be occupied . The Sugar Factory restaurants and retail stores have locations in Las Vegas , Hollywood and New York City and also plans to open its first international retail space in Bahrain this summer .</answer><suggestions>sugar/ORGANIZATION factory/ORGANIZATION american/ORGANIZATION brasserie/ORGANIZATION rosemont/PERSON midwest/LOCATION chicago/LOCATION las/LOCATION vegas/LOCATION midwest/LOCATION rosemont/LOCATION jessica/PERSON murray/PERSON chicago/LOCATION rosemont/LOCATION rosemont/LOCATION chicago/LOCATION murray/PERSON rosemont/LOCATION murray/PERSON chrissa/PERSON davidovica/PERSON murray/PERSON murray/PERSON greek/LOCATION las/LOCATION vegas/LOCATION hollywood/LOCATION new/LOCATION york/LOCATION city/LOCATION bahrain/LOCATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140603140146AAA2DGN">
	<title>Best tacos in Arlington , Grand Prairie , Irving , Texas ?</title><suggestions>arlington/LOCATION grand/LOCATION prairie/LOCATION irving/LOCATION texas/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>What is a good spot to get tacos in arlington , irving , or grand prairie area.Only good ones i know of is azteca , Want to find something closer to arlington . Mexican tacos not a tex mex restaurant like taco bueno or taco bell . .</content><suggestions>arlington/LOCATION irving/LOCATION arlington/LOCATION tex/ORGANIZATION mex/ORGANIZATION taco/ORGANIZATION bueno/ORGANIZATION taco/ORGANIZATION bell/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401829556000">fuzys taco shop ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403478895000">Anywhere in the are . . Taco Casa . . http:\/\/www.tacocasatexas.com\/showStore.php?id=66</answer><suggestions>taco/ORGANIZATION casa/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140615191331AAdpnmg">
	<title>Do McDonalds/ORGANIZATION still only put a half slice of cheese in their Fillet-o-Fishes ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>And are they still stingy with the tartare sauce ? The last time I bought one was 5 years ago and it was dry , tasteless and there was n't enough tartare sauce to dip the fries in . Also , why did they change the recipe ? Please do n't tell me it was cut costs because I could n't be alone in not buying them anymore .</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402890027000">Ya</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402894623000">I had n't had one for years until a few months ago . There was so much tartar sauce on it I had to scrape it off with a French fry . It was really disappointing . I did n't notice if the cheese was any smaller but it was kind if a mess . I wo n't be ordering one again anytime soon .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402966192000">Get a Double Fillet - only a $ 1.00 more , better deal -- more meat : -RRB- And yeah , the cheese is small .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402993413000">Yes</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140616143448AAdU6Ze">
	<title>Name all of the restaurants on FastFoodMenuPrices.com and Fast Food Menu Prices the app ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>A&W/ORGANIZATION , Arby/ORGANIZATION 's , Baskin-Robbins/ORGANIZATION , Bojangles/ORGANIZATION ' , Boston/ORGANIZATION Market/ORGANIZATION , Burger/ORGANIZATION King/ORGANIZATION , Cafe/ORGANIZATION Rio/ORGANIZATION , Captain/ORGANIZATION D/ORGANIZATION 's , Carl/ORGANIZATION 's Jr. , Checkers/ORGANIZATION , Chick-fil-A/ORGANIZATION , Chipotle/ORGANIZATION , Church/ORGANIZATION 's Chicken/ORGANIZATION , Culver/ORGANIZATION 's , Dairy/ORGANIZATION Queen/ORGANIZATION , Del/ORGANIZATION Taco/ORGANIZATION , Domino/ORGANIZATION 's , Dunkin'/ORGANIZATION Donuts/ORGANIZATION , El/ORGANIZATION Pollo/ORGANIZATION Loco/ORGANIZATION , Fatburger/ORGANIZATION , Fazoli/ORGANIZATION 's , Firehouse/ORGANIZATION Subs/ORGANIZATION , Five/ORGANIZATION Guys/ORGANIZATION , Hardee/ORGANIZATION 's , In-N-Out/ORGANIZATION , Jack/ORGANIZATION in/ORGANIZATION the/ORGANIZATION Box/ORGANIZATION , Jamba/ORGANIZATION Juice/ORGANIZATION , Jason/ORGANIZATION 's Deli/ORGANIZATION , Jimmy/ORGANIZATION John/ORGANIZATION 's , KFC/ORGANIZATION , Krispy/ORGANIZATION Kreme/ORGANIZATION , Krystal/ORGANIZATION , Lee/ORGANIZATION 's Famous/ORGANIZATION Recipe/ORGANIZATION Chicken/ORGANIZATION , Lion/ORGANIZATION 's Choice/ORGANIZATION , Little/ORGANIZATION Caesars/ORGANIZATION , Long/ORGANIZATION John/ORGANIZATION Silver/ORGANIZATION 's , McAlister/ORGANIZATION 's Deli/ORGANIZATION , McDonalds/ORGANIZATION , Moe/ORGANIZATION 's , Noodles/ORGANIZATION & Company/ORGANIZATION , Oberweis/ORGANIZATION , Pancheros/ORGANIZATION , Panda/ORGANIZATION Express/ORGANIZATION , Panera/ORGANIZATION Bread/ORGANIZATION , Papa/ORGANIZATION John/ORGANIZATION 's , Penn/ORGANIZATION Station/ORGANIZATION , Pizza/ORGANIZATION Hut/ORGANIZATION , Pizza/ORGANIZATION Ranch/ORGANIZATION , Pollo/ORGANIZATION Tropical/ORGANIZATION , Popeyes/ORGANIZATION , Potbelly/ORGANIZATION , Qdoba/ORGANIZATION , Quiznos/ORGANIZATION , Raising/ORGANIZATION Cane/ORGANIZATION 's , Rally/ORGANIZATION 's , Round/ORGANIZATION Table/ORGANIZATION Pizza/ORGANIZATION , Shake/ORGANIZATION Shack/ORGANIZATION , Smoothie/ORGANIZATION King/ORGANIZATION , Sonic/ORGANIZATION , Starbucks/ORGANIZATION , Steak/ORGANIZATION 'n/ORGANIZATION Shake/ORGANIZATION , Subway/ORGANIZATION , Taco/ORGANIZATION Bell/ORGANIZATION , Tim/ORGANIZATION Hortons/ORGANIZATION , Togo/ORGANIZATION 's , Wendy/ORGANIZATION 's , Whataburger/ORGANIZATION , White/ORGANIZATION Castle/ORGANIZATION , Wienerschnitzel/ORGANIZATION , Wingstop/ORGANIZATION , Zaxby/ORGANIZATION 's and/ORGANIZATION Zoup/ORGANIZATION !</content><suggestions>arby/ORGANIZATION 's/ORGANIZATION boston/LOCATION carl/PERSON culver/LOCATION del/ORGANIZATION taco/ORGANIZATION domino/PERSON dunkin'/ORGANIZATION donuts/ORGANIZATION el/LOCATION pollo/LOCATION loco/LOCATION fazoli/ORGANIZATION hardee/PERSON jack/PERSON jamba/LOCATION juice/LOCATION jason/PERSON jimmy/PERSON john/PERSON kfc/ORGANIZATION krystal/PERSON lee/PERSON john/PERSON silver/PERSON mcalister/PERSON mcdonalds/ORGANIZATION moe/PERSON oberweis/PERSON panda/ORGANIZATION express/ORGANIZATION john/PERSON penn/LOCATION station/LOCATION qdoba/LOCATION quiznos/ORGANIZATION starbucks/ORGANIZATION taco/ORGANIZATION bell/ORGANIZATION tim/PERSON hortons/PERSON togo/LOCATION wendy/PERSON zaxby/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402956645000">Arby/ORGANIZATION 's Baskin-Robbins/ORGANIZATION Bojangles/ORGANIZATION Boston/ORGANIZATION Market/ORGANIZATION Burger/ORGANIZATION King/ORGANIZATION Captain/ORGANIZATION D/ORGANIZATION 's Chick-Fil-A/ORGANIZATION Chipotle/ORGANIZATION Church/ORGANIZATION 's Culver/ORGANIZATION 's DQ/ORGANIZATION Del/ORGANIZATION Taco/ORGANIZATION Domino/ORGANIZATION 's Pizza/ORGANIZATION Dunkin/ORGANIZATION Donuts/ORGANIZATION El/ORGANIZATION Pollo/ORGANIZATION Loco/ORGANIZATION FatBurger/ORGANIZATION Five/ORGANIZATION Guy/ORGANIZATION 's Hardee/ORGANIZATION 's In/ORGANIZATION & Out/ORGANIZATION Jack/ORGANIZATION in/ORGANIZATION the/ORGANIZATION Box/ORGANIZATION Jamba/ORGANIZATION Juice/ORGANIZATION Jimmy/ORGANIZATION John/ORGANIZATION 's K.F.C./ORGANIZATION Krispy/ORGANIZATION Kreme/ORGANIZATION Lion/ORGANIZATION Choice/ORGANIZATION Long/ORGANIZATION John/ORGANIZATION Silvers/ORGANIZATION Mcdonald/ORGANIZATION 's Panda/ORGANIZATION Express/ORGANIZATION Panera/ORGANIZATION Bread/ORGANIZATION Papa/ORGANIZATION Johns/ORGANIZATION pizza/ORGANIZATION hut/ORGANIZATION popeye/ORGANIZATION 's chicken/ORGANIZATION land/ORGANIZATION Qdoba/ORGANIZATION Quizno/ORGANIZATION 's Rally/ORGANIZATION 's Smoothie/ORGANIZATION King/ORGANIZATION Sonic/ORGANIZATION Starbucks/ORGANIZATION Steak/ORGANIZATION & Shake/ORGANIZATION Subway/ORGANIZATION 's Taco/ORGANIZATION Bell/ORGANIZATION Wendy/ORGANIZATION Restaurant/ORGANIZATION Whataburger/ORGANIZATION White/ORGANIZATION Castle/ORGANIZATION Wienerschnitzel/ORGANIZATION</answer><suggestions>arby/PERSON boston/LOCATION culver/PERSON domino/PERSON dunkin/PERSON hardee/PERSON jack/PERSON jamba/LOCATION juice/LOCATION jimmy/PERSON john/PERSON john/PERSON silvers/PERSON mcdonald/PERSON panda/ORGANIZATION express/ORGANIZATION papa/PERSON johns/PERSON popeye/PERSON qdoba/LOCATION quizno/PERSON taco/ORGANIZATION bell/ORGANIZATION wendy/PERSON wienerschnitzel/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402957034000">So are you going to pick yourself as best answer ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140611234202AAi9C6B">
	<title>I wish to act in Indian TV commercial ads . Kindly suggest how should I go forward with it . I live in Mumbai . ?</title><suggestions>mumbai/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>I am also interested in print ads . My email id is punam_id@yahoo.co.in .</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402586757000">First of all , you should get noticed by an ad agency to feature in any media . For this , you can prepare a portfolio - a file containing your photographs , normally taken by a photo-studio specialised in this - and visiting the offices of ad agencies . Another method is to act in college plays or street plays and who knows , you will be watching you !</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402588879000">Thanks a lot for your response . But I would like to know of some good ad agencies whom I can approach .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402761003000">Did you try to do a search on Google ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140623072617AAIXida">
	<title>Has anyone noticed different McDonalds/ORGANIZATION use different sized patties in their Big Macs ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>Sometimes the patty is almost the same circumference as the bread , and sometimes it 's only about half as big . Which size is it supposed to be ?</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403533673000">By `` half as big '' I mean half the area , not half the circumference .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403534380000">If your local store is using smaller burger patties they are n't buying them from the McDonald/ORGANIZATION 's corporation . McDonald/ORGANIZATION 's uses very strict quality checks to make sure that every burger is exactly the same as all the others .</answer><suggestions>mcdonald/ORGANIZATION 's/ORGANIZATION corporation/ORGANIZATION mcdonald/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403537295000">or the volume ...</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403538330000">Yes , I 've noticed this too . I think what happens is that they all cook differently . Also , sometimes the ground beef is just put into patties of different sizes . I would feel free to complain to the manager that your burger is tiny and last time you were there it was twice as big . Also I think mccoyblues works for McDonald/ORGANIZATION 's or something like that because he 's saying how great the quality checks are and stuff . True story , I ordered 20 piece chicken McNuggets there once , and one had a bite out of it . Yes , someone had EATEN part of MY chicken nuggets . I was disgusted and told the manager . All I got were some silly giftcards , and her saying that it totally was n't her fault ! After that , I have not gone back to McDonald/ORGANIZATION 's since except when friends I was with wanted to eat there , too .</answer><suggestions>mcdonald/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403539273000">I have n't notice this , to be honest . I quite fancy a Big Mac right now . .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403545250000">I work at McDonalds/ORGANIZATION unfortunately . The same \* small \* Patties used on the Big Mac are the same patties that are used on the smaller burgers like Hamburgers , Cheese Burgers , McDoubles . Small meat is called -LRB- 10-1 -RRB- The large sized meat -LRB- 4-1 -RRB- is used on Quarter Pounder Sandwiches only . So , the Big Mac , is n't really big and you 're getting played out of your money .</answer><suggestions>mcdonalds/ORGANIZATION big/ORGANIZATION mac/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403548573000">Fake meat .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403559156000">i agree the meat patty is way too small and thin ; they should make them thick and juicy like Burger Kings burgers . make sure to complain if you 're being cheated .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403562638000">The Big Mac sandwich uses two 1.6 ounce patties , the same ones used for the regular hamburger , cheeseburger , McDouble and such . If some idiot used they 4 ounce patties to make a Big Mac , the meat would n't even fit properly on the bun so there 's no way it would n't be noticed and no way that it would be `` policy '' at any location . The whole concept behind a franchised restaurant chain is CONSISTENCY , if a franchisee were to start selling a Big Mac that were two and a half times larger they 'd end up losing their franchise . If you did get a Big Mac that was had 8 ounces of meat instead of the proper 3.2 ounces , well then somebody screwed up big time .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140603215034AABtnxF">
	<title>Best nice , but casual menu restaurants in NYC ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>So me and a friend are looking to eat somewhere nice in NYC soon . Price is not an issue , we do n't mind spending for a good experience . We like all types of food and are open to basically anything - american , italian , seafood , asian , etc. . We want it to be a nice place , if possible with a nice view and outdoor seating , but I know I 'm already limiting my choices here with everything we 're looking for . Anyway , I 've researched best restaurants , restaurants with a view and all that good stuff . The problem is all the places have such higher class menus . I know this is to be expected to a degree , but are there any really nice restaurants around with a more casual menu . American where they have a burger and fries , italian where they 'll have pene ala vodka , or more common things like that . We 're looking for a nice place but still want the food we love . Again , we 're not worried about the cost . Any suggestions are welcomed . Thanks .</content><suggestions>american/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401860056000">Www.godiningout.blogspot.com checkout third link on</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401860993000">Google it .</answer><suggestions>google/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401874895000">best restaurants</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401876211000">All are good . .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401880123000">johns pizzeria is great except they can take a while to get you your food because it is usually pretty full but we didnt have to book so it was great .</answer><suggestions>johns/PERSON pizzeria/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401891549000">You want burgers in NYC but money is not an object ? Try these : http:\/\/most-expensive.com\/burgers-world</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402397147000">All are good . .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402756821000">Le Rivage on restaurant row ,</answer><suggestions>le/LOCATION rivage/LOCATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140620003333AAaN90M">
	<title>Wave Hubb @@ +91 981011835 1 # Wave Hubb Noida ?</title><suggestions>noida/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>+91 981011835 1 | | Wave Hubb , Wave Hubb Noida , Wave Hubb Retail , Wave Hubb Sector 18 , Wave Hubb Sector 18 Noida | | @ +91 981099385 1 Wave Hubb Sector 18 Noida : After grand success of many commercial project like Wave Metro Mart at Sector 32 Noida , Wave One and Wave Silver Tower in Sector 18 Noida , Wave Infratech is going to launch its new commercial project WAVE HUBB in Sector 18 Noida . A new opportunity for investment at one of the prime location of Noida with Metro connectivity already . These retails shops are specially designed to offer glorious opportunities for everyone . A G +2 retail shopping complex : Wave HUBB is one in all solution of daily needs . For more details , visit : http:\/\/www.wavehubb.com http:\/\/www.aadhargroup.in\/wave-hubb-noida.html Project Location Advantages : Wave Hubb Located at Sector 18 Noida Project - Highlights : '' Air Conditioned with power back up shopping complex . '' State-of-the-art retail house . '' Situated within the heart of satellite town Noida . '' Stone throw from Noida Sector Eighteen railway Metro station . '' Exudes modern and stylish characteristic . '' Design speaks of up to date style with description of high standards . '' Maximize daylight in work surroundings with the employment of windows . '' Most visibility to retail space with most scope for stigmatisation . '' Vertical show windows provides a grandeur to the complete business complicated . '' Curtain glazing to convey transparency and clarity to the activities happening within the complicate</content><suggestions>noida/LOCATION noida/ORGANIZATION noida/LOCATION noida/LOCATION noida/LOCATION noida/LOCATION noida/LOCATION metro/ORGANIZATION noida/LOCATION noida/LOCATION noida/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403253692000">wow pretty nice</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140618103521AAfeF87">
	<title>subway prices ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>Does anyone know the current price of an Italian BMT 6 in and foot long from subway I know it is around $ 7.26 for a foot long</content><suggestions>bmt/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403112973000">Call your local Subway and ask them . Depending on where you live , the prices can vary .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403125212000">i would cut the foot long price in half , and then add maybe a dollar . im guessing they want to make the foot long seem like a good deal , so theyll charge more for the 6 inch</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403180080000">You can simply check out the prices on the internet . Prices for most of the items are mentioned on the different sources or you can visit some blogs or the listing website to know more .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403192572000">Go into the fuck1ng store for yourself b1-tch .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403254613000">the prices vary by location</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140613052638AAHwjzY">
	<title>Bar Salsa London/LOCATION ?</title><suggestions>london/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>Hi , I 'm planning on going to Bar/LOCATION Salsa/LOCATION restaurant and nightclub for my birthday , the opening time says something from 5pm - 2am . When does the club open like if I have dinner from 5-6 :30 ? Also can a friend not come to dinner and just meet me for clubbing there instead ? Thanks !</content><suggestions>bar/LOCATION salsa/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402664094000">300</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402664108000">uou can</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402669046000">What</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402669333000">yeps , there is some place with girls over there named LA LOLA</answer><suggestions>la/PERSON lola/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402673734000">yes</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140617194830AAHJTRC">
	<title>What happens to excess egg yolks in fast food chains ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>Many fast food -LRB- and I suppose regular -RRB- restaurants offer egg white versions of breakfast meals or sandwiches . Regardless of whether the eggs are made on site or pre-made in a factory - what happens to the extra egg yolks ? Are they perhaps put into the batch of eggs that do n't have the yolks removed ? Meaning the normal egg option would actually have more yolk than usual ? I 'm sure some factories might use it in other products they produce like baked goods , but I 'm hoping someone has had experience in a restaurant or factory that could tell me what their process was .</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I 'm not concerned , I eat egg yolks . I 'm genuinely wondering about the process from someone who might have been behind the counter .</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403059816000">They give them to the cat .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403060610000">Most fast food places do n't use real eggs . They use the stuff in cartons or frozen scrambled eggs . In other words most of these places are fast , but there is very little real food involved . You would be terrified if you knew what really goes into the cheap food and how much it costs your health . Subway recently removed the material in the bread that is used in YOGA MATS . So you could eat your sandwich or do downward facing dog on it !</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403090260000">Whites and yolks can be purchased separately .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403094332000">If you are concerned DON `` T GO THERE</answer><suggestions>don/PERSON</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140610112505AAhGjYL">
	<title>Are tips mandatory to pay in restaurants in America ?</title><suggestions>america/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>So the other day I went out eating with my friends and I had just enough money for my order . When the bill came in , the server crossed out the total including the tax , and added the money for the tip . I asked my friends if we had to pay the total including the tip and they said yes , but I 've always thought tips were just a courteous gift and was n't part of the actual bill . So is there a certain price where tips are required to be paid ?</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402424795000">in diners and simple restaurants - it is more of a gift but in nicer and fancier restaurants - regardless of your bill you have to pay at least 15 % tip .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402425227000">No , not mandatory , strictly voluntary . That s why tightwad jerks stiff wait personnel by not giving them a deserved tip . Although I have seen places that automatically add gratuity charge to bill , but they are rare .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402426274000">Yes it 's actually 20 % now</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402427293000">Voluntary TIP = To Insure Proper Service . Sucky service no tip !</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402427413000">It 's not mandatory , you can tip if you want to , if you do n't leave one , the waiter is likely to stop acting so nice to you after dinner is over</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402427505000">its actulally up to u if you want to leave a tip or not but would be rude if you dont since they gave you service serving your food getting your drink etc. .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402427698000">Going to a restaurant and not tipping is like going to the playground of an elementary school and screaming obscenities at the little kids . It 's not illegal , but it 's something that only a huge asshole would do . If you can only afford to spend $ 10 , then you can only afford to buy $ 8.70 worth of food . That 'll be $ 10 with a 15 % tip .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402429419000">Tipping is not mandatory , but you should tip on quality of service average about 15 % -20 % . Some high end restaurants add a mandatory 18 % or more to the bill for large parties\/tables that require more service . For bad service you might still want to leave a `` small '' tip so the server knows you did n't forget to tip , but was unhappy with the service .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402430847000">It would depend upon how many of you there were in the party . Most restaurants will automatically add a tip if there are more than a certain number of people - usually 6-8 people . In groups that large or larger , tipping would be mandatory and there is usually a sign near the front or on the menu . A party that large takes a lot more of the server 's time and effort to take care of . One party of 6 + people can take that server away from 2-3 other tables , so their effective tips are reduced . Also , a large party is taking up more tables that could otherwise be turned over faster and would produce more in sales . That is why tipping is mandatory on larger parties . Even if you all asked for separate bills , they would likely add that service charge , because that creates even more work for the restaurant . In other words , I you plan on eating out at a restaurant , you should make sure that you have enough money for both your food and a reasonable tip . Otherwise , order a less expensive or smaller meal with the money you do have available .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402431069000">Dunno</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402431156000">It 's not mandatory , but servers make in the vicinity of $ 3 an hour . They live off of tips . Until they get paid minimum wage , tipping should be considered mandatory . But as others have said , the size of your party can affect whether or not a tip is included .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402431591000">Yes , the USA/LOCATION is crazy like that . Richest country in the world and can not even pay their people proper wages . Nowhere in the world do you have to tip like this .</answer><suggestions>usa/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402433891000">Only if the menu states a mandatory tip is added to the bill . Otherwise , my tip is '' get a better job '' ...</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402434804000">Just tip</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402455068000">I tip . I do n't tip rude , careless waiters . If they are busy but attempt to try to get you serviced , I just tip under 10 % .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402911549000">Yes it 's 20 % tip</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140622003739AAdUNRt">
	<title>mcdonalds/ORGANIZATION metime service quiz answers ?</title><suggestions>mcdonalds/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<content>Have been stuck on this for a while , would be great if you could share me the answers ; - -RRB- Thanks !</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403452223000">No , sorry .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140605102530AA17S7s">
	<title>\* Best Answer \* Help me name my blog ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>Hi ! My name is Kyle/PERSON Garland/PERSON and I 'm going to be starting a food blog on London and the South-East -LRB- London/LOCATION , Surrey etc. . -RRB- Can anybody think of a witty , clever name -LRB- including part of my name if possible -RRB- for me to name my blog ? Best answer gets a vote : -RRB- Thank you ever so much .</content><suggestions>kyle/PERSON garland/PERSON london/LOCATION london/LOCATION surrey/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401989266000">Blog</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401990457000">bst tricks-4u</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401990763000">Garland 's Garnish ... i want 10 % of the site profits : -RRB-</answer><suggestions>garland/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401991818000">yes</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401993127000">KylesEateryStyle</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401996826000">Call it Kyle 's Kulinary Konversations . I can see no reason that would n't work out .</answer><suggestions>kyle/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401998237000">call it Kyles Kitchen or KK for short</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402001628000">Garland 's Gastronomy</answer><suggestions>garland/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402018740000">Garland-Flowers or Food ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402050261000">Eats by Kyle .</answer><suggestions>kyle/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402065935000">Oh , if only it were that easy ! People are suggesting names that sound good , but there is a lot more to choosing the right blog name than that . If you want your blog to do well -LRB- attract lots of visitors and make you some money -RRB- choosing a blog name that is short , memorable and easy to spell is essential . If someone hears you say `` Kyle 's Kulinary Konversations '' at a party\/in passing , they just are n't going to know that the spelling is not with a C ! You will also find that having a really long blog name like this makes it easy for spelling errors when people type in your URL - and spelling errors mean that people either get told there is no such page - or someone else 's blog gets a visit ! I would strongly recommend that you do a little research into what makes a great blog name - if you 're serious about blogging and care about your blog being successful . If you want a quick and easy summary , here 's a really useful article on the key points to consider when choosing a blog name - link added below . It also links to a blog name generator - so you can get more ideas for your blog name ! Best of luck !</answer><suggestions>kyle/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402133744000">k Kyles</answer><suggestions>kyles/PERSON</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140604112329AAS36PD">
	<title>Is Stilton cheese sold in any major supermarket chain in the USA/LOCATION ? Also what does it taste like ? Swiss , cheddar etc. . ?</title><suggestions>usa/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>Or is it too regional or whatever to be popular .</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401907427000">You should be able to get it at whole foods or any fine foods store . I too wonder what it tastes like . I saw it on how it 's made but never really looked for it It has a similar taste to blue cheese It 's said to cause odd and vivid dreams if eaten before bed . Now I really want to try some !</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401909455000">I buy it at Stater Bros. in California/LOCATION . Find it also at Pavilions , Vons and Ralphs all in Southern California . Taste wise very unique . Similar to Gorgonzola , but not quite as strong in my opinion . Swiss and Cheddar have their own unique tastes but compared to Stilton can be considered mild . On line try : 1 - igourmet.com\/stilton.asp 2 - Buy Stilton Cheese online -LRB-888-RRB- 253-8436 Best Artisan Cheese & Meats Buy Stilton $ 9.99 & up @CleverHen</answer><suggestions>california/LOCATION vons/ORGANIZATION ralphs/ORGANIZATION southern/LOCATION california/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401987069000">Yes , it 's widely available . I bought some yeaterday at a King Soopers near me in Denver/LOCATION , but thay also have it at Whole Foods , Safeway/ORGANIZATION , Wegman/ORGANIZATION 's on the East Coast ... It 's a blue cheese .</answer><suggestions>denver/LOCATION safeway/ORGANIZATION wegman/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402039706000">foods store</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402045589000">food store ...</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402061765000">You should be able to get it at whole foods or any fine foods store .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402107312000">You should be able to get it at whole foods or any fine foods store .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402479079000">foods store .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140622183237AAlmEtx">
	<title>Why does Dominoes need to do a `` quality check '' on their pizza ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I ordered a pizza from Dominoes on-line and they gave me an up to the minute report of what they were doing . Order Placed , Prep , Bake , Quality Check , and Delivery . Well , it 's kind of nice to get immediate feedback of just where my order is in the process , but I wonder -- what is the quality check stage ? After they bake it and before they deliver , do they really do a quality check on the pizza ?</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403487560000">they are keeping you updated on your order you can call them or their might be something you can click to stop the updates</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403488783000">So you get all the items you ordered and that the items you 've ordered have the correct toppings , , etc. .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403489278000">It 's to make sure that the pizza has the proper ingredients that you ordered and meets the high quality standards of Domino/ORGANIZATION 's . They 've always done it more or less but it 's more about making people who look at the pizza tracker feel like their special pizza is getting the VIP treatment .</answer><suggestions>domino/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403489569000">Not sure .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403490367000">Yes</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403492224000">They need to make sure the pizza is as low quality as possible so they can save money .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403502665000">actually it helps them as much as it does you , for better quality of your pizza , and better customer service . if something is wrong in the process , this helps them to identify which step is not working or needs to be changed , sometimes its an employee that needs to be changed . : -RRB-</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403533715000">Yes they do . Every restaurant -LRB- if they are worth eating in -RRB- makes sure the order is correct and the food is cooked according to their high standards before they serve it to the customer .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403540042000">That order tracker thing is a really good feature actually . I guess they would give the pizza a quick visual check - to make sure the toppings are correct and its not burnt or anything .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140610075021AAwlDsA">
	<title>Where to make big money as a server in Miami/LOCATION area ?</title><suggestions>miami/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>We are moving to Miami/LOCATION in August . I 've heard it 's not the best time for server jobs but I also know the turnover rate in the restaurant business so I am hoping I could get lucky . I consider myself a professional server with five years of experience in casual dining , resort style , and a little fine dining as well . I would prefer to work at a popular spot where I can make over 200 every night . 200 is a decent night for me now , but I 'd like to aim higher where 200 would be a slow night . If possible I 'd like to keep it more casual dining but I 'd be willing to do fine dining too . I 've heard some servers in Miami/LOCATION can make around $ 100,000 a year that would be awesome ! I 'm also open to the location . We will most likely live outside the city , maybe even closer to hollywood/LOCATION , aventura or around coral gables . But im willing to commute up to a half hour into city or wherever . Also I can speak some spanish not a lot though , in case that matters .</content><suggestions>miami/LOCATION miami/LOCATION hollywood/LOCATION aventura/PERSON coral/LOCATION gables/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402420375000">McDonalds/ORGANIZATION</answer><suggestions>mcdonalds/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402422494000">Well , Miami/LOCATION is pretty big . But the first thing that comes to my mind is Hooters . Depending if you got some or not .</answer><suggestions>miami/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402425683000">See www.bestincomeguide.com</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402538352000">Give us some more information .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>

