<question id="20140615215502AAWIjLB">
	<title>Does this Social Security count as Welfare for my job application ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I was applying for a job online when I came across this question : `` Have you or a member of your immediate family received any type of government assistance such as TANF -LRB- Temporary Assistance for Needy Families -RRB- , AFDC or any other type of welfare program in the form of a check , debit card or direct deposit in the past 2 years ? '' I am 18 years old , never had a job before , and my mother died about 5 years ago . Because of that , I have gotten a few social security checks in the mail this year , and I was wondering if that counted as welfare for this application . I do n't want to make it seem like we 're in an economic struggle and use foodstamps , because my father has a good enough job to support us comfortably . Does the SS checks I 've gotten count as a type of welfare , and will the employers look at it badly if it 's marked yes ? There 's a Yes , No , and Unsure box to check , so idk what to do .</content><suggestions>tanf/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402895848000">that is an Infrigement however as the area as you you are at a loss , as they have more as you in most cases they give the job as you and sack as the day ends . so be correct and answer as yes and get the interview . you have not as application lied . also many people are on help not only you why shame go for it the new start as a new . and the best of all as the new .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402902273000">I agree with the first answer</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402927827000">If you had been on welfare the employer could get a tax break , that would give you an advantage in getting a job . HOWEVER , since social security is not considered any form of welfare , you have to answer `` No '' . .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402936377000">It is not welfare . Sorry to hear about your mother .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140619190906AAxXT6l">
	<title>what are the best hospitals in San/LOCATION Francisco/LOCATION ?</title><suggestions>san/LOCATION francisco/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>Trying to get medical insurance and need to decide which hospital to go to . Thank you very much .</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403232473000">yes</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140623005211AAQ4eOc">
	<title>Cheap Swimwear in Australia/LOCATION ?</title><suggestions>australia/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>Where are some shops in QLD , Australia where they sell cheap swimwear ? $ 10 - $ 35</content><suggestions>australia/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403510445000">Kmart/ORGANIZATION . Maybe big W or Target . You are asking for cheap swimwear in Winter , your choices are VERY limited . You might find a Millers outlet with some clearance stuff still in stock if you are lucky otherwise you are fresh out of luck .</answer><suggestions>kmart/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140609111240AAvCNqw">
	<title>Where can I find a job in Fort/LOCATION Worth/LOCATION , Texas/LOCATION ?</title><suggestions>fort/LOCATION worth/LOCATION texas/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>I 'm 16 years old and I am looking for a job that is NOT a fast food restaurant . I DO N'T want to work somewhere that requires serving or making food . Any suggestions , please and thank you !</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402342546000">Here are several dozen for you . http:\/\/www.snagajob.com\/job-search\/w-fort+worth,+tx\/q-teen?radius=10</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402358032000">I like eTeenJobs . They have a great website set up for teenagers looking for summer jobs . They help you start thinking about your career after school and have tons of information . http:\/\/www.eteenjobs.com Hope this helps !</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140608112522AAMjxU9">
	<title>Were can I get fireworks in LA ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I 'm looking for some powerful illegal fireworks not that cheap TNT fireworks ... anyone know were I can get some in LA/LOCATION ?</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402268527000">Here 's the deal with the fireworks in Los/LOCATION Angeles/LOCATION County/LOCATION very dry no water big problem if you wanted to get some really powerful illegal fireworks you 're looking at South the border Mexico/LOCATION then your Taking A huge chance of bringing that I would recommend it just because of the fire hazards and the trouble you get into should Get caught with them ! However unofficial doing this but Ventura/LOCATION County/LOCATION used to have Red devil fireworks stands in Fillmore and all over Ventura/LOCATION County/LOCATION by there . however I would highly recommend that you do n't do any Fireworks Unless city bus beautiful type of performance of fireworks very hazardous very dry plus I 'm not sure if Ventura County still allowing hut</answer><suggestions>los/LOCATION angeles/LOCATION county/LOCATION mexico/LOCATION ventura/LOCATION county/LOCATION ventura/LOCATION county/LOCATION ventura/LOCATION county/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403035524000">How about just DO N'T . Los Angeles county is under a heavy drought , fire risk is HUGE , and even a single spark can set off a massive wildfire . Please do n't put other people 's lives , homes and business at risk .</answer><suggestions>los/LOCATION angeles/LOCATION county/LOCATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140610174552AAptb2t">
	<title>Will my package be delivered tomorrow ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I live in Staten/LOCATION lsland/LOCATION , NY and the package is shipped by UPS Mail innovations . Around 12:50 pm its was updated saying its in Edgewood/LOCATION , NY/LOCATION , United/LOCATION States/LOCATION says the : Package received for sort by destination UPS Mail Innovations facility . Will i be getting it tomorrow i would like to know cause i need it by then . Please answer if u can . I would just really like to know . Thank you !</content><suggestions>staten/LOCATION lsland/LOCATION edgewood/LOCATION united/LOCATION states/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402452723000">Call 1-800-PICK-UPS .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140619110535AAA13D9">
	<title>How do I know if a website is legitimate ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>Here is the website : https:\/\/worldpatentmarketing.com\/ They seem like they might not be scammers , but I ca n't be too sure . Is there a way to see if websites like these are real or not ?</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403201585000">If you can see the https as the protocol , that only means that it was granted by the internet to be safe and secured to users .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403204974000">You really ca n't , but you need to do you due diligence . Google/ORGANIZATION their name and see what people are saying . check their facebook page , check the BBB link to see if there have been complaints . @Redz The https means it passes information over the internet securely - not that the website wo n't scam you . Any website can purchase the ssl certificate .</answer><suggestions>google/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140616030742AAiRtlk">
	<title>How long does singpost registered delivery parcel takes to reach me ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>It 's my first time registered for registered mail . The sender is from Singapore/LOCATION , so is local sending to local .</content><suggestions>singapore/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402936288000">Registered mail is secure mail , but slow moving mail . Everyone that handles it , must sign for it . It can take longer than you think .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140603053113AAVRR5O">
	<title>is there any true form filling or data entry job in India that pays in INR -LRB- indian rupes -RRB- and paid by cheque ?</title><suggestions>india/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>best will get 10 points . .</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401827937000">That 's difficult to answer as all I have is questions ??? First , do you know the value of a Rupee ? And why would they pay you by check when PayPal/ORGANIZATION is available all over India/LOCATION . The last I knew , today , the Rupee is worth $ 0.017 , or less than 2 cents , and Indians do n't pay US wages , and contract labor like you are indicating you are interested in , wo n't pay you much at all . I once worked for an Indian company and wrote over 100 articles for them one month , then their website was down for 2 months and came back as a different name . I never got paid . Good Luck , but be careful . John/PERSON</answer><suggestions>paypal/ORGANIZATION india/LOCATION john/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401867593000">There are such companies but they do not pay the high salaries that frauds promise . You can ask me for details . contact leadlion98 at yahoo dot com</answer><suggestions>yahoo/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140613214814AARwXS4">
	<title>What places hire at 15 in Oregon/LOCATION ?</title><suggestions>oregon/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>I do n't want those answers of `` mow lawns '' or `` babysit '' I want to make REAL money . Not 20 $ every couple of days . Links are appreciated . Thanks !</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402726488000">I know this guy that does stuff with meat in the back of his van . He hires young people all of the time . Must work em ' hard though . I always see them limping when they leave his van .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402740616000">I like eTeenJobs . They have a great website set up for teenagers looking for summer jobs . They help you start thinking about your career after school and have tons of information . http:\/\/www.eteenjobs.com Hope this helps !</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402753365000">Feel free to reach out to me for tips\/help getting started ! Here 's my blog which should explain most of it : http:\/\/jeffcollier251.wordpress.com\/</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402786181000">in the US/LOCATION under FLSA a minor 14 or older may work in an : Office , Grocery store , Retail store , Restaurant , Movie Theater , Baseball Park , Amusement park , or Gasoline service station Businesses such as Publix/ORGANIZATION , Kroger/ORGANIZATION 's , Food/ORGANIZATION Lion/ORGANIZATION , Sonic/ORGANIZATION , Chic-Fill-A/ORGANIZATION , McDonald/ORGANIZATION 's , Winn-Dixie/ORGANIZATION , Krystal/ORGANIZATION 's , Dairy/ORGANIZATION Queen/ORGANIZATION , and Burger/ORGANIZATION King/ORGANIZATION along with smaller local businesses that are in the same genre tend to hire those your age . Fast-food and grocery stores are willing and able to train new employees but ... ... ... ... ... Minors tend to have many issues that affect their ability to work such as tardiness , absenteeism , numerous schedule requests , poor work-ethic etcetera . I am NOT implying you will have those issues but the fact that many your age do makes it more difficult for you to get an opportunity to prove your worth . Because of this you must be able to show through words and actions that you are reliable , dependable , punctual , detail oriented , coach-able , mature , and team oriented . You will also need great references since you do n't have work experience . Talk to teachers , counselors , clergy , coaches , club sponsors , and directors of places you have volunteered or people you have done casual labor for and ask them about giving you a reference . Get accurate , current contact information for them and ask them to be ready to get calls for references from potential employers . Remember : Most businesses are individually owned and operated so it is the owner 's policy and past experience with minors that will determine if they will hire you . Apply everywhere you can , the worse that can happen is they do n't hire you . click on the following link for information about child labor laws http:\/\/www.youthrules.dol.gov US Department of Labor YouthRules</answer><suggestions>us/LOCATION flsa/ORGANIZATION publix/ORGANIZATION kroger/ORGANIZATION mcdonald/ORGANIZATION 's/ORGANIZATION winn-dixie/ORGANIZATION krystal/PERSON us/ORGANIZATION department/ORGANIZATION of/ORGANIZATION labor/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140608012413AAjMA7a">
	<title>Where is best place to buy cheapest quality watches ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>See more : http:\/\/bonomax.com</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402216229000">CHECK SOME BEST JOBS FOR YOU http:\/\/www.naukribhandar.blogspot.com\/</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402233630000">Michelle 's is spam for a Vietnamese scam site created 2014-02-20 . https:\/\/www.networksolutions.com\/whois\/results.jsp?domain=bonomax.com We see spammers spamming the spam . The Report Abuse function is currently ineffective .</answer><suggestions>michelle/PERSON</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140609124251AAzYE7J">
	<title>What is like to work at a liquor store ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>Has anybody worked at a liquor store ? Is it fun ? Or is target better ?</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402343395000">You 're more likely to get robbed at a liquor store .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140609214747AADyA9I">
	<title>what public place hires at 14 ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>its summer and I need a summer job so I have some money and I need a public job like stores or something . im 14 turning 15 in November who and where would hire me ?</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402452824000">The supermarkets , and fast food places .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402461738000">Feel free to reach out to me for tips\/help getting started ! Here 's my blog which should explain most of it : http:\/\/jeffcollier251.wordpress.com\/</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140622225954AAAlKMt">
	<title>phan tich dau van tay o dau ?</title><suggestions>phan/PERSON tich/PERSON dau/PERSON van/PERSON tay/PERSON o/PERSON dau/PERSON</suggestions>
	<content>Sinh trắc học vân tay nghe có vẻ đáng tin . Mình đang có nhu cầu , có tham khảo vài nơi như Mr Hưng 0917 377 491 ở http:\/\/phantichvantay.vn Giá bên này 3tr1 , ổn chứ các bạn ?</content><suggestions>sinh/PERSON trắc/PERSON học/PERSON vân/PERSON tay/PERSON nghe/PERSON mình/PERSON đang/PERSON có/PERSON nhu/PERSON cầu/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403503982000">Neu phan tich van tay o ha noi thi ban su dung dich vu cua ban Hung do duoc do . Anh chi minh da dung dich vu cua ban nay . Ho se cu nguoi den tan nha de quet dau van tay cua be roi thay bao chuyen du lieu sang tan Singapore de phan tich . Khoang 1 tuan sau chuyen gia den phan tich dau van tay chi tiet va ti mi lam . Kham pha duoc nhieu dieu ve be lam ban a ! Xin loi vi may minh ko co vietkey nen ko go co dau duoc :-LRB- Ban cu lien he truc tiep ban Hung do hoac dang ky tren web http:\/\/phantichvantay.vn y. Luc ho goi dien tu van thi cu hoi ky vao .</answer><suggestions>neu/PERSON phan/PERSON tich/PERSON van/PERSON tay/PERSON o/PERSON ha/PERSON noi/PERSON thi/PERSON nguoi/PERSON den/PERSON tan/PERSON nha/PERSON de/PERSON quet/PERSON dau/PERSON van/PERSON tay/PERSON cua/PERSON bao/PERSON chuyen/PERSON singapore/LOCATION phan/PERSON tich/PERSON khoang/ORGANIZATION tuan/PERSON sau/PERSON chuyen/PERSON gia/PERSON den/PERSON phan/PERSON tich/PERSON dau/PERSON van/PERSON tay/PERSON chi/PERSON tiet/PERSON va/PERSON ti/PERSON mi/PERSON lam/PERSON kham/PERSON pha/PERSON duoc/PERSON nhieu/PERSON dieu/PERSON xin/PERSON loi/PERSON vi/PERSON may/PERSON minh/PERSON ko/PERSON co/PERSON vietkey/PERSON nen/PERSON ko/PERSON dau/LOCATION duoc/LOCATION y./PERSON luc/PERSON ho/PERSON goi/PERSON dien/PERSON tu/PERSON van/PERSON thi/PERSON cu/PERSON hoi/PERSON ky/PERSON vao/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403504117000">Neu phan tich van tay o ha noi thi ban su dung dich vu cua ban Hung do duoc do . Anh chi minh da dung dich vu cua ban nay . Ho se cu nguoi den tan nha de quet dau van tay cua be roi thay bao chuyen du lieu sang tan Singapore de phan tich . Khoang 1 tuan sau chuyen gia den phan tich dau van tay chi tiet va ti mi lam . Kham pha duoc nhieu dieu ve be lam ban a ! Xin loi vi may minh ko co vietkey nen ko go co dau duoc :-LRB- Ban cu lien he truc tiep ban Hung do hoac dang ky tren web http:\/\/phantichvantay.vn y. Luc ho goi dien tu van thi cu hoi ky vao .</answer><suggestions>neu/PERSON phan/PERSON tich/PERSON van/PERSON tay/PERSON o/PERSON ha/PERSON noi/PERSON thi/PERSON nguoi/PERSON den/PERSON tan/PERSON nha/PERSON de/PERSON quet/PERSON dau/PERSON van/PERSON tay/PERSON cua/PERSON bao/PERSON chuyen/PERSON singapore/LOCATION phan/PERSON tich/PERSON khoang/ORGANIZATION tuan/PERSON sau/PERSON chuyen/PERSON gia/PERSON den/PERSON phan/PERSON tich/PERSON dau/PERSON van/PERSON tay/PERSON chi/PERSON tiet/PERSON va/PERSON ti/PERSON mi/PERSON lam/PERSON kham/PERSON pha/PERSON duoc/PERSON nhieu/PERSON dieu/PERSON xin/PERSON loi/PERSON vi/PERSON may/PERSON minh/PERSON ko/PERSON co/PERSON vietkey/PERSON nen/PERSON ko/PERSON dau/LOCATION duoc/LOCATION y./PERSON luc/PERSON ho/PERSON goi/PERSON dien/PERSON tu/PERSON van/PERSON thi/PERSON cu/PERSON hoi/PERSON ky/PERSON vao/PERSON</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140625100949AAuIkTO">
	<title>USPS/ORGANIZATION - Out for delivery 2 days ago , have n't received package . ?</title><suggestions>usps/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<content>The tracking for USPS/ORGANIZATION showed that my package arrived in my zip code and was out for delivery early Monday morning , but since then , I have n't received the package and the status has not been updated . I called the USPS station for my zip code and all the customer service rep did was take my information down and said she 'll have someone call back . Does anyone know what might have happened ? Is this normal ? Because from my past experience I usually get it the same day it says out for delivery .</content><suggestions>usps/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403717134000">Contact the USPS/ORGANIZATION customer service at 1-800-ASK-USPS and give the tracking number . They ought to know what should be done next . If they have not discovered where the package is , get the rep 's full name and ask that they call you back at a specific time -LRB- when you will be available -RRB- to discuss how to remedy the situation . If they are not cooperative , ask to speak to someone higher up in the chain .</answer><suggestions>usps/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140605195407AAKcWWL">
	<title>Package went missing ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>Hello , so i ordered a package from plndr.com -LRB- it is a street wear clothing company -RRB- it is 100 % legit , i buy stuff from here almost once a month ! I got a package shipped awhile ago , and it has scheduled delivery for today , but i sent it to my dads house , not mine -LRB- NYC btw -RRB- It said it was delivered today at 1:22 pm in the afternoon , I go to look on the tracking information , and it says it was received , and the ups guy met the customer man -LRB- even though my dad says he did not get any package at all . Has anyone else had this problem ? This was over $ 150 of clothing , and I will be very bummy and sad if it got stolen , or lost -LRB- GOD FORBID -RRB- do you think they just made a mistake ? What should I do ? If I contact the website , do you think they would send me another package out of my same material , without paying , or fully refunding my money ... do companies usually do that ? Please help !!!</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402187371000">I 've never had that happened to me . But it looks like you got scammed .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140617164637AAddgz5">
	<title>Can I hand my package over to the USPS/ORGANIZATION Driver when he comes to pick up the mail ?</title><suggestions>usps/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<content>Hello ! I won a bid for a MacBook Air case online only later to then find out it only fits 11 '' MacBook Air 's . I wanted to cancel it but the eBay/ORGANIZATION seller said they already shipped it out , they said that I can refuse it when it arrives so I am planning to do that . I do n't want my parents to find out about the package because it is a gift to them but Im going to have to get a refund to buy the correct size . -LRB- I can not drive either -RRB- so I can not go to the post office . I want to manually hand it the USPS/ORGANIZATION Driver the next day after I 've written `` refused '' on it can I do that instead of heading to the post office ? Thank You</content><suggestions>macbook/ORGANIZATION air/ORGANIZATION usps/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403050518000">You certainly can do that .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403053484000">Yes , you can do that .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403056353000">Off course you can .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140610194612AA31tgA">
	<title>What does accepted at USPS/ORGANIZATION Origin Sort Facility Jun-09-14 , 21:31 PM , ENGLEWOOD/LOCATION , NJ 07631 mean when tracking your package on ebay ?</title><suggestions>englewood/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>My mom bought me a tablet on ebay . i tryed tracking it . and this showed up . what does it mean ?</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402454901000">It means that the seller has dropped it off at the Post Office , and it 's on the way to you .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402454921000">Your package was accepted at a sort facility . There are thousands of sorting facilities all over the country , which are like `` checkpoints '' for mail - they get scanned -LRB- which updates the tracking page for you -RRB- and are re-routed to the proper transportation to the next sorting facility near you , and from there it will be put on a truck and delivered to your mailbox\/doorstep . Keep watching daily and watch your package get scanned at sorting facilities closer and closer to you .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402496214000">As mail passes through the sorting machines , a record of the mail is created and tracking information is sent out . If your package went through a sort facility , it should be out for delivery the same day , or maybe early the next morning .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402586000000">It was mailed and scanned into the system .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140620172230AAfuPAg">
	<title>my package didnt come ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>i ordered a used amp from a guitar center in pennsylvania/LOCATION on Monday at night . It 's supposed to be shipping to texas/LOCATION , and its been 4 days , i didnt come today either and i never got the tracking number in my email . . what . what happened , my packages from guitar center usually come in 3 days . tomorrow is Saturday , will it be here</content><suggestions>pennsylvania/LOCATION texas/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403310428000">Timing on package delivery is never exact . Strange you did n't get a tracking number . if it 's not in by Monday I would contact the company .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140622124551AAdVqpC">
	<title>Jewlery Boutique Name Ideas ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I am starting a small , instagram based jewlery boutique . I am a teenager and I 'm going to be making the pieces & all , but I need a name idea . I am planning on making the shop like @Bleu__print and @MysticumLuna on Instagram . Please take a look at their shop styles if you 'd like to see kind of what I 'll be doing . I am not copying them , or going to do anything that would be `` stealing their ideas '' , I am making my own , unique jewlery , it will just be similar to those . I will be doing tattoo chocker necklaces , charm chokers , gem stones , ect . like that . I need some Ideas for names now . I do not want to use my name at all ! I do not mind people knowing who I am , but I just do n't want a personal named brand as my shop . Please help me think of some !! -LRB- It also needs to be able to be used as a instagram username !</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403466381000">Family Jewels</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403466876000">I am not trying to make a Family boutique . I am doing this on my own , with a little purchasing help from my mom . I want names that are very `` boho '' or `` gypsy '' sounding because that is the crowd I am attracting from my beginning advertising . Thanks for the help , though !</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140615091428AA1nGW3">
	<title>where can i get my flooring done for cheap in niagara/LOCATION falls/LOCATION ?</title><suggestions>niagara/LOCATION falls/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>I 'm looking for a place that will do my carpet really well but for a good price in the niagara/LOCATION falls/LOCATION st/LOCATION catharines/LOCATION area . I 'm willing to pay any price as long as it 's reasonable .</content><suggestions>niagara/LOCATION falls/LOCATION st/LOCATION catharines/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402849087000">my wife and i got our flooring done by A + professional flooring we really like how it turned out and we got it installed for about $ 1500 for our entire basement area which i find is a pretty good deal</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403272229000">More info please</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140607144411AAJhsta">
	<title>How to get my hands on a gun ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>Now i should make it clear that i am not one of those lunatics that go into schools and kill innocent children . I simply wish to get one gun -LRB- Any gun -RRB- and one bullet for myself . The gun laws in my country are extremely strict and it 's not like i can fed ex it . What kinda places have been known to sell them or should i say borrow them . Just name some examples if you can . By the end of this year i will be no more and i accept that fact . I simply wish to go down in a manor of my choosing and not something painful like drowning or hanging . If you can help me i would be immensely grateful but if you ca n't help me then please do us both a favor and do n't comment .</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402196767000">http:\/\/www.jw.org\/en\/video-why-study-the-bible\/</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140625001351AA0XSyr">
	<title>Please let me know some household goods store we could shop online . ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>Please let me know some household goods store we could shop online . I would prefer fashionable ones dealing with a variety of items .</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403687062000">the best chinese products sale Platform , save your money . want to see ? click : www.shoppingease360.com</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403693277000">WANT TO DO FREE SHOPPING JUST REGISTER YOURSELF VIEW ADS \* & ENJOY FREE SHOPPING !!! THE BEST AND FREE SHOPPING PORTAL www.paidon.in \* login daily to earn maximum products</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140616200702AA6Pms8">
	<title>Anyone know what this building is ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>This building in Los/LOCATION Angeles/LOCATION , I unfortunately do not recall which street we were on , features a large cow statue as well as three goose statues , all on the roof . The only signage merely says `` Moo '' twice . The only other possible hint is that above a door in the front is the word `` Westinghouse . '' I 've tried Google/ORGANIZATION to no avail ; anyone know what on Earth this place is ?</content><suggestions>los/LOCATION angeles/LOCATION westinghouse/ORGANIZATION google/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402978835000">Its a resturant .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140620035947AAeYEbM">
	<title>What companies deliver bottled water in greenville/LOCATION , sc ?</title><suggestions>greenville/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>I want a water cooler in my home , and have water bottles delivered . I ca n't seem to find good info for such a company in the greenville/LOCATION sc/LOCATION area/LOCATION . Or is some sort of filter better ? Any suggestions for either ?</content><suggestions>greenville/ORGANIZATION sc/ORGANIZATION area/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403270571000">I think amazon can .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403292167000">we got all strains of kush and medical Marijuana but we recommend these high grades we got Tex us with what you need : : : :-LRB- 631 -RRB- 621-8869 grape syrup with cannabinoids \* Actavis promethazine w\/codeine purple cough syrup \* Green Crack : : : : : : : : : Grade A + Top Shelf \* Sour Diesel : : : : : : : : : Grade A + Top Shelf \* Grand Daddy Purple : : : : Grade A + Top Shelf \* Sensi Star x ak47 : : : : : Grade AAA Top Shelf \* Afghan Kush : : : : : : : Grade A + Top Shelf \* Northern Lights : : : : Grade A + Top Shelf \* Lemon drop : : : : : : : : Grade A + Top Shelf \* Purple Kush : : : : : : Grade A + Top Shelf \* OG Kush : : : : : : : : : Grade AA + Top Shelf \* Blue dream : : : : : : : Grade A + Top Shelf \* White widow : : : : : : Grade AA+T op Shelf we sell the kush at 1 ounce for $ 220 1\/8 pound for $ 350 1\/4 pound for $ 650 1\/2 pound for $ 1300 1 pound for $ 2500 10 seed for $ 60 Oil for $ 30 a gram shipping $ 25 we do ship independent of country , city , state Contact Email : jeffschemicals24@gmail.com Tex us with what you need : : : :-LRB- 631 -RRB- 621-8869</answer><suggestions>tex/LOCATION us/LOCATION tex/LOCATION us/LOCATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140607104826AAF23WO">
	<title>how does a 22 year old hardworking man start his own concrete business ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I am 22 and have grade A work ethic . I work for a large scale concrete company but 16 \/ hour isnt really fulfilling my lifestyle . I know everything there is to know about making streets driveways and sidewalks . Just about anything concrete wise . I am also very skilled in tile flooring . My question is how do I get started on being self employed ? Whay legal documentation do I need and . I know I need some kind of license and insurance or something ? I live in Columbus/LOCATION Ohio/LOCATION</content><suggestions>columbus/LOCATION ohio/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402320027000">I sa a blog post on this the other day , give me 5 min to check browser history .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402332757000">Take a couple of courses about Small Business at your local community college . You may have the technical knowledge , but not how to run a business .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140603131218AA1t3hP">
	<title>I need a good iPhone 4 repair shop in SD Mission/LOCATION Valley/LOCATION area ?</title><suggestions>mission/LOCATION valley/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>Looking for a local reliable iPhone repair shop around mission/LOCATION valley/LOCATION area in San/LOCATION Diego/LOCATION that is cost affordable and reliable ?</content><suggestions>mission/LOCATION valley/LOCATION san/LOCATION diego/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401827397000">I do n't think there an be any value repairing . See how much you can get for broken phone for part and buy used phone .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401835605000">My Buddy and my Sister went to Apple Techs in Mission/LOCATION Valley/LOCATION East/LOCATION , off Mission Gore ... ... I want to say they are on Twain Ave behind Jack in the box ... ... Their repair for iphone 4 's broken screens are cheap in pricing , i think it 's $ 55 or $ 60 , and i can honestly say they do good work ... . . Check them out . I don '' t recall their phone number but it should be on their website ... ... Hope you find this of any help .</answer><suggestions>mission/LOCATION valley/LOCATION east/LOCATION gore/PERSON jack/PERSON</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140610040156AAtbQ4M">
	<title>I want to know the availability of gel permeation chromatography in chennai for my sample ... ?</title><suggestions>chennai/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>For the analysis of my sample i need to know the place where they are doing gel permeation chromatography , i also want to know the price for the analysis ...</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402398188000">ststst</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402398502000">Sry genta i didnt get ur ans can u abbreviate ur ans pls</answer><suggestions>genta/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402528758000">Also do n't forget to search this on Google/ORGANIZATION .</answer><suggestions>google/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140621073010AAv9Xv2">
	<title>Where can i buy Squeezy Freezy in toronto/LOCATION ?</title><suggestions>toronto/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>i live in Scarborough , ON</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403361188000">http:\/\/psnboss.com\/?ref=zBfUFcsEu5</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140607204711AAtWX4j">
	<title>What are some ways to get put in your local hospital ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I am not meaning to do this but im asking how are the reasons you can ? Because Im just wonder how to . I never noticed what I say somtimes but this time I am but a friend asked this and wanted me to ask here .</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402261916000">A heart attack will get you in .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>

