<question id="20140611200656AADQgAb">
	<title>is it possible to fly with just the clothes on your back or even without any clothes ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>i always wonder if i jumpp out my window if i will ever just fly up and not even get hurt , i mean its probably no possible but people can do a lot of things with their mind , with their strength and im pretty sure it is possible to fly some how if anyone knows anyways to fly other than jumping out of a plane or using some type of jetpack or anything please let me know , teach me i am a good student with things i would really love to learn , i am a guy btw this is my sisters email im 15 years old if anyone can help me i will pay them back some way some how , please dont think im crazy ive never did any drugs to be stupid , its a fantasy of mine but i also know it can be real for some people</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402543117000">Earth has gravity so whatever that you throw up it will always fall down to the ground . unless you are tight with something . Study more in school , I am sure one day you will success inventing something .</answer><suggestions>earth/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402587619000">No human being has yet learned to fly unaided .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402596898000">The closest thing to that is wingsuit jumping , but that 's really just gliding , like a huge flying squirrel .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140604152901AACS3Yj">
	<title>What tour and travel company in Uganda can provide good gorilla trekking and tracking ?</title><suggestions>uganda/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>am interested in traveling to Uganda for a safari tour and a holiday</content><suggestions>uganda/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401921058000">Ape Treks will do that the best . They offer tour safaris and holidays beyond Uganda . tour safaris to Zanzibar , Ethiopia , Rwanda , Burundi and around Africa . There email is info@apetreks.com</answer><suggestions>uganda/LOCATION zanzibar/LOCATION ethiopia/LOCATION rwanda/LOCATION burundi/LOCATION africa/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401921257000">Yes , Ape treks for Uganda safari tours and travel , gorilla trekking and tracking , holidays , etc. there are good . my friend used there tour operator and it was a great adventure</answer><suggestions>uganda/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402084497000">try google it also</answer><suggestions>google/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140604115540AAQrGu2">
	<title>Are there any interior pictures or videos on the Fantasyland/LOCATION rides BEFORE the 1983 overhaul in Disneyland/LOCATION ?</title><suggestions>disneyland/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>such as Snow White , Peter Pan , Pinnochio , etc. .</content><suggestions>peter/PERSON pan/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401922738000">I 've seen some . Look for home movies of Fantasyland from the 60 's , or Disney/ORGANIZATION public relations films celebrating various anniversaries .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401985866000">Yes , there are . But keep in mind that the technology was very primitive by today 's standards . Having a `` movie '' camera was a luxury . You recorded on 8mm film back then . Videotape for the masses was still a few years off in 1983 . So you 'll have to find some home movies . Here is one such movie : http:\/\/www.youtube.com\/watch?v=mb_8aAMoPRg</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402070214000">try google it also</answer><suggestions>google/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140607024930AAQZT27">
	<title>anyone know any mom and pop video game stores in Phoenix AZ ?</title><suggestions>phoenix/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>That might be willing to sell cod Advanced Warfare early ?</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402190840000">I sa a blog post on this the other day , give me 5 min to check browser history .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140617213812AAnm3nS">
	<title>First time Orlando trip ?</title><suggestions>orlando/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>I am taking my nieces and nephews to Orlando in December for a week we are from MN so this is probably a once in a lifetime trip for us . They will be 17,16,16 , and 10 . They love thrill rides so we are planning to go to Universal/LOCATION and Islands of Adventures for 1 day . Disney/ORGANIZATION for 2 days and SeaWorld/ORGANIZATION for 1 day . Then the beach for a day . My question is are we planning to much and are we crazy or is this possible with 2 days of parks beach day then 2 more parks before we fly home ? We have picked out rides at all parks that we want to ride and per day it 's not anymore than what we do in a day at our local theme park . Just questioning because it 's new and a lot bigger .</content><suggestions>orlando/LOCATION disney/ORGANIZATION seaworld/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403067341000">it 's very reasonable ! not saying that you wo n't be tired by the end of the trip ... but a good beach day in the trip will really even everything out . I can tell you from experience that i 've gone down to florida and `` park hopped '' and had an awesome time !</answer><suggestions>florida/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403068470000">Your plan is realistic . Get `` Park Hopper '' tickets for WDW/ORGANIZATION and spend a half-day at each park . Do realize Orlando/LOCATION is about 90 minutes drive -LRB- each way -RRB- from the nearest beach actually on the ocean . I expect that being from an inland state you want to go to the beach and that is fine , but it will be a grind unless you spend the night . If it were me , I would depart for the beach in the mid-afternoon of the day for Sea World . Spend the night at a hotel ON the beach and return to Orlando/LOCATION the next afternoon . Do understand it will be too cool to swim in the ocean in December in Florida/LOCATION , except maybe at Key West . Finally , WDW/ORGANIZATION , Universal , and Sea World are not close to each other . I recommend staying at a hotel at WDW/ORGANIZATION and using it as a base for visiting the other parks -LRB- taxi or rental car -RRB- . That way you can also visit WDW in the evenings .</answer><suggestions>wdw/ORGANIZATION orlando/LOCATION orlando/LOCATION florida/LOCATION wdw/ORGANIZATION wdw/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403094207000">I think you 'll be busy and exhausted , but that 's what these kinds of vacations do to you : -RRB- I would actually advise against getting the Park Hopper tickets at Disney/ORGANIZATION - you wo n't have time to see or do anything in just a half day at each park . However , December is a great time to go -LRB- assuming you are n't going around Christmas -RRB- in terms of crowd levels , so you should be able to see and do a lot . If you have 5 full days , then I would suggest this : \* Day 1 - Universal \* Day 2 - Sea World \* Day 3 - beach -LRB- maybe leave on Day 2 after Sea World , stay the night , come back in the evening of Day 3 -RRB- \* Day 4 - Magic/ORGANIZATION Kingdom/ORGANIZATION or Hollywood/ORGANIZATION Studios/ORGANIZATION -LRB- Disney/ORGANIZATION -RRB- \* Day 5 - Magic Kingdom or Hollywood Studios I would stay on Disney property , at least for your Disney days , so that you can take advantage of Extra Magic Hours and the transportation services to Disney/ORGANIZATION .</answer><suggestions>disney/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403094521000">That sounds like a great schedule . They are all young , so being on the go the whole time will be fine . We did that sort of thing when we were younger . You will need a vacation from your vacation , but I guess that I do n't understand people who can lay around a pool or the beach for a week . Now , I am not saying I would do what you are doing . I would personally rather spend the entire week at Disney/ORGANIZATION , but that is just me . Universal does have some great thrill rides and I think your nieces\/nephews will love it . We went to Sea World in San Antonio in March . We had not been to a Sea World in about 10 years , and I have had my fill of it for another 10 . It is a fun place if you have never been , but I do n't feel like I need to go back all that often . So , if it sounds fun to you , and you want a very active vacation , then it is fun . Have a blast .</answer><suggestions>disney/ORGANIZATION san/LOCATION antonio/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403095516000">Wow ! You 're going to be exhausted . With the new Fastpass + system it makes it more difficult to do the ParkHopper . If it was me , I would skip the beach & do 3 days at WDW . I would go to Magic Kingdom , Disney/ORGANIZATION 's Hollywood/ORGANIZATION Studio/ORGANIZATION &/ORGANIZATION Epcot/ORGANIZATION for 3 whole days . If you decide to only do 2 days , then I would do MK one day & then either DHS or Epcot the other day . It 's so sweet of you to take your nieces & nephews . Have a great time !</answer><suggestions>disney/ORGANIZATION hollywood/ORGANIZATION studio/ORGANIZATION &/ORGANIZATION epcot/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403099728000">Disney/ORGANIZATION parks can take a full day to get through . I would put that day off in the middle of the parks . The beach is not that close to Orlando . staying by the pool and than going to Downtown Disney/ORGANIZATION may be another option . and for a once in the life time trip-STAY AT A DISNEY/ORGANIZATION RESORT When in December are you going ? IF you are going during normal school 's winter break note the parks are going to be jammed packed .</answer><suggestions>disney/ORGANIZATION parks/ORGANIZATION orlando/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403150296000">Wow that sounds like a lot of fun . I think its reasonable . I recently went down to orlando , did a day at universal and two days at disney/ORGANIZATION . I really enjoyed universal . Universal also has City Walk -LRB- which is free -RRB- and lots of fun to walk around at night !! Either way you will have a lot of fun . If you really want the once in a life time experience stay at a hotel in disney/ORGANIZATION . Universal is like 25min from disney/ORGANIZATION so its your call as to whether you want to transfer hotels or not . The hard rock hotel at universal is incredible but expensive . There a number of nice hotels right outside universal that are cheaper and bus you to the park . Personally I would skip sea world . I went their years ago and it was a disappointment . First of all its insanely expensive . Second , I ca n't bear to see the animals basically imprisoned there , knowing they are treated so poorly . If you do n't know what I am talking about , just google it . Have fun</answer><suggestions>orlando/LOCATION disney/ORGANIZATION disney/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403184264000">Sounds like a packed , but do-able schedule . They 're older kids so they 'll be easier to keep organised . But I would definitely take a minute and think about if you want to go to seaworld . Its not a sanctuary or a center of conservation like they like to say . Not a single animal that enters the park or is born there has ever been released . They die after a short life in a tank , when they should have been swimming 100 miles a day . Giving them money is telling them `` I am okay with this , here 's some money so you can continue to do it . '' Not the best example for the kids .</answer><suggestions>seaworld/LOCATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140624203758AAyLMD9">
	<title>Is walking in Newark , NJ safe ?</title><suggestions>newark/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>Thanks for the answers . I 'm glad walking should be relatively safe . I thought it would be but I figured it would be better to ask now than be sorry I did n't later !</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403695317000">It 's been years since I walked around Newark , so I ca n't say for sure . But the fall-back position , since you 're concerned -- why not just take a cab ? With a short distance , the cost should n't be much . Take a look as you 're going along , and if everything looks fine , you can walk back .</answer><suggestions>newark/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403703912000">You should be fine . Downtown Newark -LRB- along with the Ironbound section -RRB- is relatively safe .</answer><suggestions>newark/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403711317000">Daytime should be totally safe . I would walk on Raymond Blvd. . Penn Station has a number of places where you could wait , and purchase fattening junk food . Raymond does not have much where you could wait , and I hope the day is not too hot and sunny as there is little shade . Market does , as the name suggests , have a few places .</answer><suggestions>raymond/PERSON raymond/PERSON</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140612013350AAX11Xr">
	<title>What is the cheapest travel from UK to France ?</title><suggestions>uk/LOCATION france/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>Hey , I heard coach is cheap but does anyone know any good companies where I can get some cheap deals . This is important as I am not living in London so I will need something cheap which includes traveling to London . Thank you</content><suggestions>london/LOCATION london/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402564090000">I think it 's train ... !!</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402564812000">London to Paris from # 15.00 on http:\/\/uk.megabus.com\/</answer><suggestions>london/LOCATION paris/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402567356000">Megabus as Gerd says . Or Eurolines which do London to Paris from # 19 one-way http:\/\/www.eurolines.co.uk\/ Mind you , if you book early and do n't mind when you go , Eurostar deals are from # 69 return . MUCH quicker than the coach http:\/\/www.eurostar.com\/uk-en\/eurostar-deals</answer><suggestions>megabus/ORGANIZATION gerd/PERSON london/LOCATION paris/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403044875000">Try Eurolines .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140608120927AA1JZcv">
	<title>If it 's true that the British driving on the left way came from the ancient Romans ' ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>Horse riding and driving times , does that mean that the rest of the former Rome 's dependencies were car driving one way and horse riding\/driving the other way during their transition from horses to cars ?</content><suggestions>rome/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402256078000">Driving on the left most certainly did NOT come from the Romans . The Romans left the British Isles about 1,500 years before cars became common -LRB- to any extent -RRB- .</answer><suggestions>romans/ORGANIZATION isles/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402256791000">The Wikipedia article has the story about the Romans driving on the left in Britain : http:\/\/en.wikipedia.org\/wiki\/Right-_and_left-hand_traffic#History</answer><suggestions>wikipedia/ORGANIZATION britain/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402257190000">Everyone `` drove '' or more accurately rode on the left , because most people are right handed and it was easier to draw a sword and fight . When Napoleon/PERSON came to power he changed -LRB- as he changed everything -RRB- and his allies and our `` enemies '' also changed</answer><suggestions>napoleon/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402267112000">Yes . Romans in Britain kept to the left , this can be confirmed by looking at the wheel ruts at Roman quarry entrances . Unladen carts going in on the left , laden carts coming out obeying the same rule . The laden carts wore deeper grooves into the roadways .</answer><suggestions>britain/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402270256000">It is entirely to do with Horse riding because we mount and dismount our horses on their left hand side and as we do so we are standing on the verge at the left of the road . Where people ride or drive on the right , this means they must mount and dismount in the middle of the road which is dangerous . https:\/\/www.youtube.com\/watch?v=H1CijzSi3TM</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402323904000">Yes it started with the Romans -LRB- or even before -RRB- as most people being right handed , it left your sword arm free , whether you were on foot , on horseback or in a cart or wagon . -LRB- Orakle I 'm astonished to read that the Romans left the UK before cars were common - you live and learn ! -RRB- Napoleon/PERSON was left handed , and he changed the side of the road to the right so he had his sword arm free . As he did n't invade the UK , despite many attempts , we carried on driving on the left . As Europeans settled in the new world , they took their driving habits with them , and now there are just a few countries -LRB- mostly Islands like the UK and Japan -RRB- that dive on the right as it 's a bit difficult to change the side you drive on at an inland border crossing . Interesting to think that they the side they drive on in many modern democracies was because of an autocratic French emperor with a power complex .</answer><suggestions>uk/LOCATION napoleon/PERSON uk/LOCATION uk/LOCATION japan/LOCATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140609031322AAZz3r8">
	<title>Is Sri Lankan breaking away from -LRB- 3S -RRB- SEA-SUN-SAND tourism and moving towards Eco Tourism ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>Sri Lanka is an island -LRB- total area of 65,610 km , with 64,740 sq km of land and 870 sq km of water -RRB- in the northern Indian Ocean off the southern coast of the Indian subcontinent in South Asia ; known until 1972 as Ceylon , Sri Lanka has is borders with India to the northwest and the Maldives to the southwest by sea -LRB- Its coastline is 1,340 km long . -RRB- Sri Lanka has a documented history that spans over 3,000 years , and consists ancient historical tourism sites , including ` Sigiriya ' which can be claimed as 8th wonder of the world . Hill country of Sri Lanka which was used to grow `` CEYLON TEA '' is just like a green carpet , when traveler moves to there . Sri Lankan people are friendly . Rural culture , village agriculture can be one of the tourist attraction . 30 % of land area coved by forest . Sri Lanka is rich of wild life , -LRB- Land and Marine -RRB- Wildlife of Sri Lanka includes its flora and fauna and their natural habitats . Sri Lanka has one of the highest rates of biological endemism -LRB- 16 % of the fauna and 23 % of flowering plants are endemic -RRB- in the world even though it is relatively small . The costal tourist destination in Sri Lanka is seasonal . In May to October in West Coast Sea is rough . But at that time East Cost Sea is cram . During the other days west coast is cram and east coast is sea is rough . So you can select your destination as such . . In August there is huge cultural & religious procession in central part of Sri Lanka</content><suggestions>sri/LOCATION lanka/LOCATION indian/LOCATION ocean/LOCATION south/LOCATION asia/LOCATION ceylon/ORGANIZATION sri/LOCATION lanka/LOCATION india/LOCATION maldives/LOCATION sri/LOCATION lanka/LOCATION hill/PERSON sri/LOCATION lanka/LOCATION sri/LOCATION lanka/LOCATION sri/LOCATION lanka/LOCATION flora/LOCATION sri/LOCATION lanka/LOCATION sri/LOCATION lanka/LOCATION sri/LOCATION lanka/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402447329000">Well thank you ! You were as great guide and host ... your question ??</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402466903000">Wow , you know many things regarding Sri lanka .</answer><suggestions>sri/LOCATION lanka/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403018250000">Thanks for the bio on my home country , to answer a short question NO it is not moving away from tourism - the country is still recovering from a 26 year war something you failed to mention . Sri Lanka is making great strides and improving the infrastructure as well as many aspects of people 's lives . Eco tourism may be coming but it 's not evident yet . It 's a wonderful country with happy people but the same as every other country in the world it 's not without it 's difficulties .</answer><suggestions>sri/LOCATION lanka/LOCATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140608151316AAZv17m">
	<title>Ned help with planning Disneyland/ORGANIZATION Paris/ORGANIZATION holiday !?</title><suggestions>disneyland/ORGANIZATION paris/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<content>Ok so basically I am planning on taking my sister to Disneyland/ORGANIZATION Paris/ORGANIZATION sometime in the near future . We 've never been away on our own before -LRB- I just turned 18 , she 's almost 16 -RRB- so I wanted it to be just the 2 of us . We need to save up the money first -LRB- this will take a while as we 're not mega rich or anything :P -RRB- but planning ahead , I was thinking of transport . Do I book separate flights or can I do that through the process of booking the actual Disney/ORGANIZATION tickets ? Also how does travel to\/from the airport work if none of us can drive ? As I said I 've never been away before so I have no experience of traveling ! And also how long should we go for ? I dont know much about the actual Disney/ORGANIZATION land Paris attractions so holiday length wise I 'm thinking roughly 3 nights and 4 days , is this too long\/short ? Also my bf who had been like 5 times when she was younger says we should get fast passes or something ?! What even is this ? Does it cost more money ? Also looking for info on weather I should go for food deals and stuff like that . I 'm thinking of going around March\/April time 2015 , is this a good time ?? All help\/advice will be greatly appreciated !</content><suggestions>paris/LOCATION paris/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402290478000">And that , people , is the modern education system for you .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402315886000">At 16 and 18 , I would advice you to use a travel agency near where you live . They will help you work out travel and the tickets as well as your hotel booking . If you just want to ` do Disney/ORGANIZATION ' you best stay near or on the grounds and staying in one of the Disney/ORGANIZATION hotels will be more expensive but it will be easier than when you need to take a bus to get to the park . I do not know about those fast passes , your travel agency will . As you are looking for personal experience , I would say that a friend who has been 5 times should know quite a bit . But if she only went in summer and you go in early spring , you might not need those fast passes as the crowds will be different .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402338355000">Can you be more specific please ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402392751000">The fast pass is just a ticket you get from automats outside the most popular rides . It 's free . You insert your ticket to the park and it prints a ticket with a time . You come back to the ride at the time written on the ticket and then the queue will be very short -LRB- use the `` FastPass lane '' -RRB- . In the meantime you can enjoy other stuff rather than waiting in line . I believe you live in the UK amiright ? You can take Eurostar from London to Paris , only 70 $ return if you book 3 months in advance . Then you can take the metro + RER to get to Disneyland/ORGANIZATION -LRB- very easy but a bit long -RRB- . A cheaper but much more uncomfortable option is national express or megabus -LRB- coach travel -RRB- . No it 's not possible to book flights on Disneyland/ORGANIZATION 's website . They 're no travel agency . If you want the trip planned for you , see a travel agent but remember it 'll be more expensive .</answer><suggestions>uk/LOCATION london/LOCATION paris/LOCATION metro/ORGANIZATION disneyland/ORGANIZATION megabus/ORGANIZATION disneyland/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140623153135AAqXQHR">
	<title>Is New York busy during St. Patrick 's Day week ?</title><suggestions>new/LOCATION york/LOCATION st./LOCATION patrick/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>I am fully aware that there is a parade and a lot of celebrations on St. Patricks day in New York City , but is the week busy with out-of-towners ? My family and I are traveling there for that week -LRB- 13th of March to the 20th -RRB- and are hoping that it is still down season for tourists like the majority of March is ... Of course there will be tourists there , but is it a significant increase ? My family loves to go see Broadway shows , so will getting tickets be a problem with the crowd ?</content><suggestions>new/LOCATION york/LOCATION city/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403566548000">Not too intense . The events do not attract that many from out of town</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140613030213AAZi4zH">
	<title>Pass to travel from Sheffield to Salford and Sheffield to Nottingham ?</title><suggestions>sheffield/LOCATION salford/LOCATION sheffield/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>Hello to everyone ! I would like to know how much is the Pass to travel from Sheffield to Salford , and from Sheffield to Nottingham -LRB- by train -RRB- . I need to know this information as soon as possible because I will go to England , in August , with my boyfriend and we need to know the prices of the transportation in order to organize ourself financially . We are from Portugal , we tried to look up this information in several sites but we do not find it ... Thank you for your help !</content><suggestions>sheffield/LOCATION salford/LOCATION sheffield/LOCATION england/LOCATION portugal/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402693701000">If you are just going to these places less than 4 times per week just buy individual tickets each time you travel by train . An Off Peak Return from Sheffield to Nottingham is # 13.20 . An Off Peak Return from Sheffield to Salford is # 18.30 Off Peak is any train except before 09-30am weekdays . If you are traveling more than 4 times per week on the same route you need a Season Ticket . valid between any two stations for a week , a month , 3 months or a year . Go to www.nationalrail.co.uk and the go to the ` Season Ticket calculator ' section of the site For # 30 you can buy a ` Two Together ' railcard from any railway station which gives you a 34 % discont on all your rail tickets except before 09-30am on weekdays www.railcard.co.uk If you are going to be doing a lot of rail travel in the U.K. while on holiday here you can buy a Britrail Pass before arrival www.britrail.com</answer><suggestions>sheffield/LOCATION nottingham/LOCATION sheffield/LOCATION salford/LOCATION u.k./LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402836130000">Thank you for your answer , I think that it help me a lot . Actually , I will do this route -LRB- Sheffield to Nottingham -RRB- for a year -LRB- 5 days per week -RRB- , and my boyfriend is going to to the other route -LRB- Sheffield to Manchester -RRB- , also for a year -LRB- 5 days per week -RRB- , because we are trying to live in Sheffield . However , we do not know which are the best choices to do in order to save money . If it is possible to live in Sheffield or not . We think that we will have to be in Manchester\/Nottingham at 09:00 am ... So we are studying this hypothesis to live in Sheffield . If the pass is too expensive , I think that we have to live separated . Anyway , thank you very much for your help !</answer><suggestions>sheffield/LOCATION nottingham/LOCATION sheffield/LOCATION manchester/LOCATION sheffield/LOCATION sheffield/LOCATION sheffield/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402873603000">Prices for one year : Sheffield to Salford # 3,408 Sheffield to Nottingham # 2,720</answer><suggestions>sheffield/LOCATION salford/LOCATION sheffield/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402877973000">Also do n't forget to search this on Google .</answer><suggestions>google/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140605044942AAisLvo">
	<title>Where are movie theaters in Bordeaux , France , that play English speaking movies ?</title><suggestions>bordeaux/LOCATION france/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>I 've tried to Google theaters , but no luck . Perhaps someone familiar with the theaters in the area would know better ?</content><suggestions>google/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401970175000">go visit these places</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402048550000">You 'll find the information at this link http:\/\/dordogne.angloinfo.com\/whatson\/movies\/</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402310822000">Most big cities have at least one movie theater that plays movies in `` version originale sous-titrée '' -LRB- original version with subtitles -RRB- We have this very annoying habit of dubbing foreign movies . When you see `` VF '' it means the movie is dubbed . If you see `` VOSTF '' it means it 's in a foreign language with French subtitles . ETA I 've just checked the website of UGC Bordeaux . Except for French movies and kids movies -LRB- makes sense -RRB- , all are played in VOSTF . http:\/\/www.ugc.fr\/cinemaAction!execute.action?id=1&page=7</answer><suggestions>french/LOCATION ugc/ORGANIZATION bordeaux/ORGANIZATION vostf/LOCATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140609221937AAH7tge">
	<title>College , New York , and RENT !?</title><suggestions>new/LOCATION york/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>I am wanting to go to NYU or Columbia here in the fall of 2015 , and to weight my options I was wondering how is life in New York . Is it affordable for college kids ? From what I have seen on Craigslist rent can be $ 1000 and up ! How does a college student afford that ? Also , I am pursuing my acting and writing career . Is there any place in NY that will let a playwright in and also a pursuing actor . Also , is there any advice going into NY like how to work the public transit . What 's the fee for the public transit . Also , seasons .</content><suggestions>nyu/LOCATION or/LOCATION columbia/LOCATION new/LOCATION york/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402396951000">First , Columbia and NYU are amongst the most expensive colleges in the nation -LRB- about $ 50,000 a year -RRB- . Also , both are amongst the most difficult to be admitted to -- you would need super-good grades and SAT\/ACT scores . If you are admitted to either , you would be eligible to live in their dorms , which are much less expensive than trying to get an apartment . So , before you worry about rent , you should seriously look into whether you are likely to be admitted to those schools , and if you are , whether you can afford the tuition . If you 're really serous about attending and this is n't just a fantasy , you should be getting ready to apply in the fall -- meaning looking at their admission requirements , taking campus tours , taking another round of SAT\/ACT exams , starting to work this summer on your admissions essay , etc. . This is the summer when people who want to start college in the fall of 2015 should be getting busy . If you 're not doing any of the above , this is just a fantasy about living in New York .</answer><suggestions>columbia/ORGANIZATION nyu/ORGANIZATION new/LOCATION york/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402417915000">Both Columbia and NYU have dormitories , which will normally be cheaper than renting on the outside -LRB- where $ 1K\/month would be very inexpensive and likely in a terrible slum or ultra remote -RRB- . When I was a Columbia student -LRB- back in the late Stone Age -RRB- I used Hartley Hall , but there are several others , including a couple much newer . For admission in 2015 , start the process not later than January 2015 . There is a large building on Hudson Street dedicated to providing inexpensive housing for those in the arts , but you have to have a good track record established to be considered . You `` work '' public transit by paying . Rides are $ 2.50 each , you purchase a Metrocard , and if you lay out an initial amount of $ 10 or more you get a small discount .</answer><suggestions>columbia/ORGANIZATION nyu/ORGANIZATION columbia/ORGANIZATION hudson/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402434830000">Don has it right . Both of these colleges mentioned are private and tuition is very expensive . In order to get in to these universities , not only your grades in High School , passing the ACT\/SAT as well with curricular activites related to your major is a FACTOR -LRB- yes in caps -RRB- to get there . Now about that ad mentioned from Craigslist for an apartment you seen for $ 1,000.00 , it is a scam . Most people who visited these apartments are ones who take pictures and post them so they can get your money and you loose out to the persons who actually live there . Even if you decide to rent a place , you should have roommates so that expenses can be shared and utilities as well . Your first choice -LRB- if accepted to any of these schools -RRB- is to live in the dorms . Keep in mind rates to live in the dorms are less expensive than renting out an apartment . Also , renting out an apartment requires that you have employment and the landlord\/agency would require you to have references , first months rent and security deposit . Why are we stating this you ? We just want you understand the reality here living and going to school in NYC . Best wishes on your goals and if you are unable to make it to both colleges , keep focused on your career and much success .</answer><suggestions>don/PERSON</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140603020037AAlyzyA">
	<title>Who has had enough of civilization and ca n't stop thinking about running off to the Australian bushland or even Alaska . ?</title><suggestions>alaska/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>People ripping off people , people taking advantage of people , have to work 60 + hrs to keep a mortgage . Who else here has had enough and ca n't stop thinking about leaving to live the bush . Well I ca n't . I have it all planed out and been planing it for 6 months . Hope that in 3 months time i can do it ! Who else want to join and start a small civilization where there is no murder , no work , no CRAP !</content><suggestions>bush/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401787018000">What 's the point of running off into the bush if you take a bunch of people with you ? You 'd still have all the same problems . People never change . I 've like to live further from the city , but not with a hoard of other runaways .</answer><suggestions>bush/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401789555000">Only a few people so it 's a small community with the same ideas . So I do n't go crazy lol its hard out on your own so a couple of people to share the work load . Say 4 others is a lot better then hundreds or thousands of people .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401791205000">how do you figure the no work aspect ... somebody has to work chopping wood , carrying water , cooking food , washing and cleaning is n't that work even if you live off the grid you still need that dreaded M thing money you need solar panels and\/or a generator which needs fuel , then the essential groceries etc there is no escaping it and life in the bush is very very hard and is definately no holiday you know there is this funny thing that happens when you run away ... yep you take yourself with you and people will always be people whether there are two or two million there will be love hate passion and all the stuff that humans do</answer><suggestions>bush/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401796609000">Before you make any rash decisions I think you should watch this film , Into the Wild : http:\/\/www.youtube.com\/watch?v=2LAuzT_x8Ek And maybe go do some WWOOFing to make friends and learn about living off the land http:\/\/www.wwoof.com.au\/ Living off the land can be a terribly hard life . Dealing with death , sick animals , snakes , the darkness of night , no police or medical facilities , poverty and solitude when you 're in a remote area with limited resources can be very very confronting . Human beings have become civilised and congregated in towns and cities for survival , and for very good reasons . People in communal bush living can also become dog eat dog and selfish and scary ... a commune gone wrong or bad neighbors in the bush can make office politics and long train commutes look like a walk in the park .</answer><suggestions>bush/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402242415000">I can tell you have n't thought this out Ryan/PERSON . Lets start with Alaska/LOCATION , with all the interest from buyers from down south , even a shack with no running water and an outhouse are bring $ 175,000 US plus . These places are miles from anywhere , and in the winter your snowed in , you better have enough firewood cut and plenty of stores . As for Australia/LOCATION my friend , a lot of land as I found out from going there comes under crown control , and other large parcels comes under aboriginal control , your not going to build anything out where I was . Even if you could , that $ US175K would be petty cash compared to prices I have seen charged over there just for land ...</answer><suggestions>ryan/PERSON alaska/LOCATION australia/LOCATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140615020333AAAIUUW">
	<title>Hi ' is there anybody out there with spare tickets to the disney/ORGANIZATION treasure trove on ice show in wellington/LOCATION ?</title><suggestions>wellington/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>would gladly pay ...</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403258181000">I saw an article the other day about this , let me check my history real fast and I will get back with the link</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140622230045AAAI6WE">
	<title>I m planning to go to new/LOCATION zealand/LOCATION for Vacation in Few Days . Can anybody tell me how expensive is the city ?</title><suggestions>new/LOCATION zealand/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>How is the fare of the hotels over there ?? Can i stay in some Bed and breakfast accommodation ?? will it be less expensive for me ?? Any help is appreciable thanks in advance</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403503974000">It is a fraction cheaper than Australia/LOCATION , but you will still need the equivalent of at least NZ$ 1000 a week , even using B & B. s. which appear to be much the same as hotels . Check this site for an idea of prices . http:\/\/www.booking.com\/searchresults.html?src=index&nflt=&ss_raw=&error_url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.booking.com%2Fbed-and-breakfast%2Findex.en-gb.html%3Faid%3D376367%3Blabel%3Dbooking-name-AyJKxHSdVhlt5LH2rN0PUgS39560110201%253Apl%253Ata%253Ap1%253Ap2494%252C000%253Aac%253Aap1t1%253Aneg%3Bsid%3D990077fdafaa2cd3b7dceb6fe642169c%3Bdcid%3D1%3B&aid=376367&dcid=1&label=booking-name-AyJKxHSdVhlt5LH2rN0PUgS39560110201%3Apl%3Ata%3Ap1%3Ap2494%2C000%3Aac%3Aap1t1%3Aneg&sid=990077fdafaa2cd3b7dceb6fe642169c&si=ai%2Cco%2Cci%2Cre%2Cdi&ss=Auckland&checkin_monthday=1&checkin_year_month=2014-7&checkout_monthday=7&checkout_year_month=2014-7&interval_of_time=any&flex_checkin_year_month=any&=2&no_rooms=1&group_adults=2&group_children=0&ppt=bed_and_breakfast&dest_type=city&dest_id=-1506909</answer><suggestions>australia/LOCATION nz/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403508535000">Which city do you mean ? Auckland/LOCATION , Wellington/LOCATION ? Where ? Why do n't you check them out on Trip Advisor ? Great food to be had in NZ/LOCATION , lovely people too .</answer><suggestions>auckland/LOCATION wellington/LOCATION nz/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403533583000">It 's a little cheaper than Sydney/PERSON Roger/PERSON , but you should be really asking in the New/LOCATION Zealand/LOCATION forum .</answer><suggestions>sydney/PERSON roger/PERSON new/LOCATION zealand/LOCATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140623010804AATRu9l">
	<title>Kpop fans only ?</title><suggestions>kpop/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<content>Do you think that it would be cool\/successful is kris from exo and jay park do a rap song together ? It think it 'll be awesome . Do you ? Why and why not .</content><suggestions>kris/PERSON exo/ORGANIZATION jay/PERSON park/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403618083000">YES ! Kris has a deep voice that will sound awesome with Jay Park ! I am a fan or both . Maybe they will work together . Actually , I want an OT4 of Chanyeol , Kris , Jay Park , and Eminem . I love rap ... so ... = D</answer><suggestions>kris/PERSON jay/PERSON park/PERSON kris/PERSON jay/PERSON park/PERSON</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140608183101AAll62c">
	<title>Is Hakulani a first name that Hawaiian people have ? If so , what gender usually has this name ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I know there 's the name Hokulani , as well `` Hoku '' and `` Lani '' being separate names . Is Hakulani a name people in Hawaii/LOCATION have at all ? If so , what gender would it fit most ?</content><suggestions>hokulani/PERSON hawaii/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402371861000">Hey , you ask that question coupla week ago , but neva choose answer , so my suggest go back an check out answer you given then , they not change in 3 week , ok ? Peace an aloha to you !</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402817935000">I 'm not sure why you messaged me privately and then ascribed Kono 's answer to me , but whatever . I have never heard the name Hakulani . I have heard Hoku and Lani but never Hakulani . If you 're not Hawaiian , what difference does it make ? It 's like naming a Spanish kid Pierre .</answer><suggestions>kono/PERSON hakulani/PERSON lani/PERSON pierre/PERSON</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140622025924AAbvcWQ">
	<title>Hotels in Europe/LOCATION ?</title><suggestions>europe/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>Hi , I 'd like to ask about European hotels . Do they have flip-flops and shampoo ? Apart from those required documents , what do I need to bring with me to have a comfortable trip in July ? Thanks !</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403432793000">Depends on the hotel . Some more upmarket ones with have shower gel , shampoo , body lotion , flip-flops . Budget hotels obviously wo n't .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403433705000">I have traveled quite a bit in Europe/LOCATION and only once was given flip-flops in a hotel , next time I visited the same hotel I was not given them . I would say bring your own , flip-flops or other kind of footwear that you will be happy to change into at the end of a day with a lot of walking . Shampoo is always available . Hotel stock it , free of charge , hostels have it for sale at the front desk . It does not hurt to have a tester size bottle of your favorite brand with you when you travel , most people prefer to use one brand only anyhow . In July I would have short\/skirt -LRB- depending on your gender -RRB- and short sleeved shirts\/nice tops , T-shirts and at least one pair of jeans or trousers that are as warm and a sweater of jersey , as weather is not really predictable in much of Europe/LOCATION . Also bring a jacket that is pretty much waterproof or an umbrella that folds away small , as rain is possible if not likely in July . That last mostly if you travel to London/LOCATION and Pari/LOCATIONs and farther north .</answer><suggestions>europe/LOCATION jersey/LOCATION europe/LOCATION london/LOCATION paris/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403454111000">I spent almost 14 years living in Italy/LOCATION and traveling throughout Europe/LOCATION on weekends and holidays andhave made many other trips to various places there . Every hotel I 've been in in Eurpope/LOCATION had things like soap and shampoo . I 've never been in one that had flip-flops . There have been some with slippers . Expect the daytime temperatures to be high especially in southern Europe/LOCATION . . The most important thing to take is comfortable shoes for sightseeing . You want something that 's broken in before you go . I always take a small folding umbrella that can be carried in a pocket or purse . You may or may not need it on your trip , but it 's useful to have in case of rain . If you have a laptop , cell phone and\/or camera , you 'll want a plug adapter . The outlets in the UK/LOCATION and on the continent are different so you may need more than one . Personally , I prefer individual adapters rather than the universal adapters .</answer><suggestions>italy/LOCATION europe/LOCATION eurpope/LOCATION europe/LOCATION uk/LOCATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140620192235AA5KHXm">
	<title>Morocco WINS : WHAT DO YOU THINK ?</title><suggestions>morocco/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>2014 World Cup Soccer Cheap Jerseys Wholesale , Big discount for sale include cheap nfl nike jerseys , nba\/mlb\/nhl cheap jerseys , cheap snapbacks free shipping from china/LOCATION . if you want to buy the soccer football jerseys , you can see the site : http:\/\/www.cheapsoccerjerseyser.com\/</content><suggestions>cheap/ORGANIZATION nfl/ORGANIZATION nike/ORGANIZATION china/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403325060000">inchaellah morocco wins in the next cycle</answer><suggestions>inchaellah/ORGANIZATION morocco/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140622163515AA7A77e">
	<title>Do you have a current and legal will ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I have a current will and have had since my mid twenties . I have no wish to die intestate and leave a myriad of problems for those I leave behind .</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403480243000">Yep .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403480449000">Oh yes ...</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403481113000">Yes , I made mine when I bought my house . You should update your will if circumstances change .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403481161000">Yes but I have learned that death brings out the worst in people so sometimes having a legal will means nothing because not everyone respects the last wishes of those who have passed .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403481246000">Yes . I believe all adults should have one .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403482770000">I do have one , but just like Molly , I have also learned that a legal will and also the nominated beneficiary of your superannuation -LRB- even a binding death nomination -RRB- , can be challenged after someone 's death .</answer><suggestions>molly/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403485788000">Yes , and have also organised Powers of Attorney for medical and financial issues if I am not in a position to make decisions .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403494546000">Yes , in three different countries .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140617134810AAX61tb">
	<title>What was Dunedin/LOCATION New/LOCATION Zealand/LOCATION like in the 60s 70s 80s 90s ?</title><suggestions>dunedin/LOCATION new/LOCATION zealand/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>In believed I lived in New/LOCATION Zealand/LOCATION in my previous life before I was born , it came to me in a dream , I searched on google/ORGANIZATION earth around nz/LOCATION and came on otago peninsula it just looked the same as it did in the dream , Mercedes/ORGANIZATION Benz/ORGANIZATION car was there on the edge of the peninsula as it was detailed because the car had a blackboard reg pre 1987 as the dream was set in 1982 as I said a prayer about that year , any Dunedinites can tell me there personnel experience , I believe I was born in the late 60s early 70s and died in the late 80s early 90s , I believed I went to otago boys high school in that life , and I 'm very fond of the goodnight kiwi bird and cat tv ending witch lasted from 1977 to 1994 , I get de ja vu 's of things and flashbacks that look like street and the train station and school and bungalows etc and another dream set around blueskin bay being driven in a Volkswagen/ORGANIZATION Passat at nighttime with a beautiful sunset theme like pink skyish , I 've being to Dunedin/LOCATION or New/LOCATION Zealand/LOCATION in my current life but I want to go someday to see if much has changed</content><suggestions>new/LOCATION zealand/LOCATION google/ORGANIZATION nz/LOCATION otago/LOCATION peninsula/LOCATION mercedes/ORGANIZATION benz/ORGANIZATION otago/ORGANIZATION boys/ORGANIZATION high/ORGANIZATION school/ORGANIZATION blueskin/LOCATION bay/LOCATION volkswagen/ORGANIZATION pink/PERSON skyish/PERSON dunedin/LOCATION new/LOCATION zealand/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>Never being to Dunedin/LOCATION or New/LOCATION Zealand/LOCATION yet \*</content><suggestions>dunedin/LOCATION new/LOCATION zealand/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403038218000">Never being to Dunedin/LOCATION or New/LOCATION Zealand/LOCATION yet \*</answer><suggestions>dunedin/LOCATION new/LOCATION zealand/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403045421000">Not many cars and many of them where older ones . apart from some people who had done very well . Fisheries where big I lived in Dunedin/LOCATION in the mid to late 60s . I was in my teens early 20s . Cadburys chocolate factory was across the road from the Railway station . There was some nice coffee shops The peninsula was a nice drive and one could spot penquins there Or perhaps attend a ball at Larnachs castle . Work was easy to get . The ships would come into Port Chalmers . Winter was cold and sometimes snow . often a frost . In 1990 there was a masacare at Aramoana/LOCATION known to locals as The spit where 13 people where shot dead by a crazed gunman . A nice City with many Scottish . A good University and friendly people .</answer><suggestions>dunedin/LOCATION aramoana/LOCATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140615004107AA0Il4W">
	<title>In Istanbul/LOCATION for 12 hours only on a Sunday ! are markets closed ?</title><suggestions>istanbul/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>I arrive early morning an leave in the afternoon an unfortunately its on a Sunday . I really wanted to see the bazaar market but i just found out its closed on Sundays , i want to know if there is other good markets in Istanbul/LOCATION on Sundays that anyone knows of . thankyou</content><suggestions>istanbul/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402919778000">Go to the Spice/ORGANIZATION Bazaar/ORGANIZATION aka Egyptian/ORGANIZATION Bazaar/ORGANIZATION -LRB- Mısır Çarşısı -RRB- , it 's open on Sundays .</answer><suggestions>spice/ORGANIZATION bazaar/ORGANIZATION aka/ORGANIZATION egyptian/ORGANIZATION bazaar/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402934515000">Orakle has a good idea . The Spice Bazaar is very much like the Grand Bazaar . But much smaller .</answer><suggestions>orakle/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403255917000">Can you be more specific please ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140623114258AAUKXoj">
	<title>is fiji/LOCATION water legit ?</title><suggestions>fiji/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>or is it the same as other water ... ... . .</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403551887000">i dunno i hear that is like really pure</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140618212015AAM2O4i">
	<title>Travel Portal or Flight booking API providers list in India/LOCATION ?</title><suggestions>india/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>I am looking for the list of Travel portal development companies or flight booking API providers list in India/LOCATION . Please recommend me also .</content><suggestions>india/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403254802000">Axis/ORGANIZATION Softech/ORGANIZATION Private Limited is the best option for you , Axis/ORGANIZATION Softech/ORGANIZATION best travel technology company in Delhi/LOCATION India/LOCATION offers travel portal development services and flight booking engine API .</answer><suggestions>softech/ORGANIZATION softech/ORGANIZATION delhi/LOCATION india/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403255982000">OSPL Trip is also one of the best travel portal development company as well as white label solution provider in India/LOCATION . For launching your own brand travel portal you can also go with white label solution .</answer><suggestions>india/LOCATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140603150630AAk23z7">
	<title>How to conceal a pack of cigarettes better ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>Ok so ik how to hide it in my house no prob , but for me im unsafe walking around with them on me , my parents caught me with them and im almost eighteen . Dont give me shit how i should n't , ik the effects so chill . Like would it work if i just stuffed it in my underwear or something . They know what it would look like in my picket and might ask me to empty them . Any advice on conseeling it on me in a better way ?</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401833541000">invest in a reasonably cheap\/durable cigarette case , keep it in a back pocket , like a wallet . cigarette cases are relatively thin and would be more difficult to notice , as opposed to a thicker cigarette pack</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401920160000">Try the old spy technique called the dead drop . Drop a pack or two into a Zip-loc baggie , seal it and stow it in a place outside your home , like the knothole of a tree , or a loose brick in the outside wall of a building . Also , consider switching to vaping when you turn 18 . That way , you can gradually ease yourself off of nicotine while continuing to indulge .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140617130308AAqDdcG">
	<title>Do hotels charge the number of people or the number of rooms ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I reserved 2 rooms through booking.com for a hotel in Europe/LOCATION . I paid through my credit card and everything , but when I got to the confirmation page , it said that 2 rooms = 4 people . The problem is , we 're actually 6 people -LRB- 3 adults and 3 children -RRB- . I made sure this was in the search criteria that I entered on the website . So will the hotel charge me extra for the 2 extra people -LRB- Who are children btw and do not require an extra bed -RRB- ? Or will they let them stay with no extra charge ? I called the customer support for booking.com and they said that `` 4 people '' meant that the room had capacity for 4 people . I told them that the children will not need an extra bed and they responded by saying that getting an extra bed is my choice entirely and if it is not required , I will not be charged extra . However , I am still very skeptical . Could someone please confirm ?</content><suggestions>europe/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403035576000">Do n't know about Europe/LOCATION , but here in USA/LOCATION the charge is normally by the room . However , due to fire safety rules , there is a maximum number of people per room -LRB- normally 4 people for two double beds max , suites can hold more -RRB- . I would think that 6 people in 2 rooms would be fine , and , at least here , no extra charge vs the 4 people . Call the hotel directly and ask them .</answer><suggestions>europe/LOCATION usa/LOCATION max/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403036746000">Depends on the hotel , sometimes all hotels in a country use the same system of room or number of people , but mostly it is up to the hotel . Contact the hotel and tell them you are coming with three adults and three kids , when they are ok with it , you will not have problems . Booking.com is not the hotel and can only give the general rules . Mostly kids under a certain age go free when staying in a room with their parents\/guardians , but it differs what age that is as well .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403037467000">You need to call the hotel and talk to a human to ask . Ensure they know it is 3 adults and 3 children . In the future , use hotel websites -LRB- ex . www.hilton.com -RRB- and not travel websites -LRB- ex . www.booking.com -RRB- to book hotels , unless the travel website offers a significantly better rate .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403052550000">In Europe/LOCATION fees are based on the number of people . Rooms can only sleep a set number of people , depending on local laws , fire regulations and insurance . If rooms are only for two persons you can not squash in more people . If six people are staying you have to book enough rooms to accommodate six people .</answer><suggestions>europe/LOCATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140614114159AAxmnir">
	<title>Al Ain - KSA road ?</title><suggestions>ksa/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<content>Had been to Al Ain today and usually love exploring the roads in UAE had noticed a sign board which stated Al Quoa - Saudi/LOCATION Arabia/LOCATION and had just taken that road to explore it it ended up in a single lane desert road and this runs along the border of Saudi-UAE was not sure how far that route goes and had turned back as dint want to end up in a desert or get lost in middle of nowhere . Had checked on google that the road goes along southern part of UAE-Saudi border and ends somewhere in Saudi route so any idea if there is a direct route from Al Ain to Saudi that By passes the main Abu-Dhabi-Tarif-Saudi Route or the only route is Abu-Dhabi-Tariff-Saudi . Just wanted an info tried on google but routes are not clear</content><suggestions>uae/LOCATION saudi/LOCATION arabia/LOCATION saudi-uae/LOCATION google/ORGANIZATION uae-saudi/LOCATION saudi/LOCATION saudi/LOCATION google/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402813601000">Not really to travel to Saudi/LOCATION by road you have to drive to western/LOCATION Abu/LOCATION Dhabi/LOCATION border , where the official crossings are located . You ca n't cross from the south side as there is very little population there , it is mainly empty desert . Those roads are there for use by border patrols and area locals such as farmers & bedouins etc. . However on the Oman side there are several crossings because there are some villages to the east & north , but not to the south .</answer><suggestions>saudi/LOCATION western/LOCATION abu/LOCATION dhabi/LOCATION oman/LOCATION east/ORGANIZATION &/ORGANIZATION north/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140609122525AAYu0rC">
	<title>any beaches near columbus/LOCATION ohio ?</title><suggestions>columbus/LOCATION ohio/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>I want this summer to rock and whats a summer without a trip to a hot sandy beach ! It could be a lake or ocean , but preferrably close . Not like super close but not like hours and hours away ... I did go to one beach but i never ever plan on going there again , it was a man made lake that was made where an old Cemetery use to be and there are reports of caskets still floating on the shore ... plus there was bird poop every step u took . . so if anyone knows any good lakes or ocean beaches that are NOT on a cemetery or coated in bird feeces i would LOVE to hear ! : -RRB- Please and thank you for your time , and have a great day : -RRB-</content><suggestions>sandy/PERSON beach/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402341954000">Look at a map</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402346370000">Cedar Point is 2 hours away https:\/\/www.cedarpoint.com\/rides\/Fun-on-the-Water\/The-Cedar-Point-Beach Ohio/LOCATION is six hours from the nearest ocean</answer><suggestions>ohio/LOCATION</suggestions>
</question>

