<question id="20140606091726AA70ovE">
	<title>I 'm trying to sell you a house-trust me , I have it and it 's GREAT . It 's the best house ever ! What do you mean you do n't believe me ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>Located in the Bahamas/LOCATION , this house has a four car garage and comes with a robotic housekeeper that also gets your groceries . It has its own solar panels and has a beautiful ocean view . Six bedrooms and three bathrooms-it comes fully furnished and even has a pool-table and piano . No , you ca n't see it yet . I need you to sign on the dotted line . Oh , I forgot to mention the yacht that comes with it all . The whole thing is a small sum of $ 1000 . Why wo n't you sign the dotted line ? It 's not like we 're talking about your eternal soul or anything-just a measly $ 1000 .</content><suggestions>bahamas/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402071523000">It 's been done before , and done better : https:\/\/www.youtube.com\/watch?v=fDp7pkEcJVQ</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402071533000">you : trust me who the hell are you that i should trust you one bit . .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402071628000">Can you throw in something supernatural ? That would seal the deal for me . Anything that violates some law of physics would do .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402071750000">READ THE RULES AND I HAVE A HOUSE ... WRONG FORUM SPAMMING ... ... ... . .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402072003000">I would have to thoroughly examine the house first , or have experts tell me their opinion before buying it .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140610211341AAYKQNO">
	<title>Was melchizedek/PERSON in the OT Jesus/PERSON ?</title><suggestions>jesus/PERSON</suggestions>
	<content>Do you think Jesus appeared to people in the OT before He was born and crucified . Athiests your free to answer too , already can smell it coming , but I dont care .</content><suggestions>jesus/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402460125000">could be</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402460284000">It is not necessary to believe Melchizedek/PERSON was an epiphany of Christ . I believe the Bible is vague on that point on purpose . It is clear that Melchizedek/PERSON typifies Christ . The writer of Hebrews uses the example of Melchizedek/PERSON to show that both priesthoods pointed to Jesus/PERSON as the fulfillment . I hope this helps .</answer><suggestions>melchizedek/PERSON melchizedek/LOCATION jesus/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402460309000">Who was Melchizede/PERSONk ? http:\/\/www.gotquestions.org\/Melchizedek.html</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402461724000">I do n't believe he was literally Jesus/PERSON Christ/PERSON , but merely a literary picture of Jesus in His eternal priesthood , as it says in Psalm 110 `` You -LRB- Messiah -RRB- are a priest forever , according to the order of Melchizedek/PERSON '' . The conclusions drawn by the author of the Letter to the Hebrews shows he infers this from the original reference in Genesis , when for instance he states he was `` without mother , without father '' , inferring this simply from the lack of a genealogical trace of his origins .</answer><suggestions>jesus/PERSON christ/PERSON jesus/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402503042000">No Like `` Pharaoh '' and `` Abimelech '' , `` Melkhizedek/PERSON '' was not a name . Melkhizedek/PERSON \/ Adonitzedek was the title of the Jebusite kings of Jerusalem/LOCATION . While Abraham/PERSON had a very positive relationship with the Jebusite king of his time , Joshua/PERSON wound up executing the last king of that line for attacking Israel/LOCATION when they re-entered the land .</answer><suggestions>jerusalem/LOCATION abraham/PERSON joshua/PERSON israel/LOCATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140618142850AAJkDfw">
	<title>If someone was to perform 0ral sexx , kneeling on their prayer mat , facing toward Mecca ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>@ Tyga We should try it and see what happens LOL</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>Would Allah view this as a form of worship ?</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403126975000">Lol @ Ben/PERSON ... `` We should try it and see what happens '' .</answer><suggestions>ben/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403127047000">Allah is faq so its a form of worship he pleases</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403127089000">I am pretty sure oral sex is haram in Islam .</answer><suggestions>haram/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403127321000">Only for jews and christians to thier god</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403134209000">As you can see , all the Muslims in this section took so much offence to this , we 're all crying . Dude , this was 100 % pointless lol . It was n't really funny and it got deleted earlier . You 're trying too hard . Just chill out and enjoy life . Stop trying -LRB- and evidently failing -RRB- to anger the Muslims here , you suck at it .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403140050000">Salam No Allah would not recognize as a prayer or worship when someone made oral sex kneeling down on the prayer mat facing toward the kaaba in Mecca It means making play to Allah which is forbidden naudzu billah min zaliq</answer><suggestions>salam/PERSON kaaba/LOCATION naudzu/PERSON billah/PERSON</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140614133438AAjTFR7">
	<title>Why Does God Always Nitpick At My Sins ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I like nicotine and masturbation . Nothing is comparable to that dopamine and nicotine rush I get when I pop a snus in my mouth and then touch myself . Am I really that bad ? I see people all around me fornicating , stealing , picking on the homeless , and doing all sorts of bad things , and yet God does n't seem to do anything about them . But whenever I indulge in my minor vices , my conscience eats away at me , and the Church tells me I should n't do those things . What gives ? I 'm not trying to boast , but I think I 've done a lot more than most people have for my age . I converted at such a young age , even against the will of my family , following the commandment to leave father and mother behind and to love God more than them , I always give money to homeless people , and I 'm still a virgin . What 's wrong with an over religious virginal 18 year old male touching himself and snusing every once in a while ? Why does God have to be such a spoil sport ? What 's the point of all these dumb rules ?</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402778258000">it appears as tho , once you discovered your groin , its all the enjoyment you get out of life ... . poor thing ... ... ... ...</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402778297000">because all sin leads ultimately to death he wants you to live with him forever - never dying keep up that tobacco habit and you will die much sooner than expected or desired</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402778422000">God is n't doing that , since a god does n't exist . The church is doing that . Blame the church</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140619050221AAJaFcY">
	<title>Majority of people are forgetting whats in the bible ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>Justify this : Kill People Who Do n't Listen to Priests '' Anyone arrogant enough to reject the verdict of the judge or of the priest who represents the LORD your God must be put to death . Such evil must be purged from Israel/LOCATION . '' -LRB- Deuteronomy 17:12 NLT -RRB- Kill Homosexuals `` If a man lies with a male as with a women , both of them shall be put to death for their abominable deed ; they have forfeited their lives . '' -LRB- Leviticus/LOCATION 20:13 NAB -RRB- Death for Adultery '' If a man commits adultery with another man 's wife , both the man and the woman must be put to death . '' -LRB- Leviticus/LOCATION 20:10 NLT -RRB- Death for Fornication '' A priest 's daughter who loses her honor by committing fornication and thereby dishonors her father also , shall be burned to death . '' -LRB- Leviticus/LOCATION 21:9 NAB -RRB- Death to Followers of Other Religions '' Whoever sacrifices to any god , except the Lord alone , shall be doomed . '' -LRB- Exodus 22:19 NAB -RRB- Kill Nonbelievers `` They entered into a covenant to seek the Lord , the God of their fathers , with all their heart and soul ; and everyone who would not seek the Lord , the God of Israel , was to be put to death , whether small or great , whether man or woman . '' -LRB- 2 Chronicles 15:12 -13 -RRB- Lets be fair i will say all religions are evil .</content><suggestions>israel/LOCATION leviticus/LOCATION leviticus/LOCATION leviticus/LOCATION israel/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403179512000">You ca n't take death out of a death cult . They live to die . It seems their entire purpose in life is to die , and take as many with them as possible . In all fairness , you have been very fair there .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403179696000">Most are Old laws , they do n't apply since Jesus fulfilled the old laws .</answer><suggestions>jesus/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403179802000">You wo n't understand without faith .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403180133000">If i took texts from the quran , let 's be realistic you would all bash it even though its the same thing in the bible .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403180165000">`` Oh , uh ... those things in the bible do n't count because ... SHUT UP ! ''</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403180218000">It is all explained in the Bible . Why do n't you read it for yourself ? How any can get it wrong , as you do , can only be from an evil motive . Explaining to those with an evil motive does n't change the evil motive nor stop them from false allegations , nor from bigoted opinions .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403183292000">Why is this evil ? It is laws that if they are obeyed , people are not put to death . The understanding is that if you do these things , you are responsible for your own death because you chose to commit great sin . In Britain/LOCATION and then in America/LOCATION the death penalty was imposed for all sorts of crimes from serious to minor . By the 1700s , 222 crimes were punishable by death in Britain/LOCATION , including stealing , cutting down a tree , and robbing a rabbit warren In 1612 , Virginia/LOCATION Governor Sir/PERSON Thomas/PERSON Dale/PERSON enacted the Divine , Moral and Martial Laws , which provided the death penalty for even minor offenses such as stealing grapes , killing chickens , and trading with Indians . Laws regarding the death penalty varied from colony to colony . The Massachusetts/ORGANIZATION Bay/ORGANIZATION Colony/ORGANIZATION held its first execution in 1630 , even though the Capital Laws of New England did not go into effect until years later . The New/ORGANIZATION York/ORGANIZATION Colony/ORGANIZATION instituted/ORGANIZATION the/ORGANIZATION Duke/ORGANIZATION 's Laws of 1665 . Under these laws , offenses such as striking one 's mother or father , or denying the `` true God , '' were punishable by death . -LRB- Randa/PERSON , 1997 -RRB- .</answer><suggestions>britain/LOCATION america/LOCATION britain/LOCATION virginia/LOCATION thomas/PERSON dale/PERSON massachusetts/LOCATION new/LOCATION england/LOCATION new/LOCATION york/LOCATION duke/ORGANIZATION randa/PERSON</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140603164416AACMXNh">
	<title>so nobody wants to be my partner in a program i 'm in , what do I do ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>and at lunch the people in the class i 'm at do n't say hi to me , they just do n't ask me to have lunch with them , i 'm the only person in the class who has a learning disability and everyone is normal functioned , why does this happen ? I mean it made me cry and it 's just not fair .</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401839108000">talk to your teacher</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401839567000">I to had a learning disability , it just means u fall under the 10 % that learn differently than the rest of the people , they cast u out , but screw them , in a bunch of ways u will excel compared to their normal limited ways , as for ur project at least now u dont have to carry the weight of another peraon botching it up , u can do it ur way , so make it different , be urself outside the box , as for friends find people who are geminis , pisces , and aquarius they all tend to help and like people who r different . Be urself and dont show them them that it bothers u , after while friends will come at least like the rest of them u dont have ro weed out who ur real friends will be . Hope this help and good luck : -RRB-</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140626170527AAjZBOY">
	<title>I want to have sex but Im only 17 . Whats even worse is Im a Christian . Help ? Encouragement ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>Sorry If that was unclear</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>-LRB- Im a female -RRB-</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I go to a Christian School , They teach us that `` Do n't have sex till your married '' Yet they all did it before marriage . They also say thats its the # 1 `` unforgivable sin '' . NOT TRUE . The unforgivable is not accepting Christ into my heart as my lord and savior . Also my `` sin '' is not my eternal death , Gods `` grace '' is new `` everyday '' right My friends are Christians too . If I have sex they will disown me . I love my friends but I also love my boyfriend .</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403827961000">Honestly I think if you love your boyfriend and it 's a mutual love and not him trying to convince you yeah just use a condom . The Christian idea behind saving yourself for marriage is just their way of making sure you really love someone as opposed to just sex . That 's why it 's called making love not ` fucking ' . -LRB- Excuse my language -RRB-</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403828322000">If you feel that your ready then go for it , plenty of people has had premarital sex and if your friend 's ca n't accept that then find new friends who will .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403828367000">I do n't believe that sex before marriage is a sin , but I do believe having sex without love is a sin . I believe that sex is very sacred and is a way to express a deep love . The main reason that it was thought to be a bad idea to have sex before marriage is so that people do n't have children too young or before marriage or to get an STD . So with that in mind , do what you think is right for you and your heart . I know that if you have your mind set to go through with it , no one can stop you if you are alone with the person you are dating , but before you have sex , make sure you take necessary precautions . You can even pray to God and for Him to help you make the right decision for you because in my opinion , God gave us freewill and He wants us to you it , but it can also be comforting to talk things through with God because He listens to all of our problems and concerns . I would also like to add that you could always wait until you graduate so that if a pregnancy does occur , you can at least have graduated high school especially if you plan on going to college because it is easier to finish college with a child than high school , at least that is the way it seems for people I know . I hope this answer helps :-RRB- .</answer><suggestions>god/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403828856000">Go have sex , dont stop yourself because people say your religion says to . People can not make you do what you do not . If you wish to be celibate , you must do it for God , you must be encouraged by his promises of celibacy , if not , you have no faith and your act of celibacy is just a stumbling block for you .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140608143713AAg7e9D">
	<title>why does hollywood keep making Slave Movies ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I always hear cooperate america/LOCATION -LRB- whire people -RRB- so quick to say `` black people need to move on & forget about slavery its the past its over with slaves do n't exist today its the past ca n't change it we never owned a slave we are n't responsible for slavery we should n't be held accountable blah blah blah all that bullcrap but every year more & more slave films are made . `` THE BUTLER '' `` 12 YEARS A SLAVE '' `` DJANGO '' `` ROSEWOOD '' `` MISSISSIPPI BURNING '' etc. in order to not think about the past we do n't need things to remind us of it . ROOTS came on last week . the media keep putting these films out but people are bothered when black people talk about then why do n't directors\/producers of these films STOP MAKING films like this . Ca n't have it both ways . Ca n't expect us to forget but you steady put out movies to remind us about it then get mad when you feel like we are blaming you . because what the movie shows is white people mistreating black people that 's all we see when we pay to see movies like this then anger starts to boil & conversation are had then white people do n't understand why they are being blamed for what the whites on t.v. are doing .</content><suggestions>america/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402263647000">They make them because people enjoy watching them , would you want to go to watch a movie about the first slaves being white Scottish slaves of the white rich Englishman who were in fact the first slaves in the world ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402264192000">You ca n't have it both ways . The people that are saying leave slavery in the past are not the same people making movies etc about slavery . You know that . Do n't take such a simplistic view .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402266093000">Because : 1 . People keep going to see them 2 . Just because you ignore something , it wo n't `` go away '' . You might as well ask `` why do filmmakers keep making films about the Holocaust ? '' ps The Butler , Rosewood , and Mississippi Burning were not about slavery .</answer><suggestions>mississippi/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402431850000">If you can understand what it means to leave racism in the past and move on , you 've solved 50 % of America/LOCATION 's problems .</answer><suggestions>america/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402606985000">making money off black peoples misery ... ... maybe they enjoy watching those movies , maybe they make them feel as though they have the upper hand and are superior ... And we black feel less that human all over again ...</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140609044507AAN0sUq">
	<title>To the people who think that `` Life Begins at Conception '' , should a woman who menstruates be prosecuted for murder ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>Why not ?</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402314421000">Err ... you do n't know what `` CONCEPTION '' means do you Here , educate yourself . -LRB- Please -RRB- http:\/\/www.nhs.uk\/Livewell\/Fertility\/Pages\/Fertilitythefacts.aspx</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402314632000">That 's only one -LRB- or possibly two -RRB- lives sacrificed on the altar of godlessness . On that basis every man who takes a swift one off the wrist should be prosecuted for genocide !</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402314672000">life does begin at conception biologically and scientifically . . if you consciously perform an act to end that life , which is indeed human for no justifiable reason other than you just decided you dont want it around ... you are a murderer plain and simple . . throw some candy coating on it if you want ... doesnt change the fact . .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402314679000">Menstruation is NOT conception . It is the clearing and cleaning of the '' `` factory '' '' for the next possible fertilisation . Peace . The answer would be '' `` Bull ...</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402314800000">Unrelated . Try again .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402314949000">You might find this science fiction story interesting . You might even find a name or two that jingles a bell if you think hard enough . It 's short . http:\/\/sooziestories.weebly.com\/</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402314976000">Oh dear , I think we 're going to have to give you a sex education lesson Menstruation does not involve conception my young fellow</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402315024000">no life includes a egg from the woman and a sperm from the male eggs discharged by menstruation are not fertilized by the sperm study sex education first then come back and ask proper questions</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402315045000">Ever heard of a fertilised egg ? The production of an egg has nil to do with an abortion unless it 's fertilised .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402315092000">A woman can not menstruate if she is conceiving . Got to learn hard stuff from Yahoo/ORGANIZATION .</answer><suggestions>yahoo/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402315288000">Life begins at conception , but the prosecutor should only prosecute cases in which it is possible to obtain evidence of criminal intent . Menstruation and miscarriage are biological functions to which intent can not attach . If one can show that the woman intentionally took a drug to cause miscarriage , then prosecution may proceed . In any case , God sees all , and what the prosecutor can not show does not escape the notice of the one judge who determines if a person is worthy of being redeemed into heaven or sent to the incinerator for permanent disposal .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402315732000">Your statement about menstruation is way off , since menstruation only occurs when the ova is n't fertilized . However , there are many problems with the `` Life begins at conception '' argument : 50 % of fertilized ovum self abort , either fail to attach the uterine wall or , for whatever reason , fail to develop . With such a law we would have to treat every one of those cases as a potential ` murder ' and have it investigated by the police . Or , some forms of birth control do not stop fertilization of the ova , only the attachment of the ova to the uterine wall ; such laws would make IUDs and some forms of `` the pill '' illegal . Or , many women are not aware they are pregnant for several weeks following conception ; if a woman drank alcohol or engaged in other potentially dangerous activities to the fetus before they are aware of the pregnancy , would they be considered criminals ? Finally , most anti-abortion rights advocates claim a justification from their Christian beliefs , yet the Bible does not condemn abortions . They have twisted vague passages such as `` I knew you in the womb '' and claimed them as supporting their view .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402316533000">I 'm pro-choice , but this argument does n't really make sense . An egg that is passed by menstruation has not yet been fertilized .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402316824000">Someone wants to reassure herself . Abortion is murder in any trimester .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402318371000">Cause nothing fertilized the egg .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402329412000">I would n't put it past some . I mean not when the Virginia/LOCATION GOP nominee for Attorney General introduced a Bill forcing women to report their miscarriages to police . -LRB- Google/ORGANIZATION `` Senator Mark Obenshain '' -RRB- .</answer><suggestions>virginia/LOCATION google/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402330878000">Menstruation is not conception . It is the body getting ready for the possibility of having a fetus in the womb , there is no actual fetus or fertilized egg . The body stores up extra blood each month and when there is no fertilized egg , then the body gets rid of the blood via menstruation .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402338723000">1 . No . 2 . Never mind the absence of mens rea , the mense occurs because conception did n't occur or the zygote did n't implant .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140622182545AA9CcLX">
	<title>Should I accept a promise ring from my boyfriend ? What finger do I wear it on ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>My boyfriend and I have been together 9 months and he told me that he bought me a promise ring . I just do n't know when it is coming . But I 'm not sure if I should accept it ? What exactly does it symbolize ? Is it normal to feel so anxious yet scared ?</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403486815000">I guess you should accept it if you want to accept a promise .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403487039000">Yes !!! It 's so adorable when guys do that -LRB- : awwww < 3</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403487939000">Of course accept it !! it 's a sweet gesture and you will hurt him if you reject it ... and he 's waiting because he wants to make sure the mood is right !</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140625050257AAiG2K1">
	<title>Do black people generally have smaller brain sizes ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I 've heard the difference in brain size between a black and a chimp is n't much .</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403697884000">That is not fair to say , all humans have the same average brain size , females have a smaller brain though .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403698029000">YES Proof : http:\/\/www.sciencedirect.com\/science\/art ... African-descended people -LRB- Blacks -RRB- average cranial capacities of 1267 cm3 , European-descended people -LRB- Whites -RRB- 1347 cm3 , and East Asian-descended people -LRB- East Asians -RRB- 1364 cm3 . These brain size differences , containing millions of brain cells and hundreds of millions of synapses , were hypothesized to underlie the race differences on IQ tests , in which ... Blacks average an IQ of 85 , Whites 100 , and East Asians 106 .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403698064000">You 've heard wrong .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403698473000">Yes due to their erectus DNA .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403702309000">If brain size were the only factor in intelligence then the sperm whale would be 10 times smarter than all of us . Then again , looking at some of these answers ...</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403703210000">I know a lot of black people who are smarter and better off than the average white person . Also , they are not degenerate humans who spend all day on the computer trolling with multiple accounts spreading hate</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403703381000">this question is stupid .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403706326000">I do n't think it 's polite to compare anyone to a chimp ... there are smart people out there of any race . Although IQs do tend to be higher in East Asian countries ... people are still largely products of their environment . So a high IQ wo n't do you much good if you grew up in a socio-economic system that did n't offer opportunities for you to excel , for such a system to take advantage of your potential . A white or black person can still often have a higher IQ than the average IQ of East Asian countries . But if they grew up in poverty there simply wo n't be many opportunities to show the world how brilliant they are . If you hate an entire race of people , likely you just never took the time to get out there to meet many of those people .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403706846000">I like how your proof is a link that does n't work .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403708007000">like many previously mentioned , i dont think brain size has to do with intelligence however in the case of blacks , i think they are far less intelligent than whites , asians , and any other race in between . it 's not BECAUSE of their skin color , but people of black people 's skin color just HAPPEN to be extremely unintelligent . the environment shaped them that way . it 's more complicated than it sounds . but as far as your question goes , its probably a myth -LRB- not that it matters in the long run though -RRB-</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403714006000">Black women are ranked the most educated group by race and gender . This is so because out of all the races we are enrolled in colleges more than any other race . You do not hear about this fact because society and the News does not want to focus on the positive things about Black women and our accomplishments so they keep sending bad messages about us on the News , online , the media . Did n't expect a Black person to put you in your place huh ? This goes for jonny/PERSON , southasiangurung , and the rest of the people here with similar comments . Do your research before you ask unintelligent questions , because you are the one looking like you have a small brain . This also goes for the people making bad comments about Black people 's intelligence . You all should not be talking about Black people 's intelligence when you all are not even smart yourselves to know that Black women are enrolled in colleges more than any other race and gender . Wan na say more ?</answer><suggestions>jonny/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403714843000">Ignore this guy .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140622180632AAT4Nrc">
	<title>I 'm 12 and is it okay that I masturbate ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>If so is there toys that I make homemade</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403485961000">Hairbrush handle , anything that vibrates -LRB- like the end of an electric toothbrush -RRB- , you can get creative . -LRB- I 'm assuming you 're a girl as guys do n't generally ask for toys for masturbation -RRB- .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403486156000">Um ... why ca n't you masturbate ? Who 's gunna stop you ? If your looking for ` homemade things ' then just stop right there because it will most likely end in a hospital trip and a lot of embarrassment . Just use your finger and plz wash it after . If you want o be alone when you do it just play music in the shower and use cream rinse as lube but if you do n't normally take a long shower your parents might know what 's up -LRB- hehe sorry -RRB- so try to be inconspicuous .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403487051000">Sure it is okay .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140622130247AAXGWb7">
	<title>Is the idea that nothing happens after death better than heaven and hell ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>Well I used to want to believe there was a heaven because I did n't want to cease to exist -LRB- And still do n't -RRB- But when I thought about both of these places probably I 've found that they 're even worse . Hell is constant torture and being in pain for eternity and then heaven is doing whatever you want for eternity . But thats the thing it never ends ever wo n't everyone eventually get bored because they 've done the same thing over and over repeated like millions and billions of times ? At least with nothing after death I can never get bored or suffer . Its why I also tend to think more about my life and try and forget about death until I 'm dead .</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403467412000">Or ... What if there 's only heaven and bad people simply cease to exist ? That would be the best thing And BTW , in heaven , there would be an infinite amount of activities so nobody gets bored</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403467452000">nothing . islam .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403467506000">That must be the most hopeless way to live in this life .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403467528000">well consider ghosts . they hang around here for who knows how long ... I dunno man . I 'd rather go to heaven . I would rather live and do fun stuff than die and that be it . but whatever it is , i am pretty sure that if there is a hell no one wants to go there . .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403467664000">The idea of closure is the best one . After 10000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000000 years , I 'd definitely be so bored . Earth and every other thing in the galaxy and beyond will be long gone , possibly the universe as well .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403467739000">the idea that there 's no afterlife is supported entirely as an idea there are 2 reasons to believe there is an afterlife 1 - we know it instinctively because God has built that into us 2 - the bible declares it</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403467813000">The universe moves in circles , big bang , big crunch , big bang . At some point in the cycle , the same universes happen , and then they happen again , in different variations , over and over again , forever . As part of these universes , we too are born over and over again , forever , doing different things each time , not remembering our previous lives , but we 've been doing it forever already .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403467815000">i dont give a monkey 's what happens after . to me my life , my current life , would be over .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403467823000">Let 's see Trillions upon Trillions of years endlessly praising a ego maniacal god . . Get kinda boring after the first trillion years Trillions upon Trillions of years in eternal torment sounds kinda like the above . Will get boring after the first trillion years Then there is Nothingness Nothingness wins</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403468327000">If nothing was eternal , there would n't be anything now .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403468758000">The thing is that you never bothered examining the Bible to find any of these things . It is just what you and generations before were told by the same deceitful clergies . As long as they kept the laity upset , the more money they pockted . . The Bible shows hell is only the grave , where any mental function stops . -LRB- Eccles . 3:18 -20 ; 9:5 , 10 ; Psals 146:4 -RRB- . Just the same as animals . The mind must function to feel pain it bliss . So there is absolutely no torture in ell . There is also a release from hell . Ever knew hat did you ? Rev. 20:13 -14 shows the dead , both good and not so good are released from hell which us then destroyed . The lake of fire there is explained in verse 14 . It is he second death . There is a release from the 1st death but not the 2nd . It is only necessary to be within God `` s memory to be worthy of a resurrection . The Bible shows God 's original purpose was for perfect humans to live on a perfect earth forever . Most of the resurrected will be back to earth .</answer><suggestions>eccles/PERSON ell/PERSON god/PERSON earth/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403469438000">I like it ... Some people seem to need a ` belief ' in an afterlife to give their lives meaning or ` hope ' ... more power to them ... I do n't ... IMHO</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403469805000">NO</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403469807000">`` Is the idea that nothing happens after death better than heaven and hell ? '' Reality is always better than fantasy .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403473079000">Based on answers so far , the knowledge on this subject does n't even get beyond 0.001 % . It 's not much better among most preachers . Let 's just say , most people know as much about this as an 18 month old baby knows about quantum physics ... You are all in for a gigantic gob-smacking surprise .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403542433000">Ecclesiastes 9:5 says that the dead are conscious of nothing at all . Those who are dead now are as if they were sleeping . They are awaiting resurrection and judgement .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403561901000">i dont give a monkey 's what happens after . to me my life , my current life , would be over .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140611031519AAoLS4M">
	<title>Can you give me the explanation of this slogan `` Speak in English fluently and be Competitive Globally '' ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>Help me please</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402482922000">The first thing to note is that it was probably written by somebody who is not a natural speaker of British English ! It wants to say that if you can speak English you will be in a good position to get work in many parts of the world .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402484876000">That 's economic reality . If you 're running a moped hire business in Corfu you 're not going to get much trade if you can only communicate in Greek ! If I contacted a Swiss bank with 20 million quid to invest and they said `` Sprechen Sie Deutsch ? '' , I 'd go next door . etc etc</answer><suggestions>corfu/LOCATION sie/PERSON deutsch/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402516806000">It 's just a stupid advertisment-slogan , exaggerating things . It suggests that you NEED English everywhere on earth , and that ALL jobs are open to you if you speak English . it also implies that being competitive is not relative . In reality , a lot of jobs will NOT be open to you if you do n't speak the LOCAL language , at least not as long as other applicants DO speak it .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140611000925AAc6xTo">
	<title>Merlin/PERSON POV and Arthur/PERSON POV -LRB- Legend -RRB- Novels for a young\/teen reader ?</title><suggestions>merlin/PERSON pov/PERSON</suggestions>
	<content>Hello : D I am searching for an Arthurian Legend -LRB- NOT the Merlin TV show ! -RRB- book\/novel taken from Merlin 's point of view and tells the whole story . This book NEEDS to be for a young or teen reader -LRB- not a picture book -RRB- . A big thick , adult style book is no use . Needs to be a concise but simplified telling of the legend . Also one from Arthur 's POV would be great as well -LRB- again a book for young\/teen reader -RRB- . Kindle books are FINE : D OR ANY - Young\/Teen reader novels of the Arthurian Legend would suffice . -LRB- But NO , sc-fi , what-if , TV shows , Camelot High , Alternate Universe , etc etc -RRB- MUST be the Legend of King/PERSON Arthur/PERSON and his Knights , Merlin/PERSON and related characters .</content><suggestions>merlin/PERSON arthur/PERSON arthur/PERSON merlin/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402526187000">I read this AMAZING MERLIN SAGA LAST SUMMER I HIGHLY RECOMMEND IT ! It 's exactly what you want . http:\/\/tabarron.com\/books\/novels\/merlin\/ They also have it on the kindle from Amazon ! : -RRB-</answer><suggestions>merlin/PERSON saga/PERSON amazon/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402611942000">Crystal Cave by Mary Stewart was a book I had read twice before I was fourteen . It 's told from Merlin 's POV and I do n't consider myself a freak . T. H. White 's the Sword in the Stone is from Arthur 's POV and it was made into a Disney movie so of course it 's for kids .</answer><suggestions>mary/PERSON stewart/PERSON merlin/PERSON t./PERSON h./PERSON white/PERSON arthur/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402659624000">Do you seek political power , magic power , protections , super power , spiritual power or more contact him on facebook with -LRB- Oduduwa/PERSON Ajakaye/PERSON -RRB-</answer><suggestions>oduduwa/PERSON ajakaye/PERSON</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140609211214AAvr7b5">
	<title>If my mom bought me a dress at Maurices and she got the wrong size can I still exchange it without a receipt ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>It has been a few months since she bought the dress . But I do not live near a Maurices so I havent been able to exchange it . : -LRB-</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402374918000">check their website for exchange policy</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402375244000">I think you canif it still has the tags and is n't messed up at all</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402376055000">Most places will do it if it is an even exchange , with tags . The problem comes in where you only get the lowest price it last sold for . So you may only get $ 9 for a $ 45 dress .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402377891000">Clothing is usually seasonal . It would be unusual for the same dress to still be available after several months . However , if the dress still has its price tags attached , you may be able to get a `` due bill '' , which is a store credit only . You can use it toward something else in the store . If your mom used a credit card to purchase the dress , the store might be more willing to accept it back if her purchase appears on her monthly statement . Maybe that 's still around -- it 's worth a try .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402386171000">You can try but too much time has passed . You should have rang them and explained the situation the minute you knew it was n't the right size . They probably would have asked to send it back . I think you 've left it too long . You never know until you try , good luck .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140621074621AAaJnZh">
	<title>Ramadan/LOCATION : Is there a single country on planet earth that can ?</title><suggestions>ramadan/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>See Lee Lee , Indeed/LOCATION Vatican/LOCATION is religious state based on Christianity . But how much is its area compared to the whole country of Italy/LOCATION ?</content><suggestions>lee/PERSON lee/PERSON vatican/LOCATION italy/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>Angela/LOCATION , There were supposed to be 10 Commandments for believers of Judaism . And Jesus/PERSON Christ/PERSON came to retrieve the lost sheep of children of Israel/LOCATION . Who authorized you to reduce 10 commandments to only 2 ?</content><suggestions>angela/PERSON jesus/PERSON christ/PERSON israel/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>be called a true Christian nation ? Indeed Saudi/LOCATION Arabia/LOCATION is not a perfect Islamic nation , yet she has established shariah law within her boundaries . Are Christians not required to obey any code of conduct ?</content><suggestions>saudi/LOCATION arabia/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>See Lee Lee , Indeed/LOCATION Vatican/LOCATION is religious state based on Christianity . But how much is its area compared to the whole country of Italy/LOCATION ?</content><suggestions>lee/PERSON lee/PERSON vatican/LOCATION italy/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403362118000">No . Mainly because everybody has their own opinions .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403362159000">Nope . They 're all secular countries .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403362177000">Israel/LOCATION ... howerevr old teatament allows inviting foreigners . .</answer><suggestions>israel/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403362233000">christians believe in freedom of religion.Unlike muslims who feel threatened if others practiced other beliefs .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403362525000">Vatican/LOCATION is a Christian theocracy . Its legal system is rooted in the Canon Law . The Supreme Pontiff has legislative , executive and judicial powers . It 's up to you to decide if it is a ` true ' Christian nation .</answer><suggestions>vatican/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403362609000">No only uncivilized mussie nations oppress freedom of speech and religion . Proof : i can say bad things about jesus/PERSON in my country they will get offended but nobody will arrest me or try to kill me . I say bad thing about in mussie countries they arrest you and try to kill you</answer><suggestions>jesus/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403362845000">Its better that way .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403363882000">The difference is that Christians are quite happy for others to preach their own religions , they are not worried or have a complex . The local Christian church here in my town in Surrey/LOCATION , UK/LOCATION , lets the small local Muslim population use its meeting rooms for Friday prayers . I can not imagine a Mosque in Saudi/LOCATION or Iran/LOCATION , showing the local Christians the same act of kindness</answer><suggestions>christian/ORGANIZATION church/ORGANIZATION surrey/LOCATION uk/LOCATION iran/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403364290000">Athos Greece/LOCATION is a self-governing state run by the Orthodox Catholic church . Like Vatican/LOCATION City/LOCATION , it is an autonomous theocracy . Andorra/LOCATION , England/LOCATION , and Norway/LOCATION all have religious authorities as nominal heads of state -LRB- or heads of state as nominal religious authorities -RRB- , but are not truly theocratic in practice .</answer><suggestions>greece/LOCATION vatican/LOCATION city/LOCATION andorra/LOCATION england/LOCATION norway/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403365354000">Quote `` Are Christians not required to obey any code of conduct ? Quote `` Love they neighbor as thy self '' If you do not understand that it incorporates the whole of the 10 Commandments `` Do unto others as you would have them do unto you ''</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403365597000">All countries , whether religious or not , have laws - These are the codes of conduct . Such laws may be moral -LRB- where people are helped and protected -RRB- or immoral -LRB- where there is legal murder and injustice -RRB- . Freedom is an important requirement for any creation of Allah \/ God \/ Abba , so any law which unjustifiably restricts freedom is contrary our Creator 's wishes . In the past , Christian States have been very cruel , as are some Muslim , Communist and Atheist States today , often using philosophical justification for atrocities . Laws should exist to help and protect good people against the bad . No laws should be based purely on religious beliefs which are often wrong or misinterpreted .</answer><suggestions>abba/ORGANIZATION christian/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403369497000">In all my years -LRB- 75 -RRB- going and attending a catholic church ... I have never heard or seen any priest or bishop putting down other religions ... in fact if it did exist ' they would be expelled by the pope . unlike some of your Imams and clerics who preach hate that instils anger amongst the young minds .</answer><suggestions>catholic/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403373185000">Alteast Europe/LOCATION band America/LOCATION is hundred times better than being in Saudi/LOCATION Arabia/LOCATION or Pakistan/LOCATION . Which is completely hell filled with terrorist groups killings everyday and beating women .</answer><suggestions>alteast/PERSON europe/PERSON band/PERSON america/PERSON saudi/LOCATION arabia/LOCATION pakistan/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403378891000">All of them . For where believing Christians live , believe , worship , pray and follow , that is part of His Kingdom , the Kingdom of God . We are all part of His elect , part of the Body of Christ , we are the saints , the elect , we are those who call Him `` Abba '' and who He calls His adopted children , His dear ones with full rights to His inheritance . And they even come from countries like yours ... `` After this I looked , and there before me was a great multitude that no one could count , from every nation , tribe , people and language , standing before the throne and before the Lamb . They were wearing white robes and were holding palm branches in their hands . And they cried out in a loud voice : ` Salvation belongs to our God , Who sits on the throne , and to the Lamb . ' `` These in white robes -- who are they , and where did they come from ? '' I answered , `` Sir , you know . '' And he said ... `` They have washed their robes and made them white in the Blood of the Lamb . ''</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403388096000">Christians only have one rule to follow . It is called the golden rule . Treat others as you want to be treated . Muslims do n't have this at all . Muslims and others are not equal under Islamic law .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403410846000">Nope . They 're all secular countries .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403490687000">No . Mainly because everybody has their own opinions .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403521927000">Israel ... howerevr old teatament allows inviting foreigners . .</answer><suggestions>israel/LOCATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140612124803AAr1ZMX">
	<title>Help ! Translation from Hindi into English ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>Please translate this expression from Hindi into English ... `` Taash ke patte mein Ikka , aur zindagi mein Sikka , Jab Chalta hai , To Duniya Salaam karti hai '' . thanx</content><suggestions>patte/PERSON mein/PERSON ikka/PERSON aur/PERSON zindagi/PERSON mein/PERSON sikka/PERSON jab/PERSON chalta/PERSON hai/PERSON duniya/PERSON salaam/PERSON karti/PERSON hai/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402602578000">Ace cards , and coin in life , when the moves , salute the world 's</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402608086000">in a pack of cards hes an ace and in life he is a gold coin , when he walks people salute him .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402628797000">`` The world bows down to power and money '' ... that 's what it says ! Literal translation would be -- When an Ace in the pack of cards , and a coin in life shows up , then the world salutes it .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140615205718AApdJGk">
	<title>could you be so kind and teach me korean ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>i have gainned interest in korean recently . I love learning new languages . my native language is spanish , sescond is english , i have been learning french but now i am really interested in korean . i just dont know where to get started and where . could anyone be so kind to teach me some korean ? i will be a dedicated student : p thanks .</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402891089000">i meant how and where to get started . . sorry about that : s</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402891616000">To start , I love learning new languages as well ! It 's a fun thing to do and opens many job opportunities especially if you know a lot . Well bascially How : I remember trying to learn Russian . So when I heard a their was a Russian speaking student at our school I was dying to meet him . But it turned out he was n't the way teacher so that failed . I ended up learning it online and that 's probably going to be the best bet for you too . Getting started : well , you just have to find an online course . None of them will be free I can almost guarantee but its worth a shot . Sign up and get started ! Best of luck !</answer><suggestions>russian/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402960388000">im korean but i didnt know it very well . . and i got frustrated when someone thought me korean bc it was too hard . . but you can try an online course . . but i learned alot from korean dramas :-RRB- if youre interested you can search `` top korean dramas '' and watch some one youtube or drama fever app . :-RRB- with subtitles of course</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402977120000">This -LRB- http:\/\/www.infocobuild.com\/language\/korean\/korean.html -RRB- brings a collection of online resources for learning Korean , including study stuff on hangul and grammar lessons . I hope they can help you learn basic Korean .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140622085704AAA4wfw">
	<title>Why do people keep judging me . . ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>My parents and friends judge me by how I look and what I like . It makes me cry -LRB- I know I 'm a baby cry . - . -RRB- hearing people saying I look disgusting or `` Why do you like this ? '' `` Why do you wear this ? '' I really like horror and I also wear black a lot . I use eyeliner and mascara . My mom said I look gross and my dad said I look like an emo and a horrible person . I told them they ca n't judge people by how they look and what they like cause everyone has their own opinion . I feel like talking to a councelor . Am I right or wrong ?</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403453921000">You Are Not Ugly , Society Is ! Am sorry that they make you feel like that . no one has the right to make you feel like your not beautiful dont lose who you are . You are you , you are beautiful . Please do n't let them change you . If you need to talk to someone am here . But you are right take care and dont forget your beautiful Lizmoore6969@yahoo.com</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403455351000">Ignore them . This world is full of ignorant judgemental fvcks .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140619184905AArLOPa">
	<title>Do I like African American people ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>My answer : No I dont like them . Do I have any reasons : Yes I do ! Do I have many reasons : Yes I do ! My reasons : They are arrogant , cocky , self-absorbed and agressive . My evidence : one time a black man called me a white twat , another time two black men told me to `` fuck off '' because the street wasnt white territory , one time a black woman said i am a rich white boy who is a `` fool '' because i accidently bumped into her shopping trolley . Do I need any reasons or evidence : No i dont need any reasons or evidence because I just dont like african american people . P.s. i dont care if you guys dont give a shit but its my opinion and it counts . I also dont give a shit what you people think of me because in my perspective you 're opinion of me or anyone else does n't count .</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403229069000">And there is 89.9 % of the Republican party right there ... ... ... ... ... ... ... ...</answer><suggestions>republican/ORGANIZATION party/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403229301000">Good , now ask somebody do they care ? and you do realize this is a site for asking questions right ? not to spew out random racist idiotic thoughts ... suck it up and get a life . Obviously you do care what people think otherwise you would n't feel the need to come on a social website and vent out your hatred</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140612213900AAIuOWy">
	<title>Tell me about your religious beliefs ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I promise I will try really hard not to laugh and to take them seriously</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402634456000">I do n't have any</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402634850000">Based on the Sumerian text and how its stories are found in the text of every religion around the world . I believe that at one time we were visited by extra terrestrials . http:\/\/www.huffingtonpost.com\/2013\/04\/09\/alien-code-in-human-genes_n_3034876.html http:\/\/www.evolutionnews.org\/2014\/05\/alien_dna_found085701.html This would also end much of the debate between theists and atheists .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402634915000">You have the same mindset as a Christian - that same arrogant , smirking , know-it-all attitude ... Hmm . Maybe you ARE a Christian ? ...</answer><suggestions>christian/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140612210603AA3e5w2">
	<title>For the Duke of Ed gold award , do I have to do a minimum of 12 months for each section service , skill , and physical recreation ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>Is it supposed to be split up like 4 months of service , 10 months of skill , 4 months of physical or something ?</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>Or can I just do 18 months of one section -LRB- Direct entry -RRB- . Also does things like photo editing , scripting , forum moderating , online game administrator count towards a skill ? and who can sign that since the `` assessors '' will be online . Thanks in advance !</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402677676000">And he said to them , `` Go into all the world and preach the gospel to the whole creation . He who believes and is baptized will be saved ; but he who does not believe will be condemned . And these signs will accompany those who believe : in my name they will cast out demons ; they will speak in new tongues ; they will pick up serpents , and if they drink any deadly thing , it will not hurt them ; they will lay their hands on the sick , and they will recover . '' So then the Lord Jesus/PERSON , after he had spoken to them , was taken up into heaven , and sat down at the right hand of God . And they went forth and preached everywhere , while the Lord worked with them and confirmed the message by the signs that attended it . Amen .</answer><suggestions>jesus/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402778575000">Did you try to do a search on Google ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140625061721AAZtfz4">
	<title>what are the opinions of the deobandis ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>what are views of them ?</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403702782000">ALOT similar to al/PERSON azhar/PERSON . It follows the ideologies of ahlus sunnah wal jama'a .</answer><suggestions>al/PERSON azhar/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403707915000">Deoband/PERSON and Bareli/PERSON scholars follow Hanfi school of thoughts based on the teaching of Imam/PERSON Abu/PERSON Hanifa/PERSON -LRB- RA -RRB- but they do not believe in Nazer/PERSON o Niaz/PERSON and Wasila/PERSON of/PERSON Aowliya/PERSON Allah/PERSON and follow up of the practice and rituals of Early pious Muslims . They claim strict follow up of Quran and they reject many Hadiths found in Siha/PERSON sitta/PERSON . The difference in both the sects is very small but the dispute may lead to rejection of the authority of each other . Deobandis are strict in their practice and behavior like Wahabism -LRB- of Saudi/LOCATION Arabia/LOCATION -RRB- . They do not pay due respect to Aowliya Allah and their Circles -LRB- Msalic \/ Silsilas -RRB- Barelvi scholars follow Abu Hanifa 's school of thoughts as well as the guidance & Rulling of Salf & Sufi circless like Chishti , Qadri , Naqshbandi maslaks etc. . They pay respect to the existing Khaliphas and Mujawars of the said Circles \/ Msaliks . Barelvis are simple , mild and follow the fatwa and guidance of the said Khaliphas and Peers of certain circles .</answer><suggestions>deoband/LOCATION bareli/LOCATION abu/PERSON hanifa/PERSON nazer/PERSON niaz/PERSON aowliya/LOCATION allah/LOCATION siha/PERSON sitta/PERSON saudi/LOCATION arabia/LOCATION abu/PERSON hanifa/PERSON chishti/PERSON qadri/PERSON naqshbandi/PERSON maslaks/PERSON barelvis/PERSON khaliphas/PERSON</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140622033603AAomdjr">
	<title>You know what I 've discovered ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>That in all my life , the one thing that 's really prevented mr from going anywhere is the hypocrisy of man . You there . All of you with your tongues of misguidance , Spewing hate to everyone who dost not agree with your idiotic morality . You are a fool . And every single one of you are as full of excrement as the next . To the atheist , who will swear by his bullshit science thay he little understands thay there can be no God . And to the moralistic bible thumper who will bomb an abortion clinic and take the lives of women and feti in the name of your god . When will you stupid motherfuckers ever learn ? You are nothing . Your lives mean nothing . Your concepts of truth are impeded by your own animalistic desire , and the very one of you who point to the kettle will be the pot who will burn in the fire . Why do n't you all just save karma some time and nuke yourselves ? I 'm way ahead of you . .</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403433451000">That 's great . Please tell us what time today you will be asking a question people actually care about .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403433490000">says the 12 year old lol</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403433527000">Okay cool . Now what 's your question ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403433579000">I like your way of solving things which is to talk about them instead of actually doing something about it .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403433754000">So sorry that you turned yourself into a loser . Stop blaming others and grow up ...</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403433890000">There 's an interesting book you should read . Quest among the bewildered . By wulf/PERSON zendik/PERSON . Is not for the faint of heart . But like all revolutionaries be was corrupted .</answer><suggestions>wulf/PERSON zendik/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403433934000">Colossians 3:8 ESV But now you must put them all away : anger , wrath , malice , slander , and obscene talk from your mouth . You 're dong it wrong ... Edit : What you say says more about you than anyone else ... Someone needs a hug ...</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403434111000">The time is now . F #ck n #gger</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403434118000">self-righteous little gob $ hite</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403434632000">Methinks thou dost protest too much</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403434772000">cool story ... but gods are still man-made ideas .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403435361000">Cool</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403443366000">Who made you get out of bed today with a rotten attitude Samm/PERSON ?</answer><suggestions>samm/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403462928000">OK , so now tell us how you really feel .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140611024537AARmApG">
	<title>what gods do you believe in ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>i personaly worship the donger god</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402480041000">I believe in the Almighty Father Holiest of Holies</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402480094000">dung ? ... .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402480099000">I believe in the one true Flying Spaghetti Monster .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402480245000">i believe that there is only one god in this whole universe .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402480333000">Goku SSJGOD</answer><suggestions>goku/PERSON ssjgod/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402480445000">Gary/PERSON , the invisible magical unicorn . He is a very fair deity , he likes praise but if he does something wrong like sending inclement weather he also accepts criticism .</answer><suggestions>gary/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402480503000">I believe in the one and only God , that God is the creator .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402481269000">Hank/PERSON Hill/PERSON</answer><suggestions>hank/PERSON hill/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402481425000">There is only one creator of the entire universe and everything in it , God . This creator is known by many names from the different cultural perspectives around the world . Some call the creator Allah , some call the creator FSM , some call him Odin , Zeus , etc. . A rose by any other name smells as sweet . But there are lesser gods which God did create . Psalm 82 addresses them . Basically , anyone who brings the word of God may be called a god and is a judge of man . See also John 10:35 .</answer><suggestions>allah/PERSON fsm/ORGANIZATION john/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402481588000">The one and only true God , FSM -LRB- peace be upon his meat balls -RRB- his big bang with the virgin Evolution created us all and made some great pasta sauce .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402482367000">I believe that we are all gods , but I do n't worship any of us</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402486116000">i beleive that i m god</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402487487000">Jesus/PERSON Christ/PERSON is my Savior : -RRB- The truth is that we are all sinners who have rebelled against a perfectly holy and righteous God . As a result , none of us is good enough to enter a perfect heaven . We have all sinned and , therefore , deserve to spend eternity separated from God in hell . No amount of good works or trying to live a good life can take care of your sin problem . Eph . 2:8 -9 says , `` For by grace you have been saved through faith , and that not of yourselves ; it is the gift of God , not of works , lest anyone should boast . '' It 's because of His amazing love for us that Jesus/PERSON Christ/PERSON came to this earth to die on the cross and pay your sin debt and mine in FULL . Three days later , He rose again and conquered death . He promises to forgive ALL your sins -LRB- past , present , and future -RRB- and give you eternal life as a free gift the moment you trust in Him alone to save you . John/PERSON 3:16 says , `` For God so loved the world that He gave His only begotten Son , that whoever believes in Him should not perish but have everlasting life . '' The gospel message is simple . Jesus died and rose again so that you can receive eternal life freely the moment you believe in Him ! This link helped me when I was struggling with my salvation : http:\/\/www.faithalone.org\/tracts\/ycbs.html</answer><suggestions>jesus/PERSON christ/PERSON jesus/PERSON christ/PERSON john/PERSON 3:16/PERSON jesus/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402488971000">The God in islam teach .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402493721000">I believe in all of them but do not like them all</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140607180855AAvNgve">
	<title>how come people of these countries are considered Arabs although they look different from each other ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>people of African countries like Algeria/LOCATION , Morocco/LOCATION , Egypt/LOCATION , Syria/LOCATION , , , people of those countries look so different from ethnic Arabs/LOCATION of/LOCATION Saudi/LOCATION for example , and they even have different culture and have different versions of Arabic language .</content><suggestions>algeria/LOCATION morocco/LOCATION egypt/LOCATION syria/LOCATION saudi/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402190738000">because they all have one thing in common , the Arabic language , therefor they are Arabs . that 's like comparing between the U.S/LOCATION and Australia/LOCATION , different from etch other but both are English speaking countries .</answer><suggestions>u.s/LOCATION australia/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402193021000">Agree , an Jesus/PERSON loves ya , we just ask Him in our heart , forgive our sins to be saved , He is Faithful and Just to forgive all our sins , praise The LORD . An seek a Christian Church , not a mormon or Jehovah/PERSON 's witness , they 're not Christians or the ones that support homosexuality. An google/ORGANIZATION Beth/PERSON Moore/PERSON an Joyce/PERSON Meyer/PERSON , good Christian teachers to encourage you in Jesus . An good to read Bible , John/PERSON is a great place to begin . An may The LORD Jesus/PERSON speak to , save you , your family , friends , an all lost , give good Christians in your path , work things for your good and God 's Glory , in Jesus/PERSON Mighty Saving Name amen Shalom Have faith in God . Mark 11:22 God is a Refuge for us.Ps 62:8 ACLJ.org Persecution.org CBN.com emircaner.com more about Jesus</answer><suggestions>jesus/PERSON jehovah/PERSON beth/PERSON moore/PERSON joyce/PERSON meyer/PERSON jesus/PERSON john/PERSON jesus/PERSON jesus/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402194773000">An Arab is anyone who can speak the Arabic language , the definition of an Arab is no longer that of an ethnic one , especially after the rise of Islam , many people from the east and the west came to the Arabian/LOCATION peninsula/LOCATION to believe in Islam . Thats how in fact we got many Arabic dialects because their pronunciation was not precise</answer><suggestions>west/LOCATION arabian/LOCATION peninsula/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402206991000">Each Arab/LOCATION country have it 's own local Arabic and it 's citizen 's can speak Arabic -LRB- pure arabic -RRB- as well . people who live in the Arab/LOCATION gulf/LOCATION speak the same local arabic and have the same culture and traditions . people who live in Algeria/LOCATION , morocco/LOCATION , Tunisia/LOCATION and Mauritania/LOCATION speak the same local Arabic and have the same culture and traditions and the people who live in Jordan/LOCATION , Syria/LOCATION , Lebanon/LOCATION and Palestine/LOCATION speak the same local language and have the same culture and traditions . bear in mind that there are NO BIG deference between the local Arabic of each spot in the Arab world and the Arabic -LRB- pure arabic -RRB- . That means all Arab can understand and talk the local languages of all Arab world spots in addition to the Arabic -LRB- pure arabic -RRB-</answer><suggestions>arab/LOCATION gulf/LOCATION algeria/LOCATION morocco/LOCATION tunisia/LOCATION mauritania/LOCATION jordan/LOCATION syria/LOCATION lebanon/LOCATION palestine/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402282044000">Salam They are the same semistic race although they are different ethnic and culture</answer><suggestions>salam/PERSON</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140626203836AAh9yJF">
	<title>witches , satanists etc. . knowing you 'll go to hell . . why do you want to ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>thank you for your time and answers .</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403840411000">Everyone will be going to one hell or another according to the different religions .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403840467000">Because they will get to party with Satan .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403840524000">Anybody who believes they will go to your Hell , and want to , do not think they will be tortured there . Perhaps a sort of `` Better to rule in Hell , than serve in Heaven '' mentality . That said kid , most witches and Satanists do not believe they 're going to Hell , at least not your concept of it .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403840530000">There is no so-called hell . I will simply reincarnate</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403843225000">cause they do n't know that is why we are in charge as saint or chrisitan to spread the gospel of god . . and nit by just words , but by our action in life that they will see and it show , and that they believe and pull to the truth . .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403844369000">Witches do n't believe in the Christian hell as they are not Christians . They are pagans . Satanists believe they will be a ruling class in hell .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403845657000">God is a LIAR . And you are brainwashed believing whatever you are told .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140604180346AAsPQvO">
	<title>atheists : why do you think that religion should be insulted ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>i am a christian and find some of the beliefs and practices of muslims hard to take in if not abhorrent but i dont think that islam should be insulted , or any other religion for that matter , even the mormon faith . what makes you think that religion should be insulted and how will the world benefit from the insulting of religion ? all i can say is that religion wont go away just because it is being made fun of .</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401930409000">- People who do n't like their beliefs being laughed at should n't have such funny beliefs . - anon . - Since it is obviously inconceivable that all religions can be right , the most reasonable conclusion is that they are all wrong . - Christopher/PERSON Hitchens/PERSON Religion is a gross insult to reason and civilisation .</answer><suggestions>christopher/PERSON hitchens/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401930519000">Maybe because religion drives people to fly planes into buildings , blow things up , start wars , kidnap schoolgirls , murder doctors , vilify LGBT people , force their agenda into government policy , and teach \*\*\*\*\*\*\*\* in science classes . Can you think of a good reason to NOT insult it ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401930548000">I do n't insult religion . I insult stupidity , like trying to pass religious creation myths off as science , or legally requiring adherence to a specific religion 's beliefs . Or making me listen to prayers when I want to actually get something done .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401930572000">6But when you ask , you must believe and not doubt , because the one who doubts is like a wave of the sea , blown and tossed by the wind . 7That person should not expect to receive anything from the Lord . 8Such a person is double-minded and unstable in all they do .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401930857000">ALL who are of islam -LRB- muslims -RRB- are sworn to obey the law of their so-called god allah ABSOLUTELY and without exception ... it is the decree of allah that islam is to dominate the world ... and that ALL who do not submit to the law of allah -LRB- infidels -RRB- are to be KILLED ... that is FACT ... . If one would read the Koran , one will find out that Allah wants Muslims to kill the infidels -LRB- unbelievers -RRB- wherever they are found -LRB- Koran 9:5 -RRB- , and that peace will come only to those who submit to him -LRB- Koran 8:17 , 48:29 , and 65 -RRB- . The Koran also has Allah saying that unbelievers should be killed -LRB- Koran 2:191 , 3:141 , 4:104 , 4:89 , 8:12 -16 , 9:5 , 9:73 -74 , 9:123 , 25:52 ... -RRB- , that Muslim apostates should be killed or chastised -LRB- Koran 2:39 , 2:85 , 3:85 , 3:106 , 4:89 , 16:106 , and 47:25 -28 -RRB- , that the heads and fingers of unbelievers should be cut off -LRB- Koran 5:33 , 8:12 , and 47:4 -RRB- , and that Muslims should fight and humiliate Jews and Christians -LRB- Koran 5:18 and 9:29 -RRB- . Allah orders Muslims not to take Jews , Christians and other unbelievers as friends -LRB- Koran 3:28 , 5:51 and 9:23 -RRB- , and will not forgive Christians -LRB- Koran 4:48 and 4:116 -RRB- . Muhammad/PERSON taught to put the infidels to death wherever they were found -LRB- Koran 2:191 , 2:244 , 4:89 , 5:36 , 9:5 , and 9:29 -RRB- , urged Muslims to fight the unbelievers who are close -LRB- Koran 9:123 -RRB- , mentioned that fighting is obligatory -LRB- Koran 2:216 -RRB- , and mandated the conquering of those relatives who opposed Muslims because loyalty to Islam overrode all other human bonds -LRB- Koran 9:23 -24 , and 58:22 -RRB- . as for mormons ... . a lot of that cult is watered down islam ... one of their founding goals is to have mormonism dominate the world ... mormon law is to be imposed ... just as islam is to be imposed ... just slightly different means ... what I know of islam and mormonism I learned from muslims and mormons ... almost became a mormon way back when ... thank God I was a strong enough atheist at that time ... and checked it out independently first ... and learned what mormonism really is ...</answer><suggestions>muhammad/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401930998000">I do n't think I have ever insulted someone elses beliefs ... and I have friends of all beliefs ... Respect is something we all have to have ... because we are all human ... under one sun ... and believe it or not ... We all need each other . And we should Never blame the actions of a few ... on the many ... And according to Christian belief ... We should take that great big beam of wood out of our own eyes ... before we take the splinter out of anothers . . He \/ she who is without Sin ... should cast the first stone ... No religion ... is Pure ... none !!</answer><suggestions>christian/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401931099000">Atheists are hypocrites . They call us bigots but they discriminate against Christians by taking away our rights VIA the ACLU . Plus they mock us all the time and assault us . I 've been physically harrased by Atheists before . I used to bully Christian kids when I was an Atheist . Atheism is a religion of sin , hatred toward Christians and Communism .</answer><suggestions>christians/ORGANIZATION aclu/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401931175000">Religion does n't seem to have a problem insulting me . Most religions class me as an unworthy , immoral , lost , dark-hearted fool who not only will go to eternal punishment but also deserves it ... simply for the thought-crime of non-belief . And many religious people not only have no qualms about describing me in these terms , but doing so explicitly to my face . And they try to justify this abhorrent behavior by lamely claiming that they 're not insulting me , they 're just expressing their `` deeply held beliefs '' . Well , I `` deeply believe '' that these people are insane , and their beliefs are laughable . Turnabout is fair play . \* Note - I do not lump all religious people into the same category . Many are lovely , respectful people who practice their faith gently and are not a bad influence . The ones who fit the description above , however , can go to hell as far as I 'm concerned . Metaphorically speaking , of course .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401931186000">`` Atheists : why do you think that religion should be insulted ? '' I do n't think it SHOULD be but if you advertise LOUDLY that you believe in some really , really crazy stuff you leave yourselves wide open to be mocked ... vigorously ; -RRB- ~</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401931979000">It is christians that lie under oath in court to force their fantasies into my class rooms , not muslims .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401933276000">Playing devil 's advocate here : The main reasons that lots of atheists insult religion is because religion leads to discrimination , intolerance , and slows down the advance of science . It spreads lies to children who do n't know any better and is used to justify violence . Most atheists do n't think that way . Those that do go out of their way to insult religion tend to be immature teenagers or young adults who 've become so sure of themselves that they flat out ignore the good things that religion can bring people , like charity , a sense of community , and a set of morals that help many to become better persons . Unfortunately , the intolerant atheists currently have the megaphone and are what most people think of when the word ` atheist ' comes up . Just ignore them ; most of them grow up eventually .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401933407000">If religion makes ridiculous claims , then it is open to ridicule . Forget Islam . most of those unfortunate to have been born into that foul creed have little choice but to accept the putrid doctrine they are given.The alternative is a gruesome end . Look at your religion , Just as gruesome ; just as abhorrent , But you were lucky enough to be be born into a secular civilization which curbed exactly those atrocities that Islam carries out which Christianity - another foul creed - once did . The difference is that Christianity - no longer having the political power it once enjoyed and which Islam does enjoy , realized long ago that for it to survive , it had to comply to secular morality . That of course does not stop its leaders from still trying to dupe and manipulate the credulous . The atrocities currently carried out in the name of Christianity in Africa/LOCATION are there for the world to see . Believe whatever Babylonian\/Sumerian mythology you want to believe -LRB- for that 's where the Abrahamic religions originated -RRB- . But do n't expect that because it is your right to swallow this crap , these obnoxious religions should be immune from ridicule .</answer><suggestions>islam/ORGANIZATION africa/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401938532000">You can respect people but you should not respect ideas simply because they are held by someone else . You yourself just posted that some beliefs of Islam are abhorrent . You did not say Muslims are abhorrent . What Christians often forget is that non-Christians often find their beliefs abhorrent . Consider a very basic religious belief that could be thought of as abhorrent . Let 's start with Original Sin . What makes this abhorrent is the following : According to the bible all death is due to this first sin . Prior to the sin no death happened . But we know that life existed long before humans and the death is a natural part of existence . If death is natural and it precedes humans then it can not be due to an Original Sin . Therefore Jesus/PERSON was in error . There was nothing to redeem as there was no Original Sin . He was killed for nothing . Ignoring how abhorrent sacrificing a human for the evils of others are , original sin makes people think they are unworthy and bad people without a god . Why would they be bad people ? There is no reason to think badly of oneself . Telling people they are unworthy sinners is evil , in and of itself , as it is an observably false statement . Without Original Sin there is no redemptive death . Jesus/PERSON was n't necessary . The Blood of Christ washes nothing away . So why collect money to convert people when that money could be built feeding the poor and helping the sick ? Why make people feel bad ? That is just one of many things .</answer><suggestions>jesus/PERSON jesus/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401939307000">I never want to demean , do n't like myself then . To speak truth with love ... takes training , development , atheists donty get that .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401981371000">Often they think that disagreeing with their opinion is a personal attack . They take it that way to try to manipulate people into agreeing with them . It 's the same tactic the homosexual community uses . They run around calling everybody that disagrees with them `` haters '' , but what is actually hateful , going around yelling insults or simply holding an opinion that you feel is right ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140611002243AAXERMP">
	<title>What makes you so sure you 're right in your beliefs ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>-- Possum</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402471438000">I 'm not sure . I believe my beliefs are correct .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402471539000">Certainty is for idiots .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402471544000">The very internet you are posting this question through and the very computer you are posting it with are direct demonstrations of the usefulness of the scientific method .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402471603000">Its a thing about faith . Its a gift . You are not supposed to impose it to others</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402471647000">god tells me i am correct</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402471668000">It 's not about being `` sure '' and I never said that .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402471682000">I hear angels singing . `` the Lord is Messiah '' `` Christ died for man and He shall reign forever '' Turn to Jesus/PERSON Christ/PERSON , read the bible , and obey God . Then you will have eternal life in heaven where there is love and joy . http:\/\/www.youtube.com\/watch?v=Pe6eMQQIoqE</answer><suggestions>jesus/PERSON christ/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402471727000">LOL , can of worms Possum ! I 'm not sure about anything , in fact , at times , I actually hope I 'm wrong ! I guess each of us have a sense of what is believable and what is BS , but sure ... ? No one truly knows the truth of the origins of mankind .</answer><suggestions>mankind/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402471751000">Because I once was an habitual liar and a thief and I hated people and was enslaved to all sorts of vices including drugs , alcohol , tobacco , gambling , greed and was arrogant and cowardly and a blasphemer ; but by the grace of God I am none of those things any longer . http:\/\/www.divinerevelations.info\/documents\/several_christian_testimonies\/index.htm http:\/\/www.iamsecond.com\/films\/</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402471758000">Experience .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402471851000">That 's why I do n't have any .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402471858000">Faith , reason and practice</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402472168000">Ongoing research , constant checking of material , have n't had anyone be able to reasonably give me an alternative . Does n't look like any alternative exists as powerful as this faith I believe in .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402472247000">This is Christianity : 1 John 1:8 -10 We are sinners who confess our sins and ask for forgiveness anyone who says otherwise is a liar ... James 3:2 we stumble in many ways so we put our faith in the only perfect one Jesus Christ who is able to keep his whole body -LRB- The Christian family -RRB- in check ... 1 John 2:1 and he advocates for Christians when we do sin ... Romans 8:34 as well as he intercedes on our behalf . Philippians 3:12 -14 -LRB- concerning being perfect -RRB- `` Not that I have already obtained all this , or have already arrived at my goal , but I press on to take hold of that for which Christ Jesus took hold of me . Brothers and sisters , I do not consider myself yet to have taken hold of it . But one thing I do : Forgetting what is behind and straining toward what is ahead , I press on toward the goal to win the prize for which God has called me heavenward in Christ Jesus '' . Galatians 6:1 `` Brothers and sisters , if someone is caught in a sin , you who live by the Spirit should restore that person gently . But watch yourselves , or you also may be tempted '' . Hebrews 5:1 -3 -LRB- highlighting weakness leading to sin , not sacrifice -RRB- Every high priest is selected from among the people and is appointed to represent the people in matters related to God , to offer gifts and sacrifices for sins . He is able to deal gently with those who are ignorant and are going astray , since he himself is subject to weakness . This is why he has to offer sacrifices for his own sins , as well as for the sins of the people . It is said , `` Christians are sinners who need Christ '' and it 's never been said , `` Christians are perfect '' This is legalism : Christians must be perfect 100 % of the time -LRB- not Biblical truth -RRB- Once you accept Christ you will never sin again -LRB- not Biblical truth -RRB- If you sin the road back to Jesus Christ may be too difficult -LRB- not Biblical truth -RRB- Christians who sin condemn themselves worse than non-Christians who sin -LRB- not Biblical truth -RRB- Legalists will Deny the Following : Romans 3:28 -LRB- To this very day we maitain that we are justified by faith apart from the law -RRB- Romans 4:5 -LRB- It is God who justifies the ungodly , their faith is credited as righteousness -RRB- Romans 4:13 -LRB- It never has been by the law that Abraham and his offspring received the promise that he would be heir of the world , but through the righteousness that comes by faith -RRB- Romans 5:1 -LRB- Since we have been justified through faith , we have peace with God through our Lord Jesus Christ -RRB- 2 Corinthians 4:18 -LRB- So we fix our eyes not on what is seen , but on what is unseen , since what is seen is temporary , but what is unseen is eternal -RRB- 2 Corinthians 5:7 -LRB- For we live by faith , not by sight -RRB- And this is to name just a few passages concerning faith and the law , but legalists believe that everyone must be spotless , blameless and blemishless every day because they do not realize that only Christ will determine if we are spotless , blameless and blemishless come judgement day through how we 've lived our lives by faith in Jesus/PERSON Chris/PERSONt . Legalists believe that if we sin we are `` Backslidden '' , but this is not a Biblical truth . Our life long journey with Christ/PERSON is not a sinless one , but rather we put our faith in him and in him we will be called righteous and chosen . Legalists are more concerned about living by rules and regulations and what not to do than they 'll ever be concerned with judging what is right and living by it with faith in Jesus Christ where we are all bound to stumble from time to time even while we still press on with our faith and with love in our hearts . Charity covers a multitude of sins , love covers a multitude of sins , faith does the same as well as hospitality , but legalists work hard at denying these facts . SEE : James 5:20 and1 Peter 4:8</answer><suggestions>john/PERSON james/PERSON john/PERSON philippians/LOCATION jesus/PERSON jesus/PERSON christ/PERSON abraham/PERSON jesus/PERSON christ/PERSON corinthians/ORGANIZATION jesus/PERSON christ/PERSON jesus/PERSON james/PERSON peter/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402474055000">. I looked for 15 years for a religious group that actually taught what the Bible says . After repeatedly rejecting the one that God sent to me , because OTHERS said that the people who adhered to it were weird , God finally took pity on me and sent someone to grab my attention ! Oh my , how patient he was with me ! But to my credit , I have to say that as soon as I started to listen to the person he sent , I did quickly figure out all that she said was true . Jehovah 's Witness since 1971 . .</answer><suggestions>jehovah/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402474753000">When I was younger , I sinned deliberately . Now , I no longer sin deliberately . The one difference was that when I sought the Lord God with all my heart -LRB- Jeremiah/PERSON 29:13 -RRB- , He did find me . Since then , I have intentionally ascertained a personal relationship with the Lord God and His beautiful Son , Jesus/PERSON Christ/PERSON . There is a huge difference in my life now . I used to be overly outspoken about any topic of discussion , a nasty gossip , very judgemental toward others , and self-serving . Now , I am soft-spoken and no longer resort to arguments regarding any issues , I no longer gossip about anything , am no longer judgemental toward others , and am very grateful ; giving freely to anyone in need . When I read in 1 Peter/PERSON 2:3 -5 , about how the holy women of the ancient past used to adorn themselves with their `` inner beauty '' , I took it seriously and now attempt to live as they did . These changes were not my doing . Jesus gave me these new distinguishing qualities , based upon His teachings . When I decided to follow Him , He gave me His peace , just as He did to His disciples -LRB- John/PERSON 14:27 -RRB- .</answer><suggestions>jeremiah/PERSON god/PERSON jesus/PERSON christ/PERSON jesus/PERSON john/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402598335000">Being certain about one 's belief might not be called faith , I think . No matter what you try to do , there are certain things in this universe that we can not fully comprehend yet we believe in . It is like trying to put all the sand in the beach into your cupped hands . Our brains can only handle so much that we just can not do anything but surrender and believe . I do not need to be sure that the spirits i see when I had my third eye opened are good or bad , or the places I go to when I astral project are still of this world or just a product of my imagination . I just believe them because I believe them . I do not have to be sure but I do believe them . While some will say or ask me that I need to convince them , no need . It is no longer my problem if other people do not believe what I believe in .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>

