<question id="20140613154011AAJ98M9">
	<title>Why are Liberals calling for no new war in Iraq/LOCATION ?</title><suggestions>iraq/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>Are we going to let Iran/LOCATION do it for us ?</content><suggestions>iran/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402699317000">i do n't think it 's just liberals</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402699323000">Are you saying there should be one ? And would you enlist and fight ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402699365000">We are tired of being policeman to the world .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402699376000">Not liberal , but we see how the first turned out . It 's a failed state . Let 's fix up the 50 we have . Several are over their heads or treading water .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402699378000">It is so they do not have to explain why they told us we have to leave Iraq/LOCATION .</answer><suggestions>iraq/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402699407000">they think we put anth in to Iraq/LOCATION</answer><suggestions>iraq/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402699473000">Leftists do n't mind genocidal groups doing what they do , especially against people desiring liberty and freedom . I guarantee you we wo n't hear a peep out of the UN for the very same reason . And plus the progressivists have invested heavily in their proxy fighters , they 're not going to destroy it .</answer><suggestions>un/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402699599000">I am not a liberal but we have lost to many soldiers already . There must be some solutions ????</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402699670000">Because they are consistent and the first one was a useless disaster .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402699727000">Everyone Should just stop , yes the US/LOCATION Should not intervene in Iraq/LOCATION as simple as that</answer><suggestions>us/LOCATION iraq/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402699765000">You really want to spend another trillion dollars in Iraq/LOCATION ?</answer><suggestions>iraq/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402699885000">Because the first one worked out so well .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402700103000">Because this is just the inevitable Iraq/LOCATION civil war . So why should we go another trillion dollars and debt and sacrifice more American lives ? You 've just chosen a side to blindly support , like conservatives always do .</answer><suggestions>iraq/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402700709000">It 's HILARIOUS how CONS are always screaming about LESS GOVERNMENT INVOLVEMENT IN PEOPLES LIVES !!! ' Wahhhh . Wahhhh poopy whiny cranky CON just pooped in pants because we want less government involvement in peoples lives wahhhhhhhhhh ! '' FOLLOWED BY ... `` WHAT ? We are leaving that OTHER COUNTRY ??????????? NOOOOO !!!!! Wahhhhhh ! Wahhhhhhh ! We MUST BE ALL INVOLVED IN THOSE PEOPLES LIVES !!!! Wahhhhh ! Wahhhhh ! We need to TOTALLY CONTROL those peoples LIVES ! Wahhhhhhhh ! CON going poo poo again in pants ! Wahhhh CON need BINKY & MOMMY because PRESIDENT wants to LIBERATE us from being all up inside peoples S. H I. T. which is what CRANKY CON says wants but is now CRYING & WHINING now that it 's happening ! Wahhhhh wahhhhhhh . I want my John/PERSON McCaine/PERSON doll !!!!!! My diaper is poopy ! I 'm a stinky cranky flip flopping WHINER CON who NEVER OFFERS anything other then NEGATIVITY AND COMPLAINTS !!! ' Wahhhhhhhhhhhhhhh !!!!</answer><suggestions>wahhhhhh/PERSON wahhhhhhh/PERSON wahhhhh/PERSON wahhhhh/PERSON wahhhhhhhh/PERSON wahhhh/ORGANIZATION con/ORGANIZATION need/ORGANIZATION binky/ORGANIZATION &/ORGANIZATION mommy/ORGANIZATION wahhhhh/PERSON wahhhhhhh/PERSON john/PERSON mccaine/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402701976000">Because libs do n't want a repeat of this : http:\/\/www.cnsnews.com\/news\/article\/ali-meyer\/74-us-afghan-casualties-came-after-obama-ordered-troops-increased</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140625100007AAcadtk">
	<title>Who do you consider to be an effective leader ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>Who do you consider to be an effective leader and why ?</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403715646000">Mad Max</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403715678000">Marx/PERSON .</answer><suggestions>marx/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403715905000">ME</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403715994000">We can bring about positive change through our wallets . Our elected officials are incompetent . Fight welfare , buy American .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403716164000">honesty , truth , integrity , work ethic . proven leadership abilities and uphold the constitution to the letter to name a few . however , this can not be said of the present administration</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403716726000">FDR . Led us out of the Great Depression . Rallied us up for WWII , which launched us into the superpower position and set us up for great prosperity . Started great infrastructure projects Had a way with words that made people feel better and feel good about being Americans , but unlike some more modern presidents he was able to back his words up with legitimate improvement .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403716782000">Scott/PERSON Walker/PERSON . He stood up to the corrupt teachers ' unions and did n't back down under public pressure from liberal activists . He lowered taxes , balanced the budget , and created job growth in his state . He represents the people who elected him as well as those that did n't .</answer><suggestions>scott/PERSON walker/PERSON</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140617015321AAEmy38">
	<title>Speeding ticket officer gave me - she told me she wrote it for a different speed then what I was going . ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>So , I was speeding , and this lady said she clocked my going 68 but was going to write it that I was going 64 , yet I still get this huge ticket . The bottom line is that she wrote an invalid ticket , right ? Cause she did n't clock me going 64 ... So if I DO go to court could I easily get out of it ? Or should I just let it go and not look the gift horse in the mouth ?</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402995836000">In your state there probably is a HUGE difference in the fine , and the points given you between 68 and 64 MPH So this officer gives you a break money wise and point wise and you want to challenge that in court ? You are listening to a lot of Perry/PERSON Mason/PERSON wannabes who are telling you that if you take it to court and tell the judge that you were really going faster than what the officer gave you a ticket for , the judge will throw out the ticket , pat you on the back for being so honest and send you on your merry way . All the judge will do is say something to the effect of `` So you admit you were actually going faster than the what the officer gave you the ticket for < then I will void his ticket and charge you with traveling 68 instead of the 64 `` and increase the fine and points issued . It is up to the officer if he wants to write you for the actual speed or give you a break , and you want to fight it ? Officers give this kind of break daily , it is common practice , judges know about it , and NO DRIVER fights it , because that 4 extra MPH could cost them an additional $ 100 or so , but not you I guess . So go ahead and dispute the speed , admit you were going faster and depending on what the speed limit was , you may talk yourself into a reckless driving ticket .</answer><suggestions>perry/PERSON mason/PERSON pat/PERSON you/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402996144000">Sorry , but you still have a valid ticket . Now retired , I almost never wrote a ticket for the full speed I actually saw . Most Officers will give you some sort of a break like that . The court has a basic fine plus so much for each mile over the limit . The amount per mile goes up at certain levels . Going 20 + miles over the limit would virtually double your ticket in the area where I worked so I rarely wrote for that speed unless the person I stopped was a total jerk . It is true that you can not generally talk your way out of a ticket , but you can talk your way into one when an Officer was actually prepared to simply warn you . You can also talk an Officer into writing for the full amount when they might otherwise be inclined to give you a partial break . The courts are equally influenced by your attitude and you could talk your way into a larger fine but not likely talk your way out of one .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402997403000">You have a couple of great answers here . This is not a ticket you could fight . By the way , the difference between 64 and 68 could be a difference between an ordinary speeding ticket and a ticket that includes reckless driving charges . It depends on the speed zone you was in when you got the ticket . So , consider yourself lucky that the cop is giving you a little break and just pay the ticket . Then SLOW DOWN .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403000260000">Any lawyer will tell you that judges do not take kindly to amateur Perry/PERSON Masons/PERSON thinking they can outsmart the law , especially when the officer gave you a break . Any judge worth his salt would throw the book at you in this situation for being such a smart ` donkey ' .</answer><suggestions>perry/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403009182000">-LCB- If you need a lawyer , you can file court paperwork for a PD . This is income related paperwork . Some courts will take a fine payment on the installment plan per a court order . You should not look a gift horse in the mouth . The cop cut you a break .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403009835000">What you should do is slow down . Then see your doctor to have your brain examined . Then keep obeying speed limits .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403012712000">No , you 'll have to use actual law to beat the ticket . Making up and using a cheap gimmick defense like what you described will get you nowhere in court . You have a right to meet your accusers in court . Read your state constitution and see if it says something like that . You had the right to remain silent until you gave up that right . You also gave up some other rights as well . Plus you gave up documents that put you under the transportation code . When you did that , the cop was able to charge you with `` driving '' and `` speeding '' in a `` vehicle '' under the transportation code . Do n't feel too bad , the cop has a loaded pistol on his hip and you were unprepared and nervous . www_logosRadioNetwork_com the Rule of Law program will give you some tips on what to do before you dig a hole and fall into it . There 's some good archived programs . . look for the one 's that say `` Eddie/PERSON 's night '' If the cop does n't show up in court you can get the case dismissed . Unfortunately , they are paid to show up and usually do . Read your state constitution for rights you have and read your state statutes to know what the laws are . Also learn how to challenge jurisdiction before you acknowledge your name in court followed by your motion to put everything on the record , followed by a restatement of your challenge to jurisdiction . Otherwise you 'll waive your right to `` personnel jurisdiction '' `` secrets the police do n't want you to know '' -LRB- good title on youtube/ORGANIZATION -RRB- Some good archived broadcasts at LogosRadionetwork_com are : ROL_2013-02_25 , ROL_2014-04-28 , ROL_2013-04-01 , ROL_2014-01-27 , ROL_2014_01_06 , ROL_2014_03_24 , ROL_2012-12-17 , ROL_2014-05-12 , ROL_2014-05-05 Note : Archived Program Rule of Law ROL_2014-05-19 discussed legal definitions in Illinois/LOCATION for `` Vehicle '' , `` passenger '' , `` transportation '' , `` driver '' at 1:37:45 in the broadcast . `` in commerce '' use of the public road . Every state has similar wording . Read your own state statutes with eyes open now . U.S. Code : Title 18 : Section 31 -LRB- a -RRB- Definitions . - In this chapter , the following definitions apply : -LRB- 6 -RRB- Motor vehicle . - The term `` motor vehicle '' means every description of carriage or other contrivance propelled or drawn by mechanical power and used for commercial purposes on the highways in the transportation of passengers , passengers and property , or property or cargo . -LRB- 10 -RRB- Used for commercial purposes . - The term `` used for commercial purposes '' means the carriage of persons or property for any fare , fee , rate , charge or other consideration , or directly or indirectly in connection with any business , or other undertaking intended for profit .</answer><suggestions>eddie/PERSON youtube/ORGANIZATION illinois/LOCATION u.s./LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403125478000">So you caught a break and now want to get your ticket dismissed . Go ahead take it to court , the officer will probably show up and amend your ticket to the full speed you were going .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140625201720AA1VzQt">
	<title>With 50 college credits what will be my rank in the National Guard ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I 'm going into the National/ORGANIZATION Guard/ORGANIZATION and was trying to figure out what rank I should be in the National/ORGANIZATION Guard/ORGANIZATION .</content><suggestions>national/ORGANIZATION guard/ORGANIZATION national/ORGANIZATION guard/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403753157000">E-3 \/ PFC , Private First Class</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403755294000">Maybe E-2 or E-3 . I was an E-1 in the Army as a college graduate , years ago when drafted .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403779707000">E3 .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140626101740AADAK0e">
	<title>Will cons be happy once Baghdad/LOCATION falls ?</title><suggestions>baghdad/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>Forget that Bush went there under multiple false pretenses . Forget that this war bankrupted our nation . Forget this was just a personal Bush/PERSON family vendetta and you were duped ... The bottom line is it happened under Obama/PERSON 's watch , so you need to celebrate . Good thing Mitt/PERSON did n't win or this would hurt that party that loves you so much ...</content><suggestions>bush/PERSON bush/PERSON obama/PERSON mitt/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403803141000">No . And you seem to not realize the current situation originated in Syria/LOCATION and spread to Iraq/LOCATION and has nothing to do with Bush/PERSON . And we care about our commander in chief being held accountable 6 years in . Something you obviously do n't .</answer><suggestions>syria/LOCATION iraq/LOCATION bush/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403803171000">They care much more about screwing Obama/PERSON than about anything else -- including working for their constituents they love so much .</answer><suggestions>obama/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403803409000">No . It will mean 4,000 good American people died in vain . I think you guys are the ones who are happy Obama/PERSON fvcked this up so you can point at Bush/PERSON and say `` I told you so . '' Well , are you happy ?</answer><suggestions>american/LOCATION obama/PERSON bush/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403803463000">I like how you said the Iraq/LOCATION war bankrupted our country . Let 's not forget that Obama/PERSON out spent the Iraq/LOCATION war with just the stimulus .</answer><suggestions>iraq/LOCATION obama/PERSON iraq/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403803507000">Baghdad/LOCATION already fell because Obama/PERSON is n't military minded . He thought great oratory skills would impress the likes of ISIS/ORGANIZATION so much , that they would throw down their weapons and sing happy songs .</answer><suggestions>baghdad/LOCATION obama/PERSON isis/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403803710000">I take your approach and forget all the facts of the Bush/PERSON presidency and assume your lies and half truths are correct . I 'll also keep in mind that the inept ability of president obongo/PERSON was directly responsible for a country that was stable with our assistance descent into hell . way to go Barrack -- you want to be remembered -- and you will -- as the worst most incompetent most corrupt president in American history .</answer><suggestions>bush/PERSON obongo/PERSON</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140612200636AAqMBhQ">
	<title>Where can i find hot police man in new/LOCATION york/LOCATION ?</title><suggestions>new/LOCATION york/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>Where are they !!</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402634549000">Got that makes me want to throw up those fucking cock suckers should eat shit and die of anal cancer .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402774463000">More info please</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140610123048AAZOuhW">
	<title>Why do some Cons hate Berghdal/PERSON ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>Its not his fault he was tortured for 5 years</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>Anyone who says he sought out to be caught by the Taliban/ORGANIZATION is nuts ; If anything he was trying to get D\/CD or some sort of suicide by cop no one would willingly be a prisoner of war ; also Drs have said he has bad PTSD</content><suggestions>taliban/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402428695000">they hate anything that does n't agree with their ideology .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402428722000">Hmmm playing badminton with Team Taliban/ORGANIZATION and having tea is torture ! So little liberal , where is your proof that the captain for team Taliban was tortured ! Oh wait , there is none ! LOL the asker says there is proof that Taliban/ORGANIZATION Bowe/PERSON was tortured yet can not produce a link ! Typical sheep !</answer><suggestions>taliban/ORGANIZATION taliban/ORGANIZATION bowe/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402428724000">I 'm sure they would have all been tough guys and not tried to play the game to save their skins and possibly get released rather than having their heads cut off on live TV .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402428768000">Those are the marching orders they were given by their handlers .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402428807000">Can you say deserter ? ... . I knew you could It 's not hate , it 's distrust</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402428814000">Definitely a sad state of affairs . I 'm happy the military freed themselves and freed the guy being held .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402428835000">It is too his fault . HE LEFT ON HIS OWN FREE WILL . Do you have any idea how many times I 've said this ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402428838000">guess libs think badminton and drinking tea is torture , wouldnt suprise me.they arent the toughest bunch of people</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402428866000">On the contrary , we want an investigation and a fair trial . Libbies seem to want to sweep everything that happened under the rug despite the fact that there are 6 dead soldiers involved . Afraid of what might come up about your dear Obama/PERSON if there is an investigation ?</answer><suggestions>obama/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402428928000">Cons gon na hate bro ...</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402428934000">So it 's not his fault he taught them badmitton and how to make bombs ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402428964000">Because they think they 've found -LRB- in Bergdahl/PERSON-RRB- something else they can use to attack Obama/PERSON . And for the obsessed Obama-haters , that 's all that matters . They would throw their own grandmother under the bus if they could blame it on the President . They have recently been allying themselves with Russia/LOCATION 's Putin -LRB- the KGB/ORGANIZATION despot -RRB- for the same reason . That 's how pathetic they 've become .</answer><suggestions>bergdahl/LOCATION obama/PERSON russia/LOCATION putin/PERSON kgb/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402428979000">There is nothing to substantiate your asinine claim that he was tortured . In fact , it appears quite the opposite is true .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402429021000">1 . He was n't tortured . 2 . He walked away from his post . 3 . He sought out the Taliban 4 . Six people died looking for him .</answer><suggestions>taliban/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402429074000">He would n't help protect the opium</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402429149000">Did he desert before or after he was tortured ? Look , I do n't hate the guy , but it sure looks like he deserted , so spare me if I 'm not exactly all broken up that he was captured and held prisoner after deserting his unit .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402429191000">Does anyone see the magnitude of news coverage of this as a distraction from other issues ? -LRB- and by the way , whether a `` deserter '' , criminal , murderer , etc. we morally did the right thing by rescuing him . We would do the same for ANYONE who fell overboard , was trapped in burning bulding or firey crash . First things first ... then a trial & judgment . -RRB-</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402429220000">They just proved to America/LOCATION and the world that they hate our troops .</answer><suggestions>america/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402429225000">I do n't hate Bergdahl/LOCATION . I want him court-martialed and punished if he deserted , as his fellow soldiers are convinced he did . I am angry with the Obama/PERSON administration for treating him like a hero and inviting his family to the Rose/LOCATION Garden/LOCATION , while mailing form letters to the families of soldiers who died trying to find him . And I am angry about them releasing dangerous men from Guantanamo/LOCATION , supposedly to get him back .</answer><suggestions>bergdahl/PERSON obama/PERSON guantanamo/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402429274000">He would n't have been captured , held for five years , and tortured if he had n't deserted his unit . Desertion is a crime in the military and can be punished with any punishment up to the death penalty in times of war .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402429286000">LOL ... He was n't tortured . He deserted his post and ASKED to meet up with the taliban/ORGANIZATION and he was `` treated as a guest '' . http:\/\/www.nbcnews.com\/storyline\/bowe-bergdahl-released\/taliban-spin-we-treated-captive-guest-n119461 When has ANY POW been released and continues to keep up the appearance of their captors ? IMO , he WILLINGLY converted and gave himself up `` for the cause '' .</answer><suggestions>taliban/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402429358000">Well , he walked off his post , at great effort and actively sought out the Taliban/ORGANIZATION . If ... I say , if ... they tortured him , which is highly unlikely , it is his fault . But in deserting and abandoning his post , he knew that search parties , patrols into enemy territory at great personal risk on the part of those participating would take place . When a guy ` disappears ' , the military SOP is to try and go find him . And such efforts are dangerous . We know that such efforts costs the lives of as many as six soldiers ALL because Bergdahl/PERSON deserted . If there is another explanation for his actions , I 'd love to hear it , but my imagination is not so advanced as to conceive of any other than he deserted and thrived in the company of the enemy with which he most certainly collaborated . Please . Give me an alternative theory .</answer><suggestions>taliban/ORGANIZATION bergdahl/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402429360000">he 's a deserter ... he should be hanged ...</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402429375000">They do n't . Why do you Libs love him ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402429635000">Because he was definitely a deserter and probably a collaborator . There was once a time in our history when desertion got one shot . We also hate the fact that the worst president in history traded five very dangerous terrorists for one cowardly deserter .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402429848000">They envy him . They know they themselves would never have the guts to refuse the draft , refuse to follow wrong orders or desert a cause , no matter how unjust . that plus the Obama-bashing excuse</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402430559000">He happens to be in the way of their hate for the Pres.</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402433124000">Americans in the United/LOCATION States/LOCATION today are no herd mindlessly different to their Puritan ancestors . That 's why Americans always need a monopoly to hate , just like their ancestors always needed another witch to burn .</answer><suggestions>united/LOCATION states/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402449114000">They do n't . Why do you Libs love him ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402476590000">He was in the hands of a people that are not known to keep prisoners alive for over 5 years . He was a deserter and a defector , not a prisoner .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402543017000">He happens to be in the way of their hate for the Pres.</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402549909000">He would n't help protect the opium</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402554121000">I went on a site on this topic but ca n't remember the name , If I 'll remember I will let you know .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402565787000">They do n't . Why do you Libs love him ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402570405000">He would n't help protect the opium</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402588889000">He happens to be in the way of their hate for the Pres.</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402589963000">Cons gon na hate bro ...</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402600186000">He would n't help protect the opium</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402611406000">So it 's not his fault he taught them badmitton and how to make bombs ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402612681000">They do n't . Why do you Libs love him ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402626085000">He would n't help protect the opium</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402626985000">he 's a deserter ... he should be hanged ...</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402633832000">They do n't . Why do you Libs love him ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402635810000">He would n't help protect the opium</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402636935000">he 's a deserter ... he should be hanged ...</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402639575000">He happens to be in the way of their hate for the Pres.</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402640950000">he 's a deserter ... he should be hanged ...</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402650880000">They do n't . Why do you Libs love him ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402651319000">They do n't . Why do you Libs love him ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402653838000">They do n't . Why do you Libs love him ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402655731000">Cons gon na hate bro ...</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402661598000">he 's a deserter ... he should be hanged ...</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402663550000">Cons gon na hate bro ...</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402668413000">They do n't . Why do you Libs love him ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402670148000">He happens to be in the way of their hate for the Pres.</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402672981000">They do n't . Why do you Libs love him ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402680848000">He would n't help protect the opium</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402681765000">He would n't help protect the opium</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402689305000">He happens to be in the way of their hate for the Pres.</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402690478000">Cons gon na hate bro ...</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402694567000">They do n't . Why do you Libs love him ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402713031000">Cons gon na hate bro ...</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402715772000">he 's a deserter ... he should be hanged ...</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402720618000">Because it reminds them of how Bush/PERSON failed in that war .</answer><suggestions>bush/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402723382000">Cons gon na hate bro ...</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402724800000">Cons gon na hate bro ...</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402725479000">He would n't help protect the opium</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402732715000">They do n't . Why do you Libs love him ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402741665000">he 's a deserter ... he should be hanged ...</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402743050000">He happens to be in the way of their hate for the Pres.</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402744227000">He happens to be in the way of their hate for the Pres.</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402749215000">he 's a deserter ... he should be hanged ...</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402765712000">he 's a deserter ... he should be hanged ...</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402779265000">He would n't help protect the opium</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402781585000">They do n't . Why do you Libs love him ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402784586000">He would n't help protect the opium</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402791206000">He happens to be in the way of their hate for the Pres.</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402791927000">Cons gon na hate bro ...</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402792671000">They do n't . Why do you Libs love him ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402795375000">They do n't . Why do you Libs love him ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402797181000">They do n't . Why do you Libs love him ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402804891000">Cons gon na hate bro ...</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402806836000">Cons gon na hate bro ...</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402808186000">He would n't help protect the opium</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402811821000">he 's a deserter ... he should be hanged ...</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402816057000">He happens to be in the way of their hate for the Pres.</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402817422000">he 's a deserter ... he should be hanged ...</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402818768000">he 's a deserter ... he should be hanged ...</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402820828000">Cons gon na hate bro ...</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402823233000">They do n't . Why do you Libs love him ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402823857000">He would n't help protect the opium</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402837169000">He would n't help protect the opium</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402837674000">They do n't . Why do you Libs love him ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402838259000">He would n't help protect the opium</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402841019000">They do n't . Why do you Libs love him ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402843959000">They do n't . Why do you Libs love him ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402845450000">he 's a deserter ... he should be hanged ...</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402854655000">They do n't . Why do you Libs love him ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402858120000">Because it reminds them of how Bush/PERSON failed in that war .</answer><suggestions>bush/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402860020000">They do n't . Why do you Libs love him ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402867929000">Cons gon na hate bro ...</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402876708000">He would n't help protect the opium</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402884522000">he 's a deserter ... he should be hanged ...</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402891486000">Cons gon na hate bro ...</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402892689000">he 's a deserter ... he should be hanged ...</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402899822000">He happens to be in the way of their hate for the Pres.</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402904668000">They do n't . Why do you Libs love him ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402907915000">He happens to be in the way of their hate for the Pres.</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402913596000">They do n't . Why do you Libs love him ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402914012000">Cons gon na hate bro ...</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402919051000">He would n't help protect the opium</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402923878000">He happens to be in the way of their hate for the Pres.</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402925287000">he 's a deserter ... he should be hanged ...</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402936165000">They do n't . Why do you Libs love him ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402940662000">Cons gon na hate bro ...</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402955956000">Because it reminds them of how Bush failed in that war .</answer><suggestions>bush/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402959953000">Cons gon na hate bro ...</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402967302000">he 's a deserter ... he should be hanged ...</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402988367000">They do n't . Why do you Libs love him ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402990753000">he 's a deserter ... he should be hanged ...</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402999031000">He would n't help protect the opium</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403008321000">They do n't . Why do you Libs love him ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403024042000">He would n't help protect the opium</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403038298000">He would n't help protect the opium</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403054467000">Cons gon na hate bro ...</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140605231104AAm8fzJ">
	<title>Can i sue ebay ? Im upset ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>Can i sue ebay because they restricted my account from selling on ebay forever because i ended up buying a gucci/ORGANIZATION belt off ebay/ORGANIZATION for $ 130 and it turned out fake the man refunded me and told me to keep the belt , so i posted it on ebay because i didnt want it and then ebay banned me from selling and banned my house address from making a new account on ebay . Heres the problem ... my brother also has a ebay account with 100 % positive feedback and has never gotten in trouble with ebay before ... they also banned his account because he has the same address as me . Thats because we live togather and i tried telling ebay/ORGANIZATION and they said sorry we cant do anything about it ... what should i do ? My brother is upset and its all my fault ... but he shouldnt get punished too ... AND i told them okay im done with ebay delete my account they said they cant delete my account ... whats the point of having my ebay account if i cant sell anymore all i can do is buy stuff but i dont wan na buy stuff because then ill be making EBAY/ORGANIZATION money not me . how much can we sue them for ? And how ?</content><suggestions>gucci/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402035370000">You 'd tried to sell counterfeit goods on eBay/ORGANIZATION , and you knew you were doing it . Heck , the guy you bought it from fully refunded you , and told you to keep it . He knew he could n't legally sell it . Soooo ... you then intentionally tried to scam somebody else ? You deserve to be banned . If you push it , eBay/ORGANIZATION might just turn you over to the police . Maybe your brother can make a new account when he moves and gets a place of his own . eBay wo n't delete any accounts -- they keep records of all transactions . You 're not suing anybody , but you might want to watch it before you get turned over to the police for intentionally trying to scam somebody with counterfeit goods .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402035748000">There 's got ta be more to this story , while the obvious answer is that you tried to sell known counterfeit goods , eBay does n't just ape-shti crazy on you and ban your entire ebay/ORGANIZATION existence without some dialogue in between . By the way - why did you try to sell a belt you knew was counterfeit ?</answer><suggestions>ebay/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402057004000">Sure you can sue if you want to waste a $ 10,000 retainer and the case is thrown out at the first hearing because you agreed NOT to sue eBay/ORGANIZATION in their terms of service . If anyone should sue anyone , your brother should sue YOU . If you have $ 10,00 for a lawyer to sue eBay , then you have $ 10,000 to reimburse your brother for lost sales .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140625082631AAcgyMl">
	<title>Are Republicans really that dumb to believe Darrell/PERSON Issa/PERSON 's lies or are they just going along with his bullsheet ?</title><suggestions>darrell/PERSON issa/PERSON</suggestions>
	<content>Pathological Liar Darrell/PERSON Issa/PERSON Ca n't Stop Spreading the Hillary/PERSON Clinton/PERSON Benghazi/LOCATION Lies http:\/\/www.politicususa.com\/2014\/03\/03\/pathological-liar-darrell-issa-stop-spreading-hillary-clinton-benghazi-stand-order-lie.html</content><suggestions>darrell/PERSON issa/PERSON hillary/PERSON clinton/PERSON benghazi/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>Darrell/PERSON Issa/PERSON 's 5 Biggest Lies About The IRS/ORGANIZATION ` Scandal ' http:\/\/www.nationalmemo.com\/darrell-issas-5-biggest-lies-about-the-irs-scandal\/</content><suggestions>darrell/PERSON issa/PERSON irs/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403710139000">Liberals biggest lie about IRS/ORGANIZATION scandal : It 's a Conservative scandal . The IRS/ORGANIZATION has openly admitted that it was targeting conservative groups . The IRS/ORGANIZATION made the announcement .</answer><suggestions>irs/ORGANIZATION irs/ORGANIZATION irs/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403710245000">Show me the emails that are missing and then I will give you an answer , but until them , the Obama/PERSON administration is looking guilty as sin .</answer><suggestions>obama/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403710337000">You Liberals need to stop visiting your koolaid stand Liberal websites . The IRS/ORGANIZATION has admitted that they targeted Conservative groups . Then they said it was isolated to a field office which was found to be a lie . Then they said they 'd turn over all of Learners emails , which was a lie . The IRS/ORGANIZATION is conducting one of the biggest cover-ups in history , and you Libs with your koolaid websites keep drinking up .</answer><suggestions>irs/ORGANIZATION irs/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403710609000">yup .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403710622000">They do n't believe this or anything else they say . It 's like a crack addict putting that pipe to his lips , making excuses for it - he knows it 's bad for him , he just does n't care .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403711289000">Most people put up with crap if it is crap that has their name on it . Conservatives are gutless when it comes to standing up for principles that criticize their own members . Democrats are not much better . If Obama/PERSON did half the treasonous junk , lying and damage that Bush/PERSON did to this country , I would turn on him in a flash and never have a good word to save about him again .</answer><suggestions>obama/PERSON bush/PERSON</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140613140428AASx2zV">
	<title>Does a minor go to court if shop lifting ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>Yesterday me and my friends went to Sears/ORGANIZATION and we were caught shoplifting . We are 17 and they told us to call our parents or they would call the police . I called my uncle and the security said they would send the fine to my house . After my uncle came , he signed a paper and they let me go home . Do I still have to Go to court ? I live in California/LOCATION .</content><suggestions>sears/ORGANIZATION california/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402694017000">Sounds like it 's a civil penalty . Your parents will get a letter from a law firm stating what happened , and that they must pay $ xx -LRB- will be much higher than the value of the item you tried to steal -RRB- . The letter will state that if the penalty is not paid by such date , they have the option to pursue criminal charges . If that happens , you will have to go to court , and you will have a criminal record follow you for many years .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402694683000">I guess this is a criminal matter punishable by a fine . Minors above the age of 10 , and sometimes 8 if established that he was aware of his acts and omissions at the time of commission of an offense , are criminally liable for their acts and omissions . so the age of seventeen is triable in a court of law like any other criminal . What your uncle sign appear to me to be police bond\/bail and therefore , if that is the case , it is never an excuse of not committing person of you to court as may be required .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402694825000">Yes</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403028145000">more specific please</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403586976000">The letter you 'll probably be getting is called Civil Demand , it 's how retailers get money back for merchandise loss , security fees , processing fees , etc. . IF the police were involved you 'll probably have to go to court .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140607125905AA2JtXv">
	<title>So Canada/LOCATION has only four submarines and . . ?</title><suggestions>canada/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>they have to cut them in half to change out an engine ? http:\/\/www.cbc.ca\/news\/canada\/nova-scotia\/submarine-hmcs-windsor-shore-bound-after-engine-failure-1.2524501 They must be counting on someone to come and save their Canadian Bacon . Any idea who that might be ? ; -RRB-</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402171215000">America/LOCATION .</answer><suggestions>america/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402171246000">Nobody hates Canada/LOCATION , they do n't need protection .</answer><suggestions>canada/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402171276000">Canada/LOCATION really should n't have a navy . All that ice is n't really good . Leave the protecting up to big brother America/LOCATION .</answer><suggestions>canada/LOCATION america/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402171299000">Canada/LOCATION is protected by its deadly Walrus/ORGANIZATION &/ORGANIZATION Narwahl/ORGANIZATION army/ORGANIZATION .</answer><suggestions>canada/LOCATION walrus/ORGANIZATION &/ORGANIZATION narwahl/ORGANIZATION army/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402171385000">Who would want to attack Canada/LOCATION ?</answer><suggestions>canada/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402171668000">Canada has America . And if America/LOCATION decides to go annex Canada/LOCATION , we ca n't stop them with a good military or not realistically .</answer><suggestions>canada/LOCATION america/LOCATION america/LOCATION canada/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402172109000">Do n't ignore the rest of the Canadian/ORGANIZATION Navy/ORGANIZATION , which consists of 2 kayaks and 1 canoe</answer><suggestions>canadian/LOCATION navy/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402172400000">Ah , nice to see our neigbors stirring up the bullshit again . With friends like you , who needs an enemy .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402177692000">Is n't it hilarious to see these people think war is about hatred . Even in view of Hitler/PERSON wanting to take over the world and Putin/PERSON just deciding he would annex Crimea and other parts of Ukraine/LOCATION . War with other nations is not like terrorism . It can be a desire to over throw a bad regime for new leadership for national security ... It can be about power , aggression , strategy , resources , and self defense . Germany/LOCATION tried to get Mexico/LOCATION to join them in the world war .</answer><suggestions>hitler/PERSON putin/PERSON crimea/LOCATION ukraine/LOCATION germany/LOCATION mexico/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402183441000">I suspect that Canada/LOCATION is not anticipating being attacked by sea anytime soon , so they have time . My National Security Adviser -LRB- yea , someone who knows but will not divulge classified info over an insecure phone line , especially to a rapscallion like myself even though he is my best friend -RRB- assures me that USA/LOCATION 's nuclear umbrella was designed and continues to function very well to cover defending Canada/LOCATION . All the average American hears about NORAD is when they are tracking Santa Clause . But in reality , trust me , USA/LOCATION knows where everything is and what 's going on . OK , sure , they ca n't track a major airliner made by Boeing because nobody told them to watch it . Ok , sure , they ca n't keep track of 20 million illegal aliens invading America . OK sure , they live under a mountain so of course there are no UFOs , only space junk which , trust me , they know where every nut and bolt traveling at 17 bagizzilion mph is as all that junk orbits earth because it 's a safety hazard . So NORAD would necessarily cover Canada as well because dem pesky Rooskies would have to shoot their ICBMs over the pole to get at US or Canada . So everything 's OK , right ? We , as usual , are always prepared to win the previous war and somehow everyone forgets that the bad guys will do something new . Oh , you know , like for example when Germany/LOCATION invented armored mobility and went through Belgium/LOCATION coming up behind the French Maginot line and those wonderful French had designed fields of fire such that they could n't turn the guns around to shoot behind them , which is where the German tanks were coming from . D'OH ! The only thing the French could do to slow down the Germans in 1940 was fill the street intersections with empty wine bottles and croissant rinds while sending bicycle messengers to HQ and by the time the bicycle guys got back to the front it had moved 20 miles , so that did n't turn out well . So trust me : Canada/LOCATION will be just fine until their 4 submarines are seaworthy .</answer><suggestions>canada/LOCATION usa/LOCATION canada/LOCATION norad/ORGANIZATION usa/LOCATION boeing/ORGANIZATION america/LOCATION canada/LOCATION dem/ORGANIZATION pesky/ORGANIZATION rooskies/ORGANIZATION canada/LOCATION germany/LOCATION belgium/LOCATION french/LOCATION canada/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402237177000">Canada is n't sovereign . It exists predicated on the disinterest of others to end it and on the will of the U.S. that it keep existing .</answer><suggestions>canada/LOCATION u.s./LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402328466000">try google it also</answer><suggestions>google/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140613132938AABdKy8">
	<title>Need Info on the Processing of Assault Charges in AZ ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I was assaulted yesterday , and the assailant was taken into custody on scene , along with video evidence and a written statement of the account . A few hours later , I received a phone call from our local PD that he was being released from jail . Does that mean that charges are not being pursued , that or is it just part of the process ? Because it was the city jail , I could find no record online with more info pertaining to the case</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402692752000">No that means that the person was released somehow , by bond or ror -LRB- released by his own recognizes -RRB- . With assault cases , most time is by either money or property bond . Once a person is out of jail it is no longer public information . You need to call the courts or DA office to see how the person was released and any conditions where attached tot he release as well . And next court\/hearing date , unless the cop gave you one already . The DA will press charges against the guy . Under many state statutory laws , the DA will press the charges even if the victim refuses or want to drop the assault charges . Normally , there is a no contact court order when a person up on those charges gets out on bond . Ask the cop or DA office if there is 1 or not . This means he should have no contact with you in any way shape or form -LRB- including via the social media -RRB- BUT , that means the same for you -- you can not have any type of contact with the person . If the person violates the no contact order , he forfeits the bond and will be sent back to jail . If you violate the court order , it is called contempt of court .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402895466000">I saw an article the other day about this , let me check my history real fast and I will get back with the link</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140609170145AAsvd80">
	<title>Does the capitalist system support & perpetuate racism & sexism in any harmful ways ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>JUST ANOTHER DARN CO-INCIDENCE that WHITE MALES STILL WORK THE REST OF US ??</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402358582000">yes it does</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402358622000">Not even a little bit .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402358666000">No . Capitalism is the pillar of Western civilization .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402358671000">Ahhh , 1 out of 6 people from India/LOCATION are millionaires . And dey be draker dan a mofo !</answer><suggestions>india/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402358717000">The liberals perpetuate racism & sexism in any harmful way they can . That is all part of their agenda to divide the country along racial lines .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402358748000">Look at the western world and compare it to the third world and tell me it does n't .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402358828000">No if anything it discourages it . Racist and sexist businesses exclude a huge part of their potential customer base and that would very much hurt them . If anything socialism has more potential for racism as a democratically controlled economy could deny resources to a minority or enslave them .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402358850000">I like to say that Capitalism has a caste system . The white rich are at the top and poor whites and minorities at the bottom . The rich white males rule the nation through buying politicians even while they are a minority and the poor and the racial minorities work for them at low wages . Of course women are also screwed as well .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402359096000">No , but Affirmative Action certainly does .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402359208000">It is staggering how little you know about capitalism . Capitalism is a system in which everyone is rewarded based on their own merits . For instance it you have an amazing idea and you take the initiative to put it into action , it could make you wealthy and famous . Capitalism is an extension of liberty , aka freedom . If a company , for instance , promotes racist ideology in a capitalist society , the people simply stop shopping there if they disagree with that ideology . eventually as no one shops at that retailer anymore , they go away . There are no bailouts in a capitalist system , You either make a product that people want , and manage your money properly , or you fail . if we were actually capitalist , GM would not still be here . Simple as that . Capitalism is the single greatest force for freedom in the entire world , it is a system in which everyone has an equal chance to make it . the system we have now , is anything but capitalism . You could argue that it is crony capitalism . but even then . . not really .</answer><suggestions>gm/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402359335000">Is this what theyre teaching in Liberal Arts in College ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140619072135AAeFu7N">
	<title>I Want An Australian Passport ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>My dad was born in Connecticut . My grandmother was born in the Isle of Man . Isle of Man is a property of the United/LOCATION Kingdom/LOCATION . Australia/LOCATION being a commonwealth is there a immigration legal loophole where it allows me to obtain a citizenship in Australia/LOCATION ?</content><suggestions>connecticut/LOCATION united/LOCATION kingdom/LOCATION australia/LOCATION commonwealth/ORGANIZATION australia/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403187913000">no chance whatsoever you CANNIOT EVEN GET A BRIT ONE http:\/\/en.wikipedia.org\/wiki\/Australian_nationality_law</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403188017000">What about you ?? : Where are you right now ?? How old are you ?? For much time have you lived in the place you 're right now ?? Where you lived earlier ??</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403190828000">isle of man is british dependent but not U.K/LOCATION , so no passport from U.K ... ... ... ... ... ... ... and not from Australia/LOCATION either ... ... ... ... ... ... . .</answer><suggestions>australia/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403191528000">You want an Australian passport ! You and half a million others each year ! Having a British passport does NOT give you a loop hole into getting into Australian . Otherwise most of British would already be living there You apply , like everyone else , and hope that you meet the requirements that they are looking for</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403191948000">No way . Unless your other parent was a citizen of Australia/LOCATION at the time of your birth , and properly registered birth to Australian citizen while abroad with Australian consulate & got your Aussie passport when you were born , you have no rights to Australian citizenship . You do n't even have any rights to any visa there . You will have to qualify for immigration , if you can meet requirements .</answer><suggestions>australia/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403192333000">You can not even get one from the UK/LOCATION</answer><suggestions>uk/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403192434000">A lot of the old Commonwealth rules no longer apply . Likewise unless your US born father obtained and maintained UK/LOCATION citizenship for the purposes of passing it on to you it 's unlikely you 'd even be eligible for a UK/LOCATION passport let alone an Australian one .</answer><suggestions>uk/LOCATION uk/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403201067000">The commonwealth means nothing to the average person anymore . The UK takes and gives more immigration rights through the EU and as such all commonwealth immigration rights of UK citizens have been demolished . You have to qualify for immigration to Australia just like an Iranian citizen does</answer><suggestions>uk/LOCATION eu/ORGANIZATION commonwealth/ORGANIZATION immigration/ORGANIZATION rights/ORGANIZATION of/ORGANIZATION uk/ORGANIZATION australia/LOCATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140601094337AAbsB6Z">
	<title>3 Government multiple choice questions !? Please help !?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>1 -RRB- what is a tax return ? A. a form that shows how much tax a person must pay B. money kept back from a workers paycheck for taxes C. a tax paid by someone other than the person taxed D. money returned to taxpayers who paid too much in taxes __________________________________________________ 2 -RRB- a deficit is A. the money paid for the use of a loan B. the amount the government spends that exceeds its income C. a plan for income and expenses D. money in the federal budget that has not been spent __________________________________________________ 3 -RRB- What is the public debt ? A. borrowed money B. the amount the government spends that exceeds its income C. the total amount of money owed by an Americans in income taxes D. the total amount of money owed by the federal government</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401641504000">1 . A 2 B 3 . d</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140606032555AA8mCFY">
	<title>is it true the italian/ORGANIZATION american/ORGANIZATION mafia/ORGANIZATION applied street tax to other criminal groups ?</title><suggestions>mafia/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<content>i read online that the italian american mafia was applying street tax to crime groups is this true ?</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402052298000">Yes , it is but , it does n't happen anymore .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402059215000">When the Mafia ran crime in some major cities then they did charge small time crooks even those in their gangs a tax or tribute to stay in business . This tribute was claimed to be showing respect , but it was just like a franchise tax to do crime in their areas . In other words you had to have their permission to have any criminal activity inside their area of control .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402082335000">At one time the mafia did charge a street tax for others who wanted to operate in their areas of control . Now a days street gangs do the same thing . You are un affiliated and want to sell dope in BGD territory you paid off the BGD leadership for the right to sell dope in their area of control . If you are affiliated with another gang you start a gang war to gain control of the area you want to sell dope in . Just like the Italian and Irish organized crime families fights described in TV shows like the Untouchables .</answer><suggestions>un/ORGANIZATION italian/LOCATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140617193722AA5emAo">
	<title>Is it starting to look like Lois/PERSON Lerner/PERSON 's emails will trace back directly to the Obama White House ?</title><suggestions>lois/PERSON lerner/PERSON obama/PERSON</suggestions>
	<content>Is n't nice to know we can always count on ` factsenragerightwingers ' for MSNBC/ORGANIZATION 's talking points ? LOL</content><suggestions>msnbc/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<content>Mike/PERSON - just the fact they 've mysteriously been ` lost ' is good enough for me .</content><suggestions>mike/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403059144000">Only if the administration can not successfully cover that up .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403059196000">Nope . That 's just another crazy right-wing conspiracy fantasy .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403059202000">Yes ... I find it odd they want to be in charge of Americans health care as inept as they are .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403059208000">What emails ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403059377000">No . You 're living in a dream world of conspiracies .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403059395000">It certainly is looking that way . We already have plenty of evidence of the IRS ' wrongdoing and the involvement of Democratic congressmen like Elijah/PERSON Cummings/PERSON , Carl/PERSON Levin/PERSON , and Sheldon/PERSON Whitehouse/PERSON . Why go through the trouble of keeping those incriminating emails hidden if they do n't implicate top cabinet officials or Obama/PERSON himself ?</answer><suggestions>irs/ORGANIZATION elijah/PERSON cummings/PERSON carl/PERSON levin/PERSON sheldon/PERSON whitehouse/PERSON obama/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403059403000">Okay , but you need proof first and the investigation does n't have it yet . Key word there - yet .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403059514000">Sharyl/PERSON Attkisson/PERSON has a list of questions that nee to be asked pertaining to this subject : In light of the disclosure , these are some of the logical requests that should be made of the IRS : Please provide a timeline of the crash and documentation covering when it was first discovered and by whom ; when , how and by whom it was learned that materials were lost ; the official documentation reporting the crash and federal data loss ; documentation reflecting all attempts to recover the materials ; and the remediation records documenting the fix . This material should include the names of all officials and technicians involved , as well as all internal communications about the matter . Please provide all documents and emails that refer to the crash from the time that it happened through the IRS/ORGANIZATION ' disclosure to Congress Friday that it had occurred . Please provide the documents that show the computer crash and lost data were appropriately reported to the required entities including any contractor servicing the IRS/ORGANIZATION . If the incident was not reported , please explain why . Please provide a list summarizing what other data was irretrievably lost in the computer crash . If the loss involved any personal data , was the loss disclosed to those impacted ? If not , why ? Please provide documentation reflecting any security analyses done to assess the impact of the crash and lost materials . If such analyses were not performed , why not ? Please provide documentation showing the steps taken to recover the material , and the names of all technicians who attempted the recovery . Please explain why redundancies required for federal systems were either not used or were not effective in restoring the lost materials , and provide documentation showing how this shortfall has been remediated . Please provide any documents reflecting an investigation into how the crash resulted in the irretrievable loss of federal data and what factors were found to be responsible for the existence of this situation . I would also ask for those who discovered and reported the crash to testify under oath , as well as any officials who reported the materials as having been irretrievably lost .</answer><suggestions>sharyl/PERSON attkisson/PERSON irs/ORGANIZATION congress/ORGANIZATION irs/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403059540000">They were probably from Valerie/PERSON Jarrett/PERSON 's computer to Lois/PERSON ' Outlook Express account . They got `` lost '' in the ethernet .</answer><suggestions>valerie/PERSON jarrett/PERSON lois/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403060115000">Is n't it odd that even the backup servers went down precisely with her and 6 others computers ? and America still fumes over Nixon 's ; lost 18 minutes .</answer><suggestions>america/LOCATION nixon/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403060781000">What emails , there are no emails . Poor Issa has subpoenaed a hard drive . Clearly , Issa is attempting to take the focus off of Benghazi/LOCATION now that Abu/PERSON Khattala/PERSON has been captured and charged with the Benghazi/LOCATION attack .</answer><suggestions>issa/PERSON issa/PERSON benghazi/LOCATION abu/PERSON khattala/PERSON benghazi/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403075018000">No , it does not .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140609182413AATpjOA">
	<title>If immigration reform does not pass , will the GOP be affected in the 2014 Midterm Elections ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>Explain why or why not ? They did amnesty in the 1980s and it did n't work well for them .</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402363605000">No ... we already have an immigration policy , , , obama/PERSON ignores those laws but we have them</answer><suggestions>obama/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402363752000">Intelligent voters understand that amnesty has not stopped illegals from entering border states . We need high walls protected by lots of guns . Keeping illegals out will allow our economy to prosper .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402363951000">Immigration reform is just one of many controversial issues that the Republicans have handed Obama/PERSON . The Repubs ' first priority is to oppose Obama/PERSON , so when they find themselves on the same side on an issue they change sides . So all Obama/PERSON has to do is to take the popular side of an issue and you can count on the Republicans embracing the losing side . EVERY president since Reagan/PERSON has wanted to do immigration reform . Reagan/PERSON was the last president who gave illegals amnesty and GW/PERSON Bush/PERSON was the last president that tried and failed to do it again . A goodly majority of Americans across the country favor immigration reform , so yes , it might have an effect on this year 's elections . And it might be a major issue in 2016 .</answer><suggestions>obama/PERSON obama/PERSON obama/PERSON reagan/PERSON reagan/PERSON gw/PERSON bush/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402364573000">Regan/PERSON was duped by the Democrats , he agreed to an amnesty bill in exchange for a more secure border , the amnesty happened , but the border security that the Democrats promised , never happened . This is why , if you listen to the debate between Republicans and Democrats , the Republicans refuse to fall for that move again ! They want the border secured BEFORE any deal on amnesty .</answer><suggestions>regan/PERSON democrats/ORGANIZATION democrats/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140622031654AAtTkJT">
	<title>Why is there a system of minority supremacy in the west ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>Let me guess the jews had nothing to do with that either .</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403433041000">but if u want to earn money for free go to http:\/\/www.probux.com\/?r=augustrush996 work hard for few months and u will earn a lot all u have to do is watch ads patience is the key i m using it to purchase ps4 after 3 months of hard work -LRB- this answer is just for information , do not report the answer -RRB-</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403434417000">omg , please jog on . You LOST WW2 , just accept we have move don form your 14th century attitude .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403436095000">What are you talking about ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403439986000">Have you ever been to the west coast ? It 's nothing but white hipsters for god 's sake !</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403442026000">You 've got to stop huffing glue out of paper bags .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140614172231AAsQkBF">
	<title>Paul/PERSON why do n't alot ur puta team ?</title><suggestions>paul/PERSON</suggestions>
	<content>have block buttons ?</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402791808000">The yahoo/ORGANIZATION monitors are the first trolls and the majority of the trolls . THERE IS NO REPORTING.The SOBs just want U to think there is . This SOBs delete at will . This YAT PUTAs walk quietly and carry a big delete tool . phFVCK U paul Taylor and Ur YAT PUTAs . Now U know why they hate me . lord mando has spoken . My posts are DELETED as soon as they are posted most of the time . The yahoo/ORGANIZATION answers/ORGANIZATION Team -LRB- YAT -RRB- are doing the deleting under the direction of Paul/PERSON Taylor/PERSON .</answer><suggestions>yahoo/ORGANIZATION phfvck/PERSON paul/PERSON taylor/PERSON mando/PERSON yahoo/ORGANIZATION paul/PERSON taylor/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402792036000">.</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140623142217AAHjEJM">
	<title>Rent Problems  Emergency !! Please help !!?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>A month ago , my mom and I found a room for rent in Hicksville/LOCATION , NY . The landlord was a Chinese lady . Since it just one room , we asked her if both me and my mom can live in the same room , she said yes , but we have to pay an extra hundred for the rent since we have an additional person . So we add an extra hundred , the rent was $ 700a month and we raised it to $ 800a month . And then , we asked her if we can move in in July , and she said yes eventually . So she asked us for a $ 800 security deposit in advance , and agrees that we can move in at the end of June . But right now , she refuses to rent us the room , we did not sign contract , but she gave us a receipt for the security deposit . Are we allowed to sue the landlord ? Or can we get a double back for the security we paid since she broke the lease ? -LRB- well , not really -RRB- if I can sue her , should I call 911 ? Thank you for your help !</content><suggestions>hicksville/LOCATION ny/LOCATION chinese/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403558801000">Call the housing authority in your area to file a complaint . If they can not help , then you need to sue .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403560207000">She wont rent you the room at all , or she wants to wait till July to do so ? I dont understand your question . Since you said she was chinese , I assume that she barely spoke english , otherwise why mention it , and maybe there was some misunderstanding , You cant call 911 , its a civil matter , not criminal . You didnt sign a lease , athough I cant image why she wouldnt rent it , most landlords want paying customers .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140603004555AAv1K5X">
	<title>Do you think steve/PERSON balmer/PERSON is gon na move the clippers to seattle ?</title><suggestions>steve/PERSON balmer/PERSON clippers/ORGANIZATION seattle/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>the man lives in seattle la is still kobe country even if the clips were good the past couple of years</content><suggestions>seattle/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401781691000">I have n't even considered the issue . I Do n't Care</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401781857000">Not a chance</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401785384000">He 's not going to move the team . Ballmer/PERSON said this to the Wall/ORGANIZATION Street/ORGANIZATION Journal/ORGANIZATION : `` If I get interested in the Clippers , it would be for Los/LOCATION Angeles/LOCATION , '' Ballmer/PERSON said . `` I do n't work anymore , so I have more geographic flexibility than I did a year , year-and-a half ago . Moving them anywhere else would be value destructive . ''</answer><suggestions>ballmer/PERSON los/LOCATION angeles/LOCATION ballmer/PERSON</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140619203951AAsYSB5">
	<title>I 'm 13 and the girl I asked a nude for and was talking dirty with is 13-14 . she called the cops on me 3 weeks ago . what should I do . were ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>both minors and I have a long life ahead</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403235690000">Talk with your parents about this , they are going to find out when the cops come to talk with you . It would be better if they heard it from you . Start with your father , and let him tell your mother .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403235835000">You 're going to have a good talking to . There 's no sexual assault or child porn or stat rape here , but you 're acting in a way that 's next , so time to learn the lesson from all this NOW .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403236200000">it is illegal for minors to posses child porn .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140613162326AARvh60">
	<title>Would Hillary/PERSON Clinton/PERSON always be drunk on duty ?</title><suggestions>hillary/PERSON clinton/PERSON</suggestions>
	<content>http:\/\/d2tq98mqfjyz2l.cloudfront.net\/image_cache\/1351520890895339.jpg</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402701928000">I think she would pass out a lot , which would be better than making a sh!tty decision about something .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402701957000">kffe</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402701989000">No , she will not emulate you . .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402702068000">She will make Boris/PERSON Yeltsin/PERSON go `` damn ! ''</answer><suggestions>boris/PERSON yeltsin/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402702153000">Yes</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402702156000">She was unavailable when Ambassador Stevens/PERSON was murdered .</answer><suggestions>stevens/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402702220000">We will see when she gets electetd</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402702673000">'' what difference does it make ? ''</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402702687000">no more than bush/PERSON was boozed and coked up .</answer><suggestions>bush/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402704548000">Get used to saying President Clinton/PERSON again .</answer><suggestions>clinton/PERSON</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140617203723AAnMv8x">
	<title>What other countries is Obama/PERSON going to hand over to groups that dont care about freedom or human rights ?</title><suggestions>obama/PERSON</suggestions>
	<content>Hes handing over Iraq/LOCATION to the ISIS/ORGANIZATION and hes about to hand Afganistan/LOCATION back to the Taliban .</content><suggestions>hes/ORGANIZATION iraq/LOCATION isis/ORGANIZATION hes/ORGANIZATION afganistan/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403062706000">Nope . Bush handed Iraq/LOCATION over to the extremists when he started his unwinnable war based on lies .</answer><suggestions>bush/PERSON iraq/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403062724000">well he gave Egypt/LOCATION to the muslim/ORGANIZATION brotherhood/ORGANIZATION but got mad when the Egyptians fired them he is handing usa to the socialists</answer><suggestions>egypt/LOCATION muslim/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403062758000">Texas/LOCATION , they would fit right in to the indigenous population .</answer><suggestions>texas/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403062964000">oh look , a con trying to sound like he actually cares about an iraqi .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403063140000">Lol All this idiocy . These ridiculous accusations engender the kind of radicalism which sends U.S. politics to hell . Give it a rest ... If you think Obama/PERSON is trying to do harm , then you are a fool .</answer><suggestions>u.s./LOCATION obama/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403063281000">You do n't even know what continent Iraq/LOCATION is on or what non-Arabic country borders it . You do n't know that it was Reagan/PERSON who sold Saddam the gas he used on the Kurds in 1988 . You do n't know that every non-partisan Middle/LOCATION East/LOCATION expert in the world predicted this would happen if Bush/PERSON invaded Iraq/LOCATION - including Bush/PERSON 's own father in his 1998 book ' A World Transformed ' - which you never read because you 're a moron - so STFU nitwit .</answer><suggestions>iraq/LOCATION reagan/PERSON saddam/PERSON middle/LOCATION east/LOCATION bush/PERSON iraq/LOCATION bush/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403063839000">The Taliban ruled Afghanistan before the US was involved there . The Iraqi people and the Afghani people never had a say in their governments until now , even though it is imperfect by any standard . The last king of Afghanistan , buried a few years ago in Kabul :</answer><suggestions>taliban/ORGANIZATION afghanistan/LOCATION us/LOCATION iraqi/LOCATION afghanistan/LOCATION kabul/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403064932000">Whom do you think he 's turned America over to ? He does refer to his term in office as `` my government '' . A first for any POTUS . As thousands of illegals flood into Texas . Then get shipped around our nation .</answer><suggestions>america/LOCATION texas/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403065504000">What did Bush do when Russia invaded Georgia ? A. Nothing . What did Reagan do when terrorists bombed the Marine barrack killing 300 ? A. Nothing .</answer><suggestions>bush/PERSON russia/LOCATION georgia/LOCATION reagan/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403118591000">It amazes me the arrogance of some people , not to mention the hypocrissy . Barry trying to force his will on America is bad , trying to force it on other countries is good ? FYI Barry was elected POTUS not POTW .</answer><suggestions>barry/PERSON america/LOCATION barry/PERSON</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140614170630AA1o9BQ">
	<title>Has Obama/PERSON improved our image abroad ?</title><suggestions>obama/PERSON</suggestions>
	<content>Syria/LOCATION Venezuela/LOCATION Egypt/LOCATION Libya/LOCATION Iraq/LOCATION Sudan/LOCATION Russia/LOCATION Mexico/LOCATION , Brazil/LOCATION , France/LOCATION , Spain/LOCATION , and Germany/LOCATION spying scandals .</content><suggestions>syria/LOCATION venezuela/LOCATION egypt/LOCATION libya/LOCATION iraq/LOCATION sudan/LOCATION russia/LOCATION mexico/LOCATION brazil/LOCATION france/LOCATION spain/LOCATION germany/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402790845000">Yea</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402790865000">He has yet to do a thing to make us look good in anything . All of that most certainly did not help .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402790868000">To answer your question ; Only if your a radical Muslim , and a believer of Sharia Law</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402791011000">The democrat made us look even more imperialistic , totalitarian , and dystopian .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402791105000">Yes everyone third world blighted Ghetto nation thinks we are pushovers and are here for the taking .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402791143000">He sure has he has n't illegally invaded any of their countries so only deluded people who have no idea of the bad taste Bush/PERSON left in the worlds mouth would think different</answer><suggestions>bush/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402791185000">IMO he has done little to help us look better on the world 's stage</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402791459000">From a french person 's opinion : You would have elected a sausage , it would make our opinion about your country -LRB- as a politial entity -RRB- much better than what it was with Bush/PERSON . Obama/PERSON has an excellent reputation here . Of course there were the spying scandals , but it was Bush who initiated it . It doesn not make Obama innocent , but anything looks innocent compared to Bush .</answer><suggestions>bush/PERSON obama/PERSON bush/PERSON obama/PERSON bush/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402791564000">You are right . He 's just an uneducated flunky carrying out the NWO agenda to trash everything so the banksters can buy up everything for pennies on the dollar . Remember that Clinton did away with our industrial base with NAFTA/ORGANIZATION and the legal protections from the raiders of Wall Street . Bush continued this and upped the ante with the world 's biggest bank robbery of all time : 911 , in which over a $ billion each in gold , platinum , diamonds , bearer bonds , etc. all disappeared and the buildings were demolished with small nukes and thermite to cover up the theft ... and of course to roll out the Stasi security state . The US/ORGANIZATION corporate/ORGANIZATION government/ORGANIZATION 's habits of using military force to maintain dollar hegemony is going away . Backing our currency with foreign oil is n't working any more ... most of the Libyan and Saudi oilfields are pumping mostly water . That is why the banksters are using proxies\/mercenaries to overthrow governments so they can be looted . The US dollar as reserve currency is DEAD and the rest of the world is taking action to trade outside the dollar ... including their own version of the SWIFT/ORGANIZATION trade settlement system and so many countries buying gold and silver tons at a time ... which they are already using in trade and eventually to back their currencies . In fact , Russia in association with Turkey/LOCATION and Kazakhstan/LOCATION are rolling out their own gold backed currency . Turkey was the broker in the deal wherein India paid Iran/LOCATION for their oil with gold ... so there is the precedent . Remember Cyprus/LOCATION ? The bank runs ? Russia/LOCATION was using Cyprus/LOCATION as the clearing house in their gold purchases ! All wars are banker wars . Al/ORGANIZATION Qaida/ORGANIZATION is run by the CIA/ORGANIZATION , and the Muslim/ORGANIZATION Brotherhood/ORGANIZATION is run by British MI6 .</answer><suggestions>nwo/ORGANIZATION clinton/PERSON nafta/ORGANIZATION bush/PERSON stasi/ORGANIZATION us/LOCATION us/LOCATION russia/LOCATION turkey/LOCATION kazakhstan/LOCATION turkey/LOCATION india/LOCATION iran/LOCATION cyprus/LOCATION russia/LOCATION cyprus/LOCATION cia/ORGANIZATION muslim/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402791573000">He is much more liked abroad , by the public , than any Republican President since Eisenhower .</answer><suggestions>republican/ORGANIZATION eisenhower/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402791890000">It could not be worse than this . https:\/\/www.youtube.com\/watch?v=zFFfWSpwlok&hd=1</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402792890000">He sure has , countries like Russia/LOCATION and Iran/LOCATION are beginning to like us but then countries like France/LOCATION and Germany/LOCATION and Israel/LOCATION , France/LOCATION and England/LOCATION are becoming suspicious of us but the Palestinians are warming to us . He 's doing a great job .</answer><suggestions>russia/LOCATION iran/LOCATION france/LOCATION germany/LOCATION israel/LOCATION france/LOCATION england/LOCATION palestinians/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402793100000">Yes he has . When Presidents reduce the degree of competitiveness of the country , they increase their popularity with other countries . Either we compete or we are liked . Those are our choices . President Obama has chosen for us .</answer><suggestions>obama/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402896063000">If Israel/LOCATION attacks Syria/LOCATION and Iran/LOCATION -LRB- because of gas -RRB- It 's over for whole world.To avoid the war they are going to cut the gas deal with Russia/LOCATION to take over the regine as much at stake.The deal will include to protect Israel/LOCATION . !!!! So Obama knows that Russia will fight for Iraq to the end .</answer><suggestions>israel/LOCATION syria/LOCATION iran/LOCATION russia/LOCATION israel/LOCATION obama/PERSON russia/LOCATION iraq/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402916052000">NO ! As for Arab people , they still hate USA as how they were ! , they hate the American government not the American people . = D</answer><suggestions>usa/LOCATION american/LOCATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140601064930AA0dvez">
	<title>What is being an Artillery Soldier in the CF like ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>What is it like being a Artillery soldier ? What do you do when you are deployed ? Would you have to do non artillery things like do patrolling instead ?</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401635527000">http:\/\/www.forces.ca\/en\/job\/artillerysoldier-2</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140608113007AAoVpt8">
	<title>Is yahoo/ORGANIZATION biased in Politics & Government , It seems they Block Political Questions asked by conservative groups ?</title><suggestions>yahoo/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<content>Some of you did n't understand the question , I thought it was simple to Understand , I did n't say anything about anyone Reporting My Questions , or any of my questions being deleted by the left yahoo/ORGANIZATION users , The Key Word here Was Block . None of you can Block someone 's question , Now do you Get it ?</content><suggestions>yahoo/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<content>Daddy-O , What is with the Name calling , Im not here calling you names or making any derogatory remarks .</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402252316000">yes , it is a private company located in Liberal CA . seems obvious to me .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402252335000">No , Yahoo/ORGANIZATION Answers/ORGANIZATION is just buggy . Liberal questions are blocked as well .</answer><suggestions>yahoo/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402252339000">some leftist had to have reported you , focus your anger there .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402252374000">How would you know if they were blocking questions from liberal groups , too ? I see lots of questions from conservatives , so it does n't `` seem '' like Yahoo/ORGANIZATION ! is biased toward the liberals .</answer><suggestions>yahoo/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402252375000">No . It 's just your right-wing paranoia and delusions of persecution . You people live inside a bubble of lies and mental disease . p.s. : Conservative trolls routinely violate the TOS , but they do n't get deleted . I have had many perfectly legitimate questions and answers deleted because I dared to confront right-wing nuts with actual facts .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402252393000">No Questions get deleted because people report . If you notice more right wing questions getting deleted it 's because they are asking more often . Some questions do n't post ... that 's a YA glitch . I wait 5 or 10 minutes . If I do n't see my q on the front page , I delete and ask again .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402252415000">Yep , I can never get an anti-abortion question to post .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402252447000">The company itself does n't give a hoot what you say . If someone 's question or answer is deleted , a few individual users have reported it . It is automatically deleted by bots .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402252686000">yes they are extremely biased</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402253695000">I suspect that YAHOO/ORGANIZATION is progressive left leaning . However , most questions and answers that are deleted are in fact violations of the abuse policy against personal insults , name calling because someone does n't agree with your ideology , and chatting off topic postings . Those that are deleted and were NOT violations are mostly the victims of self styled ideology report monkeys who feel that they are entitled to suppress all postings that are in opposition to their beliefs . I have actually seen calls to all progressives to report app conservative postings with the objective to have their accounts suspended . .</answer><suggestions>yahoo/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402253756000">and liberals block us from answering question !!! right summertime ? just how anti American is that !!!!</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140611151627AAmAEbQ">
	<title>Do n't you hate people who do n't support the troops and the wars ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I think they 're ungrateful cowards and they should go live in Norway/LOCATION or Italy/LOCATION or Sudan/LOCATION or one of those other hellhole socialist countries !!!!</content><suggestions>norway/LOCATION italy/LOCATION sudan/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402525025000">yes , I agree .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402525033000">I do n't hate them , sometimes the arguments against conflicts are helpful .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402525076000">Why would you support the wars our president creates ? I support the troops who are fighting in them , but to the people who cause them my answer is no .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402525100000">I think everyone should support the troops , but not necessary all wars . For example , I thought the second Iraq/LOCATION war was premature , but the Afghanistan/LOCATION war was appropriate .</answer><suggestions>iraq/LOCATION afghanistan/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402525122000">I support the troops , my brother is in the army . I just do n't support risking his life on wars that are n't necessary for our national security . I do n't believe the Iraq/LOCATION and Afghanistan/LOCATION war were necessary for our national security , and probably hurt it more than helped it in the end . Seeing as we created more terrorist than we killed probably .</answer><suggestions>iraq/LOCATION afghanistan/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402525165000">Supporting the troops is n't the same as supporting the wars they go into . One is a group of people thrown into a bad situation , and the other is a bad situation .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402525203000">US\/NATO Troops Patrolling Opium Poppy Fields in Afghanistan https:\/\/publicintelligence.net\/usnato-troops-patrolling-opium-poppy-fields-in-afghanistan\/ Afghan Opium Production Increased 40 Times Since NATO , US Invasion http:\/\/www.mintpressnews.com\/afghan-opium-production-increased-40-times-since-nato-us-invasion\/57053\/ Banks Launder Billions of Illegal Cartel Money While Snubbing Legal Marijuana Businesses http:\/\/www.huffingtonpost.com\/avinash-tharoor\/banks-cartel-money-laundering_b_4619464.html</answer><suggestions>afghanistan/LOCATION nato/ORGANIZATION us/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402525316000">No . We are not automatons . Everybody is not exactly the same . Some can support the troops and not support wars . Remember how fantastically they perform when there is a natural disaster ! Look at that the army/ORGANIZATION corps/ORGANIZATION of/ORGANIZATION engineers/ORGANIZATION work with bridges and levee systems !</answer><suggestions>army/ORGANIZATION corps/ORGANIZATION of/ORGANIZATION engineers/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402525443000">Do mean like Dick/PERSON Cheney/PERSON , Ted/PERSON Nugent/PERSON , Mitt/PERSON Romney/PERSON , George/PERSON Bush/PERSON , Rush/PERSON Limbaugh/PERSON , Newt/PERSON Gingrich/PERSON ? Not supporting troops is one thing , but being a draft dodging bastard when you had the chance to fight for your country is a thousand times worse !!! That is what you call a coward !!! There is nothing more despicable than a right wing chicken Hawk !!!!!!!</answer><suggestions>dick/PERSON cheney/PERSON ted/PERSON nugent/PERSON mitt/PERSON romney/PERSON george/PERSON bush/PERSON rush/PERSON limbaugh/PERSON newt/PERSON gingrich/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402525628000">damn libruls !</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402525884000">I don ` t hate them as they are entitled to their own opinions .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402526765000">The German people supported their troops during World War 2 . Were they right ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140605183929AAMoGA3">
	<title>What are the 3 main goals of Pierre/PERSON Trudeau/PERSON ?</title><suggestions>pierre/PERSON trudeau/PERSON</suggestions>
	<content>This is for my Grade 10 History project . I ca n't find the answer on the Internet . Answers are greatly appreciated !!!</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402506469000">And preach as you go , saying , ` The kingdom of heaven is at hand . ' Heal the sick , raise the dead , cleanse lepers , cast out demons . You received without paying , give without pay . Take no gold , nor silver , nor copper in your belts , no bag for your journey , nor two tunics , nor sandals , nor a staff ; for the laborer deserves his food . And whatever town or village you enter , find out who is worthy in it , and stay with him until you depart . As you enter the house , salute it . And if the house is worthy , let your peace come upon it ; but if it is not worthy , let your peace return to you .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>

