<question id="20140618003957AA2mrn7">
	<title>Will sulfur damage guitar strings ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I was playing my guitar the other day with new strings and I had a some sulfur on my hands . Now the guitar strings have turned a little black .</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403077487000">Definitely yes !!!</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403078097000">Yeah , it will . Did you pour it on your guitar ? Strings are cheap and replaced every month . Hopefully it was all that got Sulfur on it .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403087103000">Honestly , I do n't think it will do more than tarnish your strings . Strings are a replaceable commodity ... and should be changed every few months for optimum tone . If they still sound okay , then do n't worry about it . If they 're overdue for a change , this is the perfect opportunity . I hope you gave the guitar a good wipe-down , including the metal hardware .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403098069000">TommyMc/PERSON 's sensible answer is best . I 'd recommend going ahead and changing the strings - and thoroughly cleaning the fret board as well , 'cause you got some on there , too . Almost anything other than string lube will mess with the strings , at least in terms of them starting to rust , corrode , or getting a little dead . It 's always best to have clean hands before even picking the instrument up , whether you 've been eating & drinking , working on something else , or just sweating . Afterwards , always wipe down the guitar , too .</answer><suggestions>tommymc/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403105191000">Sulfur is very corrosive . So yes , it can damage strings . If all it did was tarnish them ... if they sound ok , just keep them until the next string change . Just wipe them down thoroughly every time you play ... sulfur or not . Sweat and finger oils are just as bad .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140608034752AAWHbyf">
	<title>am I the only one who finds tfios overrated ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I read tfios last year because a friend nagged me to do it . I normally get hooked on books within a few chapters , but not with this book . I got halfway through the book and then stopped reading . Im always sick of people talking about it on social medias I always use , and im even more annoyed when people start being rude because I dont like it . Am I the only one who dislikes it ?</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402225952000">OMG YES i think tfios is overrated 100 % !!!! I have FINALLY found someone who agrees with me ! tfios is one of my least favorite John/PERSON Green/PERSON books . I absolutely ADORED Will/PERSON Grayson/PERSON , Will/PERSON Grayson/PERSON though :D Looking For Alaska/LOCATION was pretty good too .</answer><suggestions>john/PERSON green/PERSON will/PERSON grayson/PERSON grayson/PERSON alaska/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402229596000">I agree too . I bought the book because a booktuber I watch recommended it , and I read it once . Thought it was decent . I put it down . Have not felt the compulsion to re-read it since . There are those books that you are excited to read again , that you play scenes out of in your head and need to rush to that part to satisfy some sort of thirst you have . But with TFIOS , I did n't have that . I was n't disappointed or surprised because when I bought it I was n't looking to be swept away . I do n't think it 's a bad book because I remember enjoying it , but it never stuck with me , and it IS overrated . It is not such a masterpiece , in my opinion , that it should have gathered the attention and following that it has . It honestly took me by surprise how popular the book had become . Personally , I feel that the book just fell too easily between several other books I was reading round that time , and had nothing in it to stand out . For this reason it irritates me when I am called out for being a ` prude ' because i 'm not all hyped up about the book . I 'm no prude . I enjoy YA . I just did n't particularly fawn over THIS book . So , you 're not alone : -RRB-</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402231871000">Same . I did n't like the writing style and i did n't feel emotional reading the end . I guess because John/PERSON Green/PERSON 's on tumblr and people love him they 're more inclined to like his books . Plus everyone loves a sad ending . Looking for Alaska/LOCATION was alright , but i do n't get the hype either .</answer><suggestions>john/PERSON green/PERSON alaska/LOCATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140612201710AACVW6f">
	<title>How do I write a quote over a photo ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I see many photos on FaceBook with text written over them . I want to do this . When people inquire how to place text over photos , I have read answers to the effect of `` Just use ms paint '' . Well , I 've looked at ms paint and I see no option to type text over a photo . Please clearly explain how to type the text , select the font , font size , color , and placement on the photo . Or if there is a way to do this using ms WORD please explain . Also , when I opened a photo in ms paint , it displayed much larger than the screen . How can I size it down so I can see what my finished product is going to look like ? Thanks .</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402629839000">Right click on the photo and select Open with -- > Paint . Click on `` A '' on the tool bar which is for text . Place the cursor where you wish to write . You may also paste anything by copying it from somewhere -LRB- CTRL C and CTRL V -RRB-</answer><suggestions>ctrl/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402756672000">Actually alot of apps do this easier .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140604082431AAFp8R0">
	<title>There 's a black dot when I 'm shooting video on my camera !!?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I have a Canon/ORGANIZATION 550 , and when I use the video mood there 's a black dot it 's only there when I shoot videos and it really ruins my videos , anyone can help me ? Btw I use a 50ml lens</content><suggestions>canon/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401899246000">Without seeing an example , I ca n't really provide much help ... You might have a `` dead pixel , '' but a single dead pixel would n't be very obvious or visible .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401899411000">This will be dust on your camera 's sensor . It shows up in images as it obscures light in that area from reaching the sensor and exposing the frames that make up the video . Go to a professional camera shop\/dealer and pay them to clean it . Should n't be too expensive , maybe $ 30-50 .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401900827000">It 's probably just gunk on your sensor - get it cleaned . To confirm if it is gunk , put your camera on Aperture priority mode , and take a still shot of an overcast sky with the aperture set to f\/22 If you can see it , then it 's gunk .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140618135311AATMAF9">
	<title>What 's your writing process ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I ask because my process is so time consuming : word vomit , re-edit , leave it alone for three days , re-edit again . I write online fiction , and once I publish a chapter I realize that it kinda sucks . So I have to go back in , take down the chapter , and re-edit again . Because of this , it takes me 3-4 weeks to completely publish a chapter and I feel bad because my readers have to wait on me . Should I try a beta reader ? How do I even find one ? Is it worth it ? Anyways , how does your writing process go ? Some tips would help .</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403124963000">Write the whole story and thoroughly edit it before you post any of it . Then you will be able to have on-time weekly or biweekly updates with well-written chapters .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403125321000">Every write has to find a method that suits them best . Some revise as they go , so plough on to the end , then go back to beginning and start again . For me , the process is never-ending . I can read a story of mine back for the fiftieth time , and still find changes I want to make .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403126346000">I 'm am a slow writer , even before you take into account all the re-editing and that buisness . That 's the way I work . I tend to write very small amounts every day and take my time doing so . As a result I ususally have something that I am happy with and do n't see the need for any immediate changes . Obviously I 'll go back and make edits eventually , but I 'll usually only do so once I 've written a fair bit more . I takes a lot of time , but I find that my edits do n't have to be quite so severe .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403155079000">Slow . :--LRB- It 's taken me two years to write this novel . My editor at my publishing house only took 11 days to accept it which is great , but then the earliest release date she can get for me is March . Meanwhile I know all these women pumping out six novels a year self publishing and making money . : - \/</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403207603000">Here are my simple rules that I live by . 1 -RRB- Never , never edit while you 're writing . 2 -RRB- Let the first draft suck . It will suck . Be proud of it if it sucks . Then go back and kill it . Revise , revise , revise . 3 -RRB- After each session of rewriting -LRB- after the first draft , of course -RRB- take a break and come back . 4 -RRB- Read . A lot . Every day . 5 -RRB- Glue your butt to the chair . If your writing 's boring to write , it 's boring to read . No exceptions . 6 -RRB- Write what YOU want to read . 7 -RRB- Be fearless in your writing . Write it if it sounds weird . Especially then .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140623100602AAeUxIh">
	<title>Why are alot of country songs about beer or drinking ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I am wondering why alot of country songs are about beer or drinking ! Examples - `` Drink in my Hand '' - by Eric/PERSON Church/PERSON , `` Drink a Beer '' - Luke/PERSON Bryan/PERSON , and `` Drink On It '' - by Blake/PERSON Shelton/PERSON . Please help me answer this question ... . Thank You</content><suggestions>eric/PERSON church/PERSON luke/PERSON bryan/PERSON blake/PERSON shelton/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403543261000">They like beer</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403543263000">Beer and love problems go hand in hand ...</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403543294000">Good question . It could be because country guys drink beer often -LRB- ? -RRB- ... . That is what makes country music country style ...</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403543575000">`` A lot '' is two words , idiot .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403549436000">You can always get a beer .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140606112307AAHpG1a">
	<title>Dance questions ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>Okay I feel so stupid for asking this question okay but what are those things called okay like pas de bouree -LRB- Potta boo ray -RRB- like not what is that but like there dance steps such as when you draw an D on the floor behind you and in front of you like not wjat is that called like what is the actual name if steps like that . Sorry if this is confusing</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402082083000">The name of the step when you draw a D on the floor is a rond de jambe I think that was what you were asking ... If not you can tell me and I 'll answer again : -RRB-</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402087007000">Ron de jamba</answer><suggestions>ron/PERSON de/PERSON jamba/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402088372000">Is this the D step ? https:\/\/www.youtube.com\/watch?v=rYVogYO3N5g It is called a rond de jambe . Pronounced `` Rawn -LRB- like yawn -RRB- duh zjahmb -LRB- it 's a bit confusing , but you know how the French pronounce their J 's ? That 's the zj part . -RRB- '' This is a pas de bouree , I 'm not sure why you brought it up -LRB- it was unclear -RRB- ; but if you wanted an example then here : https:\/\/www.youtube.com\/watch?v=iPm4ajDKL10 Do n't feel stupid ! I asked the same thing when I started .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140617074422AANUT7h">
	<title>Do you know of any good old school gothic horror authors ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I already know of and have read the works of Anne/PERSON Rice/PERSON , Poe/PERSON , Dante/PERSON , the bothers Grimm , John/PERSON Milton/PERSON , Goethe/PERSON , Shakespeare/PERSON , Horace/PERSON Walpole/PERSON , Mary/PERSON Shelley/PERSON , Stoker/PERSON , Radcliffe/PERSON , Marquise/PERSON de Sade/PERSON , Polidori/PERSON , and H.P./PERSON Lovecraft/PERSON . What are some other authors with admirable quality ? Thanks in advance .</content><suggestions>anne/PERSON rice/PERSON poe/PERSON dante/PERSON grimm/PERSON john/PERSON milton/PERSON goethe/PERSON shakespeare/PERSON horace/PERSON walpole/PERSON mary/PERSON shelley/PERSON stoker/PERSON radcliffe/PERSON marquise/PERSON de/PERSON sade/PERSON polidori/PERSON h.p./ORGANIZATION lovecraft/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403016905000">Daphne/PERSON DuMaurier/PERSON</answer><suggestions>daphne/PERSON dumaurier/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403020093000">Arthur/PERSON Machen/PERSON - much admired by Lovecraft/PERSON .</answer><suggestions>arthur/PERSON machen/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403026351000">Faye/PERSON Perozich/PERSON James/PERSON Hurst/PERSON Ludovico/PERSON Ariosto/PERSON Denis/PERSON Johnson/PERSON Gottfried/PERSON Keller/PERSON Euripides/PERSON Gilbert/PERSON White/PERSON William/PERSON J./PERSON Weatherby/PERSON Otto/PERSON Penzler/PERSON William/PERSON Beckford/PERSON Jean-Jacques/PERSON Rousseau/PERSON James/PERSON Malcolm/PERSON Rymer/PERSON Stephen/PERSON Jones/PERSON</answer><suggestions>faye/PERSON perozich/PERSON james/PERSON hurst/PERSON ludovico/PERSON ariosto/PERSON denis/PERSON johnson/PERSON gottfried/PERSON keller/PERSON gilbert/PERSON white/PERSON william/PERSON j./PERSON weatherby/PERSON otto/PERSON penzler/PERSON william/PERSON beckford/PERSON jean-jacques/PERSON rousseau/PERSON james/PERSON malcolm/PERSON rymer/PERSON stephen/PERSON jones/PERSON</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140622020047AAbc35x">
	<title>Help needed on choosing a Musical instrument ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I want an uncommon musical instrument that would be a serious instrument . I do n't really want too much Country and prefer it to be portable . All I can think of is Mandolin , Update : I also do n't really want Marching band stuff . Taking the ladies into</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403427773000">I say drums , definetly , but they arent very portable . Violins are pretty badass too though .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403443492000">Ok seriously . The criteria for choosing an instrument is whether or not you 'll get laid ?? If you 're serious about music , you 'll ignore the above `` advice '' . Good lord . I for one find mandolin and harmonica players sexy , if you all care for a girls opinion . But we all know you do n't : -RRB- That aside , I 'd go with mandolin . It 's very intricate , and not easy to learn , but it 's definitely unusual . Or you could go with the sitar and be extra bad-a $ $ lol Mandolins not easy to pick up because of such small frets and the number of strings . But it 's a beautiful instrument . I 'm not the biggest sax fan . I LOVE jazz -- it 's what I sing mostly . But sax players are usually a little ... scummy ? Lol . Beautiful sound though . I just ca n't imagine being seduced to Careless Whisper yet again ... ugh . Good luck with your music ! And the ladies I guess lol @Miles -- thank u !! Harmonica is very sensual ! . \*\*\* : D</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140616072209AARwehs">
	<title>What , in your opinion , makes a good male and\/or female character ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I was just curious as to what other people thought about what makes a character `` strong '' , in the sense of personality , not strength . I 've realized since i 've been writing that I 'm not that good at classifying this stuff , to be honest , and getting some elses opinion seems like a good idea . I 'm not sure if there 's really a difference in gender on what makes a strong character , so if you want to separate them or just give an idea in general , any help would be appreciated . Thanks : -RRB- -LRB- not sure if any of that made sense but -RRB-</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I had n't really known how to word my question very well -LRB- which is probably obvious haha -RRB- but yes I was asking what makes for a strong personality in a character and all of these answers are really helpful so thank you :-RRB- -LRB- and thanks for not being assholes about it like some of the other people on this site . That 's always a plus -RRB-</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402928650000">How do you define ` strong ' ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402929060000">I think a strength in a character , male or female , is the determination to do what is right , whether they want to or not , but also the strength to back down and show mercy . It takes a lot of courage and strength to stand down and show mercy , sometimes more than it takes to stand up and fight . I hope this made sense and helped ! Good luck !</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402929303000">What is strong ? Strength can be merely having the ability to push yourself out of poverty , or stand up for yourself against bullying , strength can be as simple as having the ability to let go of a friend , or to wipe away your tears . sIf you want to make a character `` strong '' it has to harmonize with their background . Did they live in an abusive home ? Did they live in a home where they got everything they wanted . If you want to make the character `` strong for option 2 . Then you would have to make them suffer material loss and find a way to live without what they had before , find out who their true friends would be and what they did for success , then they would have `` strength '' of determination . In summary , strength differs on background</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402929327000">Dear Sierra/PERSON - A strong character is consistent with some set of core values . In contrast , a weak character is driven by emotions and circumstances . A strong character sees his\/her life in a larger context - as part of something cosmic and significant . A weak character sees life as pointless . A strong character will take bold chances . A weak character will avoid risk .</answer><suggestions>sierra/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402929365000">A character who believes in who they are and what they do .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402931019000">Are you asking what makes for a `` strong '' character ? Or a character with a strong personality ? In any case , character flaws make for both . Good character flaws , namely . Character flaws make the characters and their goals and ambitions seem more realistic -LRB- since no one is perfect -RRB- , and they give the character something to fight against at a mental and emotional level . It makes their other traits much stronger , since they are made relative to the character 's weaker traits , and as a whole , it makes the character seem like a living being with a personality of their own . Yes , everyone knows that it is scary to fight against the big lord of darkness , but it is also interesting to see a character fight against himself , or herself ... or succumb to his or her own weaknesses or faults . Exemplary courage is a lot more interesting when the reader knows that behind such courage is a scared , and weak individual with flaws and ambitions of his or her own . Character flaws can be created to match your overall flow of the story . For example : A character fighting against the lord of evil may have an irrational fear of spiders . Sure enough , the lord of evil is a spider . A character fighting against the lord of evil is a severe alcoholic , and despite his or her victories against it , the fight forces him or her to sink further and further into alcoholism as the tides turn , or when loved ones are killed . Thus , giving something for the character to strive to fight against . ~ I am referring to the `` lord of evil , '' but it could be anything negative . Say , a death of a loved one , or a hard-to-reach goal . More examples , of personal struggle , from popular media : - An aging warrior with a desire to do the right thing has , for the longest time , been doing the wrong thing -LRB- whether due to passionate love , or due to other causes -RRB- , which in-turn , leads to disaster throughout the land . The aging warrior constantly reminds himself of his accomplishments and good moral decisions ... but ca n't ignore his faults which hang over him like a dark cloud . He is now put into a position where he can make things right , but will he succeed in doing the right thing , and does he have the chance for redemption ? -LRB- A character from Game of Thrones\/A Song of Ice and Fire -RRB- . - The hit show , Breaking Bad , was all about the main character 's flaws . Walter/PERSON White/PERSON , an honest and good man , has been bullied by life . People far inferior to him have succeeded greatly , while he has had a tough life for someone of such intellect . After learning he has terminal-cancer , he decides to go into the Meth business to make money for his family . Walter White 's character flaws make for his incredibly strong personality , his extreme-love for his family is compared to his severe and dangerous aggression that he has for the world that wronged him . Throughout the show , Walters/PERSON actions change him , and soon enough , his flaws consume the man he once was . Most importantly however , we see him fighting with himself ; we see him cry , we see him afraid , we see him angry at both the world and his own actions , which perfectly sets up the ultimate irony that Walter/PERSON eventually becomes the thing people are scared of . A strong character is one that has internal faults . A character with a strong personality is one that suffers from the same faults normal people have -LRB- lust , anger , jealousy ... -RRB- , and in making a character with such traits , it becomes more relatable as a whole .</answer><suggestions>walter/PERSON white/PERSON walter/PERSON white/PERSON walters/PERSON walter/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402933186000">What makes a good character is an author who is a keen observer of people and truly understands them . There are n't any shortcuts or magic formulas .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402934186000">Readers will admire any character that is a -RRB- believable , and b -RRB- works without giving up to accomplish their goal . Many people admire characters like Atticus Finch because he chooses to take on the impossible task of defending a man for murder who has zero chance of being acquitted in the racist town where they live . But he does n't give up and he defends the case cleverly and without giving up . On the other hand , people hate Bella Swan because through most of the story , she simply lets things happen to her , and instead of working to correct or cope with her situation , she attempts suicide , engages in reckless behavior or does nothing at all .</answer><suggestions>atticus/PERSON finch/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402935800000">Well , gender \/ really \/ is no object , and hardly ever is . A strong character does what they think is right regardless of the consequences , basically .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402942695000">https:\/\/en.wikipedia.org\/wiki\/Character_Strengths_and_Virtues_%28book%29</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140604190316AAF0wYE">
	<title>Film exposed to light ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I was rewinding my film in my room with the lights off and I opened too early because some film did n't rewind all the way . I have the Minolta XD11 . Is the part of the film that I exposed ruined or would it be `` okay '' since it was exposed in a dark room -LRB- there was some light shining through the creaks of the door -RRB- ?</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401936805000">The only way to know is to have it developed .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401936812000">If the lights were off , then no problem If you go to the trouble of rewinding your film in the dark , why not go all the way and shut off the lights outside the door and place some gaffers or duct tape over the door where light is leaking through . How much of the film was not in the cassette ? Usually the film you already exposed , loading the film will be attached to the take-up spool , so no damage will be done in any case</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401951549000">Even a very small amount of light can ruin a film . You 'll have to get it developed and see what shots you have saved .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401961924000">developed</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401980541000">If you `` darkened '' again after a very brief low-level shine from the door your pics might not have been affected . But you will have to get the film processed anyway to see the remainder of the pics that will not have been affected . There is nothing you can now do about any that might have been affected . You really do not need to rewind in the dark , normal room light is fine . Just do not open the camera too early ! Just think about the old days when everybody used film - most pros , having to change film in daylight , simply shaded the camera with their bodies , or moved into the shadow of a tree if possible .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401981025000">If it was n't totally dark -LRB- with no light at all -RRB- . Then you may have exposed the film . The only way to tell how much is to get them developed and see .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140615062236AA7xcQC">
	<title>can i become a film director\/maker \/ production designer with an illustration diploma ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>before you say `` Give it up kid everyone wants to direct movies in hollywood '' please know that i make films for my passion of story telling and it does n't have to be hollywood . my plan is to work in a company for about a decade slowly working my way up and then with my portfolio i will go to film production companies with my work and to apply as production designer , and then move on to film making . If this does n't work , plan B is being an author . But still my final dream is to make movies . so ? what do you think .</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402838647000">you do n't need qualifications , you just do it and whatever courses you think will improve you</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403265354000">Give us some more information .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140614122338AAHL8sn">
	<title>Can I use a dslr to film events ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>Are there any limitations ? I have a canon/ORGANIZATION rebel t3</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402775567000">sure you can , and it 's quit good , but I do n't advice you to filming with it for so long time , like 1-3 hours , cause the sensor will heat up .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402776990000">You need to look in the manual to get some idea of how much time you have available based on the size of the memory . edit And to make sure the video format is something you can put into editing software without major hassles . Events can mean continuous filming from a fixed location for hours or it can mean wandering around and shooting all the different activities and people for later editing .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402840732000">DLSR 's do not shoot film so no , you can not use them to film anything . Some DSLR 's do , however , shoot video so you can shoot\/record\/video an event . Optical abnormalities and lack of proper audio input aside , the problem with using a DSLR to shoot long events is short record times , Most DSLR 's can only record for 20 minutes or less continuously . If you do n't mind constantly attending to this problem by feeding the camera cards and stopping and starting at pre-determined times -LRB- when you could be missing something and you should really have a second camera running -RRB- then it 's doable and people are doing this . Here 's an advocate 's blog : http:\/\/mattthomasfilm.blogspot.com\/2011\/05\/shooting-live-events-with-dslr.html There are no DSLR 's on the market that are as suitable as camcorders for shooting for long periods , or for that matter , gathering professional quality audio since there is no XLR input -LRB- professionals use a separate audio recording device -RRB- and video quality has weird quirks such as the fabled rolling shutter . The optical and audio shortcomings can be overlooked for cheaper productions . The positives are that price can be much lower than an interchangeable lens camcorder , DSLR 's are smaller an of course you have dual functionality . But at the end of the day , you 're forcing a camera to do something it 's not really designed for . DSLR 's are not a technological or photographic panacea despite how people use them . And they certainly can not film anything !</answer><suggestions>dlsr/PERSON dslr/ORGANIZATION dslr/ORGANIZATION dslr/ORGANIZATION dslr/ORGANIZATION dslr/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140623100810AA4EYqD">
	<title>What Are Some Important Quotes in the book `` Brother Im Dying '' ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>i wanted to know some quotes from the book `` Brother Im dying '' and there significance .</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403544212000">Brother , you 're flunking .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140605223141AA4aNVu">
	<title>Ca n't Find ANY Good Teen Books , Help !?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I 've been searching the internet for hours now and it 's getting late -LRB- 1:23 right now -RRB- but I simply can not find a book I think I will genuinely enjoy . It 's driving me insane right now and I would greatly appreciate some help ! I 'm looking for a book for teenage guys -LRB- male protagonist -RRB- that does n't rely on a silly mystery to keep you reading . Books I have already read . Hunger Games Maze Runner Enders Game Insignia The False Prince Divergent Harry/PERSON Potter/PERSON Percy/PERSON Jackson/PERSON Alex/PERSON Rider/PERSON Assassins Apprentice Unwind H.I.V.E. and many many more that I ca n't remember at the moment . So any suggestions ?</content><suggestions>harry/PERSON potter/PERSON percy/PERSON jackson/PERSON alex/PERSON rider/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402032961000">Maze Runner sounds good .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402033782000">http:\/\/www.goodreads.com\/list\/tag\/male-protagonist They have lists of books with male protagonists . Go to that link and select one of the YA male protagonist lists .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402033854000">Ask any librarian . They know exactly which books are hugely popular . You can also pick any of your choices , go onto google/ORGANIZATION and type in ` books similar to _____ ' to find others that are like the ones you like .</answer><suggestions>google/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402035298000">Look on Goodreads . type in your fav genre or book and it will come up with recommendations ! Anyway , here are a few of my favs ! - Leviathan by Scott/PERSON Westerfield/PERSON -LRB- the trilogy is so good ! -RRB- - Incarceron by Catherine/PERSON Fisher/PERSON . - The Mortal Instruments Trilogy -LRB- cant remember the authors name haha -RRB- and The Name of The Star by Maureen/PERSON Johnson/PERSON !</answer><suggestions>scott/PERSON westerfield/PERSON catherine/PERSON fisher/PERSON maureen/PERSON johnson/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402063992000">YA books with male protagonist More Than This by Patrick/PERSON Ness/PERSON Noble Conflict by Malorie/PERSON Blackman/PERSON Bodyguard : Hostage by Chris/PERSON Bradford/PERSON Peak by Roland/PERSON Smith/PERSON Rock Wars by Robert/PERSON Muchamore/PERSON</answer><suggestions>patrick/PERSON ness/PERSON malorie/PERSON blackman/PERSON chris/PERSON bradford/PERSON roland/PERSON smith/PERSON robert/PERSON muchamore/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402401866000">read the scorch trials its the second part of the maze runner its the best</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140616222816AASXpde">
	<title>I forgot to sand before painting , will clear coat protect it ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>Spray painted then hand painted a plastic hard hat for someone and the paint was chipping a little as I finished hand painting it . I forgot to sand the helmet first and did a lot of work hand painting it . If I cover it in clear coat will the chipping stop and will it last ?</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402983535000">Probably NOT . ANY paint on top is only as good as what the first coat is ATTACHED to . . Like people who think if they put enough paint over dirt that it will be as good as a clean surface . Good luck . Peace . P.S. there is a difference between `` CHIPPING '' and ... PEELING . A `` chip '' is more related to an IMPACT or trauma to the surface . `` PEELING '' is more characteristic of a poorly prepared substrate surface . You might get by with your project if you chipped it as otherwise the paint is adhering overall .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140625095108AAhxBZ2">
	<title>Any poems about conformity ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>My poetry interpretation theme is `` masks '' and it is basically about how people hide themselves to other people . The intro piece is `` We wear the mask '' by Paul/PERSON Laurence/PERSON Dunbar/PERSON . Do you have any poems to suggest-preferably written in the 20th century or earlier ?</content><suggestions>paul/PERSON laurence/PERSON dunbar/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403715913000">Try `` The Unknown Citizen '' by W.H./PERSON Auden/PERSON -LRB- mid-20th century -RRB- , and `` Firelight '' by E.A./PERSON Robinson/PERSON -LRB- early 20th century -RRB- . The first is about the individual in society ; the second is about the individual in a family .</answer><suggestions>w.h./PERSON auden/PERSON e.a./PERSON robinson/PERSON</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140603115701AA0IaWS">
	<title>Where can I submit chapters of my writing for others to critque ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I 'm a beginning writer and I 've been working on a story that 's somewhat comic-book style with how it 's written , minus the pictures . I keep getting stuck and do n't manage to write any new material for it for a long time and I want to have something to help motivate me to write . I 'd like to find some site that I can safely upload chapters of my story at a time and have people read them and I 'm hoping that if they want more of it that it 'll help keep me on track . What I 'm looking for is much like Fanfiction.net but considering my writing is n't fanfiction ... Thanks !</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401822227000">Wattpad/ORGANIZATION . its free and you retain rights to your work . Others can read and leave comments about your work as well .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401822679000">Wattpad/ORGANIZATION is the best</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140618140344AAAVwJx">
	<title>Would you buy a finished paint by numbers ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I run my own craft business and love painting but ca n't draw I often do paint by numbers in my spare time not the simple ones the super hard ones and they look amazing and I was wondering if I framed them and put them on my stall would people buy or think I 'm mad lol</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403125577000">I would n't but that is my choice . You do n't need others to ok this with you . If you enjoy collecting them go for it .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403129371000">I would n't want anyone to sell me one only to later realize it was a paint by numbers . However , if you are selling it cheap on a general stall to people that do n't care if its real or not , then that would be fine in my humble opinion . Art is art at the end of the day , and not everybody has big bucks to spend on expensive real art . Good luck and glad you 're enjoying doing it - art is always great fun no matter how good you are . Enjoy , and sell a bit , why not !</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403130829000">No but some people probably would .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403159485000">I would think that less artistically inclined people would buy them if they were fairly cheap . Just make sure that the customer knows that it is a paint by numbers and is n't surprised by it . I would be devastated to find out it was only a paint by numbers when I could just do that myself .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403178817000">Never .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140618141257AAQm1bZ">
	<title>Who wants help in finding a place to publish their work ? -LRB- plus tips -RRB- ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>sorry , http:\/\/sexandmurder.com\/ also Duotrope.com -LRB- you must pay but its $ 50 a year -RRB- Duotrope lists all publishing sites for you</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I was once here clueless so i thought I 'd help fellow writers out . Tip # 1 You WILL get denied early on and you will learn patience but do n't give up . Steven/PERSON King/PERSON said in one of his introductions that he was denied SO many times . Tip # 2 If you want money for it -LRB- do n't we all -RRB- It has to be good enough for them to pay for it . I was happy just to get published without payment because it 's hard enough to get published anyway . I recommend just getting published for any payment -LRB- even if it 's none -RRB- . Regardless if you get paid or not you can forever tell people that you are a published author . Tip # 3 Read their work so you know what they want and if your work fits . One site is general , the other horror . Tip # 4 Learn to dig for publishing sites . I just type in what I want but it does take practice . Ok , here you go : http:\/\/www.bigpulp.com\/#!submissions\/c1dvr http:\/\/www.bigpulp.com\/#!submissions\/c1dvr</content><suggestions>steven/PERSON king/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403126192000">Thanks !! I think I talk in the name of us all aspiring authors when I say that this has been a lot of help . Thanks for helping us and using your time for such matters . Honto/PERSON Arikatou/PERSON !! LOL Sorry , just an otaku way of saying it .</answer><suggestions>honto/PERSON arikatou/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403126597000">This is great , thank you ! Once I 'm at the stage of publishing I 'll be sure to look back at this . Greatly appreciated .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140609112801AAnee0x">
	<title>what is the most important thing to save from the world civilization history ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>what is the most important thing to save from that past ? and why ?</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402338567000">My teddy bear . I wuvs it .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402338638000">Most important things to save are records of the mistakes we made -LRB- and to have the guts to admit they were mistakes -RRB- . Otherwise , as the saying goes , we are doomed to repeat them .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402339299000">Accurate writing . You fail</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402339825000">If I could go back in time , I would save the contents of the Library of Alexandria/LOCATION .</answer><suggestions>alexandria/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402353219000">Much was saved from the Greeks , upon which the edifice of the Global civilisation that is common to Humanity rests . Yet much more had gone missing -LRB- someone here cited example of the library at Alexandria/LOCATION that was burnt -RRB- . One of the ancient universities of India/LOCATION at Nalanda/LOCATION survived for almost a thousand years with its rich library from which the Buddhist scholars from Tibet/LOCATION & China/LOCATION were copying.It was Nalanda/LOCATION 's misfortune that it survived till the Islamic times . First Sultans of Delhi/LOCATION from Turkic/LOCATION Central Asia/LOCATION in their uncompromising fanatism , burnt the library as they were heretic & against the tenets of Islam . It is said that the books on the pathways burnt for months . It was a great loss to Human heritage . And none could save them .</answer><suggestions>alexandria/LOCATION india/LOCATION nalanda/LOCATION buddhist/ORGANIZATION tibet/LOCATION china/LOCATION nalanda/PERSON delhi/LOCATION turkic/LOCATION central/LOCATION asia/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402355204000">Writing and maths .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402497926000">Nothing , it be better if human civilization went extinct so the rest of the world can finally recover from it .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140621012549AAOo4ve">
	<title>which course should I prefer when going for digital art ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>hey ! well ... I 'm currently at a position where i have no idea which course I should select ... For a very long time , i have always been interested in anime . . their story plot , soundtrack . . and especially in their art design . I hoped on becoming a manga artist but ... I 'm pretty sure that it 's pretty hard to get by.You need to be extremely creative to think out of the box . And i dont think i 'm THAT capable of something like that ... but i think i can try ;-RRB- ... also . i do like the concept of drawing anime both digitally and traditionally ... not to brag but ... I think I 'm not that bad ... I 'm pretty cool about the idea of going for Disney/ORGANIZATION or Dreamworks/ORGANIZATION -LRB- IF I 'm good enough ... :'P -RRB- . . and later i thought of game designing ... I got inspired by the games that pewdiepie played \* BroFist \* and ` I ' wanted to make some games as awesome as the ones he played ... but I 'm still confused ... I 'm hoping to get a good job with whatever I 'm opting for ... And i wan na be able to live comfortably with the money i get ... and my family on the other hand , suggested that i go for civil engineering ... so yaaa ... : P . i have some of my stuff here so then you can get an idea about what i mean ... http:\/\/unioxcaliber.deviantart.com\/gallery\/ soo ... my question is ... 1 . what should i go for -- game designing\/disney/ORGANIZATION animation \/ manga artist \/ civil engineering \/ OR is there is something else that really matches my preferences ?? 2 . will it help me out when it comes to money ?? anyway thanks for reading ; -RRB-</content><suggestions>dreamworks/ORGANIZATION pewdiepie/PERSON brofist/PERSON</suggestions>
	<content>Aaand ... I 'm 16 xD</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403381464000">Hello ! I 'm a graduate with a Bachelours in Media Arts and Animation and I have to say your work looks very clean and nice . You 've got a good hang of digital art . I would have to say to go into what makes you happy and will continue to make you happy when you have it as a job . I would start out small goals though . I knew so many people who started at the same college as myself having their set goal be Pixar/ORGANIZATION and Disney/ORGANIZATION , Dreamworks/ORGANIZATION and the likes . But more that likely when you get out you 'll be working for an advertisement company building your way up . Manga artist is also tough , there 's already many manga artists who struggle . The best thing to do is find that niche , find something that fills a spot in the art world and you will have a harder time failing . Money is hard to guarantee with a job like art , but if you are really motivated and stick with it I 'm sure you 'll be fine :-RRB- Good luck ! - Brittany</answer><suggestions>pixar/ORGANIZATION disney/ORGANIZATION dreamworks/ORGANIZATION brittany/PERSON</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140616193752AA6M8Z0">
	<title>Canvas painting help ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>Are those little wedges that fit into the slots of the wooden panels of the canvas really needed ? I notice most store bought canvas do n't even come packed with them . If they are needed should I be adding them before I paint , or after the painting is finished ?</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402973204000">They 're intended to tighten the canvas if it starts to sag . You tap them in further to tighten it more . If the canvas is pre-primed and tight enough for you , do n't worry about them yet . If it 's unprimed , wait until after you prime it to decide if they 're needed or if the canvas is tight enough as is , as priming will make it more rigid .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403131221000">Amelie/PERSON has answered you exactly here . However , I would just add for you to keep them as the painting may sag a bit in the future , it can happen .</answer><suggestions>amelie/PERSON</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140605091638AATCTbo">
	<title>Questions for Actors !?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>1 . How many acting productions have you been in ? -LRB- This includes plays , musicals , TV shows , movies , ect . -RRB- 2 . What productions have you been involved in ? -LRB- Name of production -RRB- 3 . What have been some of your favorite roles ? 4 . What 's your favorite part about acting ? 5 . How old were you when you started acting ? This is just for fun . If you have been in a freakishly large amount of productions , you do n't have to list them all .</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401985787000">I 'm not - but my daughter is a professional actor . 1 -RRB- She 's been in about 60 stage plays , two feature films , maybe 10 student\/short films , five pantomimes , one season with The Polar Express Xmas show , one TIE company for several performances , a few voice-overs and several corporate commercials for the internet . 2 -RRB- Apart from those , she helps with set-building for a community theater , and also front-of-house in her spare time - so maybe another 20 productions . 3 -RRB- She loved playing Lady/PERSON Macbeth/PERSON , Maria/PERSON in Twelfth Night , Stephanie/PERSON in Duet for One , Carla/PERSON in Kennedy 's Children and Doto in A Phoenix Too Frequent . 4 -RRB- All of it - every second of auditioning , rehearsing , performing ... everything . 5 -RRB- She started professional acting quite late - when she was about 22 , because she 'd been very ill in her teens . But she started training first in singing when she was 12 , and acting when she was 17 . Hope this is what you wanted !</answer><suggestions>maria/PERSON stephanie/PERSON carla/PERSON kennedy/PERSON doto/ORGANIZATION phoenix/LOCATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140601105234AA3ANDN">
	<title>Help with my Animal Farm essay ?? pt . 1 ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>Equality and knowledge are two of the most important factors in human life and , according to some books , animal life , as well . The intelligence of some clever pigs and the inequality they represent impact the lives of some naive farm animals . George/PERSON Orwell/PERSON reveals the injustice of knowledge and equality through the allegorical novel Animal Farm . The inability or unwillingness to question authority condemns the working class to suffer the full extent of the ruling class 's oppression . For example , the animals on the Manor Farm are being taken advantage of by the pigs , who are the smarter creatures . With the knowledge the pigs have , they are able to hold power over the other animals without them understanding . `` The pigs did not actually work , but directed and supervised the others '' -LRB- Orwell/PERSON 27 -RRB- . This illustrates how the pigs have outsmarted the other animals by tricking them into doing work on the farm without contributing themselves . In addition , the importance of knowledge is shown in the work of the guard dogs . `` When -LSB- Napoleon/PERSON -RSB- did emerge , it was with the escort of six dogs who closely surrounded him and growled if anyone came too near . '' -LRB- Orwell/PERSON 75 -RRB- The dogs were raised by Napoleon/PERSON , showing that they are not educated , but brainwashed . They have never known any other form of discipline before the rule of Napoleon/PERSON , their leader . Is this a good intro and first body paragraph ? It can not relate back to Joseph/PERSON Stalin/PERSON and needs to be about injustice of knowledge and equality .</content><suggestions>george/PERSON orwell/PERSON orwell/ORGANIZATION napoleon/PERSON orwell/PERSON napoleon/PERSON napoleon/PERSON joseph/PERSON stalin/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401645259000">Part 2 of my essay above ^ ^ ^ the 2nd body paragraph and conclusion When forming a new way of life , equality is the first issue to be taken care of , but Napoleon/PERSON instead demonstrates inequality . For example , the condition in which the farm animals work is rigor . Orwell/PERSON states , `` the animals worked like slaves , '' -LRB- Orwell/PERSON 59 -RRB- . This is a perfect example of inequality by comparing the animals ' hard labor to that of a slave . In addition , the rule of all animals being equal had been replaced , by the overruling pigs , with one that read , `` All animals are equal , but some are more equal than others , '' -LRB- Orwell/PERSON 134 -RRB- . The words `` more equal '' completely contradict the original message of the commandment . If all animals are equal , it 's impossible for some to be `` more equal '' . All in all , equality and knowledge were taken advantage of at the expense of the others ' welfare . Equality turned in to `` more equal '' and knowledge turned into power . History only repeats itself when power gets put in the wrong hands . What the animals did not know was sometimes for the better , but not knowing too much left them just as guilty as the pigs .</answer><suggestions>napoleon/PERSON orwell/PERSON orwell/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140625193136AAUePpR">
	<title>Scary Quotes from past authors ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>By past I mean dead . Long dead . By Scary I mean Poe/PERSON scary .</content><suggestions>poe/PERSON</suggestions>
	<content>@ My Lunar Laundrette Apologies , I should have mentioned that I 'm making a game by I got to lazy to say that I was this time . I am looking for quotes to add in the game so that players will see them on the ground or pick up notes with them to add to the fear factor . `` There are moments when even to the sober eye of reason , the world of our sad humanity may assume the semblance of Hell . '' `` You will see the awful horror standing in a place he should not be . ''</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>\* ... but I got ...</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403750255000">Usually , individual sentences or `` quotes '' are n't scary . It usually takes a while to build up suspense in a scary story . So maybe you should look for whole scary stories . Go to the library and get a book of stories by Poe/PERSON , or H.P./PERSON Lovecraft/PERSON , etc. . While you 're there , ask the librarian for recommendations . They know stuff like that .</answer><suggestions>poe/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403753104000">`` Knock , knock . ''</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403756731000">' I am so far in blood that sin will pluck sin ' Richard/PERSON III/PERSON , Shakespeare/PERSON ' if one good deed in all my life I did , I do repent it from my very soul ' Aaron/PERSON the moor , Titus/PERSON andronicus/PERSON , Shakespeare/PERSON ' my revenge has just begun ! I spread it over centuries and time is on my side ' Count Dracula , Dracula , Bram/PERSON stoker/PERSON ' when I came into your life your life was over . It had a beginning , a middle , and an end . This is the end ' Anton/PERSON Chigurh/PERSON , No Country for Old Men , Cormac/PERSON McCarthy/PERSON -LRB- this book is n't that old but when I read this line it gave me chills and it still freaks me out ... Look in this book there are a lot of creepy quotes -RRB- ' Better to reign in Hell , then serve in Heav 'n ' Satan , Paradise Lost , John/PERSON Milton/PERSON</answer><suggestions>richard/PERSON iii/PERSON shakespeare/PERSON shakespeare/PERSON bram/PERSON stoker/PERSON anton/PERSON chigurh/PERSON cormac/PERSON mccarthy/PERSON john/PERSON milton/PERSON</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140613212156AAMXBQH">
	<title>About how long can I expect a grade 9 RCM voice exam to take > ?</title><suggestions>rcm/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<content>I 'm taking my grade 9 voice tomorrow and I 'm just trying to get a time figured out . I 've taken grade 7 , but grade 9 is quite a bit more stuff to have in mind . If any of you have taken this exam let me know how long it took !</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403163092000">Explain in more detail please .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140609160711AAprF2f">
	<title>What is your favorite musical by Andrew/PERSON Lloyd/PERSON Webber/PERSON ?</title><suggestions>andrew/PERSON lloyd/PERSON webber/PERSON</suggestions>
	<content>Mine is Cats . Yes , I know , everyone around me seems to abhor Cats , but I love it for a lot of various reasons . First of all , it was the first musical I ever saw . My parents took me to see it when I was two years old , and I immediately fell in love with it . Once we got home , we ordered the staged movie off of Amazon/ORGANIZATION , and I watched it so many times that the disk wore out and we had to buy another one . Oh , how I so badly wish I could have seen it on Broadway/LOCATION . Hopefully it will make a return one day and I can sit second row on opening night . That would be a dream come true . I am also a cat owner -LRB- although I was n't when I first fell in love with the musical -RRB- , and I think actually owning cats definitely helps people understand the musical better and like it more . Besides the plot -LRB- trust me , there is one -RRB- , I 'm just a huge fan of the songs and choreography . My second favorite ALW musical is Evita/PERSON . I like the songs and historical significance . I understand there will be a lot of POtO answers , and while I like Phantom , I 'm a bit picky about it . I have read both the original novel and Susan/PERSON Kay/PERSON 's book , and I absolutely loved both , so it 's a bit hard for me to take a musical adaption when I love the original story so much . However , the music is still excellent . Do n't even get me started on Love Never Dies \* cringe \*</content><suggestions>amazon/ORGANIZATION phantom/PERSON susan/PERSON kay/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402512745000">By far , `` Sunset Boulevard '' . He took a classic film and literally made it sing . I wo n't say that the musical is better than the film , because the film is practically perfect - but I can certainly imagine Gloria/PERSON Swanson/PERSON 's Norma/PERSON Desmond/PERSON singing `` With One Look '' or `` The Perfect Year '' .</answer><suggestions>gloria/PERSON swanson/PERSON norma/PERSON desmond/PERSON</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140612062149AAH8vjl">
	<title>Good story ideas ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I feel like writing some stories but I suck at coming up with ideas so can you help me by giving me ideas ?</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402579473000">what kind of story are you wanting to write , love , mystery , supernatural ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402580822000">A young man yearns for adventure outside his farm life , but his uncle , who raised him when his father died , forbids it . He knows that his father was a fighter pilot in the great war , and hopes that he can be someday too . One day , one of the farm workers falls ill , and starts raving about a local hermit who lives nearby . The boy decides to take the workers to see the hermit , who explains that he knew the boy 's father , that they fought together in the war , and he presents the boy with a special sword that belonged to his father . The boy tells the old man that he wants to become a great warrior like his father , and the old man agrees to teach him . The boy returns home to find his family murdered and home burned . Turns out that the two farm workers were actually runaways from a government work program . The boy , the old man and the two workers go to the nearest city and find a smuggler\/pilot in a seedy dive who will take them to some friends in a faraway land ; one of the workers has blueprints of the government HQ , and they can use them to find a weakness to exploit . Meanwhile , the princess of that land has been captured by the government , and when she refuses to tell them where the insurgents are hiding , they wipe out her people . The boy and his team stumble onto the government 's facility , where their vehicle is impounded , and they escape capture by hiding in secret compartments . They knock out some guards , take their uniforms and rescue the princess from her cell in a spectacular gun battle . The old man , in the meantime , sneaks into a security area and disengages the gate keeping them from escaping in their vehicel . He succeeds , but he is confronted by one of the powerful and corrupt government leaders . The leader and the old man have a sword duel , and the old man gives up his life to save the others . They escape , contact the resistance , and use the blueprints to find a vulnerable spot in the facility . The insurgents attack , and the boy , piloting a fighter , hears the old man 's voice , telling him to trust his feelings and obey his instincts . The boy is being pursued by the government leader , who is about to fire on him , but at the last moment , the smuggler fires uopn the leader , allowing the boy to fire a crucial shot that causes a chain reaction , destroying the facility . The boy , pilot , and co-pilot , a very tall , hairy individual with a speech impediment , are presented with medals by the princess in an elaborate cermony . Then there are two more movies and three very , very awful prequels . The end .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402581283000">I `` feel like '' cooking an amazing banquet for 40 people . But I do n't f eel like looking at any recipes , or doing any shopping , or cooking anything at all . Can somebody do it for me ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402581801000">I 'm not exactly sure what your looking for . Horror ? Romance ? Mystery ? Comedy ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402584578000">Write about a kiddie writer who sucks at coming up with ideas for stories because he has no imagination . He asks strangers for ideas but has no idea how to write , so he goes out to play with his friends and forgets about writing .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140626111816AAUpFjA">
	<title>I do n't know what he was trying to do ? It was a chance encounter ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I ran into this guy I knew in the street . He was faltering in his walk at first and then proceeded to blatantly eye me up and down , pausing at my a \*\* . I got ahead of him and stopped by an eatery to get some food . I was busy fishing for stuff but then I perceived what was his body being close behind . It was provocatively close .</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403807144000">he got horny looking at you so he went crazy</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403807496000">What is this , the 30th time you 've posted the same thing ? He was wondering why this repetitive woman was following him . When he brushed by you , he was trying to get away . How many more times are you going to post this exact same `` question '' ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>

