<question id="20140613123024AAkX1Tt">
	<title>Easy Statistics Question . ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I 'm trying to find the width and I thought it was 3.5 but I got this question wrong on the quiz . What is the real answer and how . Thanks so much !! Question18 For the following data , construct a grouped frequency distribution with 6 classes using the TI-83 \/ 84 . What is the correct Xscl or class width ? 10 8 6 14 26 13 17 19 11 9 18 14 13 12 15 15 5 11 16 11 a. 3.5 b. 4 c. 3 d. 3.4</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402890621000">Also do n't forget to search this on Google/ORGANIZATION .</answer><suggestions>google/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402934678000">Your maximum value is 26 and your minimum value is 5 . Both values are included , so you ca n't just subtract 26-5 = 21 . You have to subtract and add 1 , so that you will capture both end points : 26 - 5 + 1 = 22 . Now , since all your data points are integers , your class width should also be an integer , therefore 4 . By convention , the lowest class limit is the minimum , so the lowest class boundary would be 5.5 . If you used a class width of 3.5 , your classes , from boundary to boundary , would be as follows : 5.5-9 9-12 .5 12.5-16 16-19 .5 19.5-23 23-26 .5 Do you see the problem ? If your data are all integers , your class boundaries should all be halfway between two integers , because we want the boundary to split the data : We do n't want a dataa point resting on a class boundary . But you have 9 , 16 , and 23 as class boundaries . In your data set you have a 9 . Does it go in the first or second class ? You have a 16 . Does it go in the 3rd or 4th class ? There is no way to tell . Then , what would your midpoints be ? The average of the class boundaries : 7.25 , 10.75 , etc. . What a mess ! But if you use 4 , the class boundaries break very nicely : 5.5 9.5 13.5 17.5 21.5 21.5 27.5 leaving you these class limits and midpoints 6 7.5 9 10 11.5 13 14 15.5 17 18 19.5 21 22 23.5 25 26 27.5 29 The only flaw is that the last class is mostly empty .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140604083714AANM1Br">
	<title>Looking for a school with a college town ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>Okay I am really into the ` college town ' vibe ... where it kind of feels like a village if you get what I 'm saying ? Lots of small shops , university gear shops , little restaurants and boutiques . Best ones I 've seen : Chapel/LOCATION Hill/LOCATION , NC -LRB- UNC/ORGANIZATION -RRB- , Nashville/LOCATION , TN -LRB- Vanderbilt/LOCATION -RRB- , Davidson/LOCATION , NC -LRB- Davidson/LOCATION College/ORGANIZATION -RRB- , Oxford/LOCATION , OH -LRB- Miami/LOCATION of Ohio/LOCATION -RRB- , Columbia/LOCATION , MO -LRB- MIzzou/LOCATION -RRB- . I would like to stay in the warmer parts of the country , but anything goes . Thanks a lot !!</content><suggestions>chapel/LOCATION hill/LOCATION nashville/LOCATION vanderbilt/ORGANIZATION davidson/PERSON davidson/ORGANIZATION college/ORGANIZATION oxford/LOCATION miami/LOCATION of/LOCATION ohio/LOCATION columbia/LOCATION mizzou/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401897096000">UMass/ORGANIZATION and Amherst/ORGANIZATION College/ORGANIZATION -LRB- Amherst/LOCATION , MA -RRB- , SUNY/ORGANIZATION New Paltz -LRB- New/LOCATION Paltz/LOCATION , NY/LOCATION -RRB- , Smith/ORGANIZATION College/ORGANIZATION -LRB- Northampton/LOCATION , MA -RRB- , U/ORGANIZATION Georgia/LOCATION -LRB- Athens , GA/LOCATION -RRB- , U/ORGANIZATION Michigan/ORGANIZATION -LRB- Ann/LOCATION Arbor/LOCATION , MI/LOCATION -RRB- , U Texas Austin -LRB- Austin/LOCATION , TX/LOCATION -RRB- , U Cal Berkeley -LRB- Berkeley/LOCATION , CA/LOCATION -RRB- , any college in the city of Boston/LOCATION , U/ORGANIZATION Colorado/ORGANIZATION -LRB- Boulder/LOCATION , CO/LOCATION -RRB- , UNC Chapel/LOCATION Hill/LOCATION -LRB- which you mentioned -RRB- , U Wisconsin/LOCATION -LRB- Madison/LOCATION/LOCATION , WI/LOCATION -RRB- . Of those , the biggest are obviously Austin/LOCATION , Boston/LOCATION , and Madison/LOCATION ; and Berkeley/LOCATION is right next to San/LOCATION Francisco/LOCATION , so if you 're trying to avoid large places , those wo n't work for you . But all of these offer that feel you 're looking for . All are fabulous .</answer><suggestions>umass/ORGANIZATION amherst/ORGANIZATION college/ORGANIZATION amherst/LOCATION suny/ORGANIZATION new/ORGANIZATION paltz/ORGANIZATION new/LOCATION paltz/LOCATION ny/LOCATION smith/ORGANIZATION college/ORGANIZATION northampton/LOCATION ma/LOCATION georgia/LOCATION athens/LOCATION michigan/LOCATION ann/PERSON arbor/PERSON texas/LOCATION austin/LOCATION austin/LOCATION tx/LOCATION cal/LOCATION berkeley/LOCATION berkeley/LOCATION boston/LOCATION colorado/LOCATION boulder/LOCATION chapel/LOCATION hill/LOCATION wisconsin/LOCATION madison/LOCATION austin/LOCATION boston/LOCATION madison/LOCATION berkeley/LOCATION san/LOCATION francisco/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402164762000">Clemson/LOCATION , SC is definitely a college town , and Clemson/ORGANIZATION is a good school .</answer><suggestions>clemson/PERSON clemson/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140610102326AA3pmaG">
	<title>What percentage do you need in order to do Higher tier for GCSE ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I 'm currently in set 3 , which means that I am currently doing Foundation tier but this is my last chance to prove that I am able to do Higher tier for Science GCSE . My exams are out of 60 marks but I do not know what mark or percentage I need in order to prove to my head of science that I am fully capable in doing higher paper . What percentage or mark do I need to do Higher paper for GCSE ?</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402546567000">more specific please</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140611170153AAHPuYj">
	<title>great gatsby help ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>i have to write an essay answering this question `` what is beauty ? what makes something beautiful ? '' referencing the great gatsby and one of the following texts : scarlet/PERSON letter , the crucible , moby dick , slaughterhouse five , and hamlet/PERSON . how should i answer this ?</content><suggestions>dick/PERSON hamlet/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402614227000">Give us some more information .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140609052848AA9cZW3">
	<title>Proper citations for training document ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I am trying to put together a training document for a course on environmental sustainability . While researching the topic online , I found a website -LRB- couple of them actually -RRB- where the information could be very useful for my presentation . What would be the best way to cite from the website considering copyrights etc. . Do I need explicit permission from the website owner , or could I just reference him\/her in the presentation . Alternatively , could I just modify the document and use it without referencing anyone ?! Thanks</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402326761000">You can use `` illustrative excerpts '' from just about any copyrighted document , to a limited extent , as authorized under `` fair use '' in a critique or scholarly review . You would simply `` cite '' the source in your footnotes . No , you can not `` just modify '' a copyrighted document without risking charges of copyright infringement -LRB- creating a derivative work -RRB- , and plagiarism -LRB- submitting works of others as your own -RRB- , the latter of which is not actually illegal unless you doing it fraudulently for money .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140622190334AAbgB4J">
	<title>when reading a scene from a script , how do i identify whatt the punctuations : commas , periods , exclamation marks , mean ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I ca n't believe it they kicked out ! That was so rude ! I mean who gets kicked out of a chain gang ? You work your fingers to the bone ... tarring roofs and this is the thanks I get ?</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403489339000">I ca n't believe it they kicked out ! - Raise your voice -LRB- get louder -RRB- from what it already was -LRB- not too loud -RRB- That was so rude ! - raise your voice -LRB- not too loud -RRB- I mean who gets kicked out of a chain gang ? - slightly make your voice higher at the end to make it a rhetorical question You work you fingers to the bone ... tarring roofs and this is the thanks I get ? - pause a little bit after the periods then end the sentence with a slightly higher pitched voice</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140619105821AAuioIb">
	<title>Where can I study university ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I 'm looking to study something like hardware engineering or software engineering . I can only pay 20000 $ since my mum 's job pays half the price but that is n't the problem the problem is if I go somewhere amazing like the USA we wo n't be able to afford it because of the prices of the apartments etc. . Where is a good place with cheap living and a university price less than 20000 $ -LRB- US dollars -RRB- .</content><suggestions>usa/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403200774000">study in kean/ORGANIZATION university/ORGANIZATION is one of the best in my opinion</answer><suggestions>kean/ORGANIZATION university/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403201394000">What do you mean by cheap ? You have a number for the tuition -LRB- $ 20,000 -RRB- , for a viable answer you need a number for annual living expenses .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403218225000">No way . Your budget is about half of what you need for school + living expenses in Canada/LOCATION or UK/LOCATION , less than half of what you need for US/LOCATION , Australia/LOCATION , etc. . Add application fees , testing fees , passport , visa , travel expenses , etc , to those numbers . You might find a school with tuition alone within that $ 20k , but you need tuition , fees , books , equipment , supplies , health insurance , room & board , clothing , laundry & dry cleaning , toiletries , grooming\/haircuts , and all your other personal incidental expenses , travel + local transportation , entertainment , club memberships -LRB- including student memberships in professional societies in your field -RRB- , more . All school budgets listed on their websites are estimates of what citizen-students pay to the school . Lots of personal expenses & international students ' expenses are not included . Guess they figure college students already know & allow for the costs of clothing , toothpaste , laundry , etc. .</answer><suggestions>canada/LOCATION australia/LOCATION room/ORGANIZATION &/ORGANIZATION board/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140621041314AA5qW3l">
	<title>This sentence is a bit difficult . Can you help me spell it correctly ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>`` A month ago or so you posted an image and when I looked at it I thought : `` This is you when it was younger '' and when I opened to see it larger I saw the description that in fact is your mom . You look just like your mom . '' I would be very grateful for your time and help !</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403349539000">A month ago or so you posted an image and when I looked at it I thought : This looks like you when you were younger and when I opened it I saw the description which stated that it was your Mom . You do look like your Mom .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403351106000">`` A month ago or so you posted an image and , when I looked at it , I thought : `` This is you when younger '' . When I opened it to see a larger image I saw from the description that , in fact , it is your Mom . You look just like her . ''</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403354566000">`` A month ago or so you posted an image . When I looked at it I thought : `` This must be you when you were younger ! '' When I opened the image to see a larger version , I read the description and realized that in fact is was actually your mom ; you look just like her ! ''</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140607211424AAdLIHO">
	<title>Generation X Events ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>For History class we have to pick an event from this generation and write an argumentitive essay on an opinion about it . I can write a good argumentive essay I just ca n't think of a good event , so what is an event with two popular sides to it ? EX : This was a bad idea because ...</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402201148000">https:\/\/www.youtube.com\/watch?v=m_mDTLphIVY</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140604150422AAIDveZ">
	<title>Question 2 . 2 . What is the factored form of 4k2 + 20k + 25 ? -LRB- Points : 1 -RRB- 2 -LRB- k + 5 -RRB- 2 -LRB- 2k -- 5 -RRB- 2 -LRB- 2k + 5 -RRB- 2 4 -LRB- k + 5 -RRB- -LRB- k -- 5 -RRB- ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>Please Help Me ! I need to run in this worksheet and i Cant figure this problem out !!!</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402082699000">more specific please</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403379543000">it 's -LRB- 2k + 5 -RRB- 2</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140610062626AA46ms6">
	<title>GCSE/ORGANIZATION Mark/PERSON 's Gospel Help ?</title><suggestions>gcse/PERSON mark/PERSON</suggestions>
	<content>I 'm revising for marks gospel and I need help to answer this question . d -RRB- `` Jesus/PERSON asked the rich young man to do too much '' Do you agree or disagree with this statement ? State why someone may disagree with you ? In your answer refer to Christianity .</content><suggestions>jesus/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402534483000">Also do n't forget to search this on Google/ORGANIZATION .</answer><suggestions>google/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140618125641AAGkGpi">
	<title>What should my child know to get into a magnet\/charter school ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>In my state , either you go to a public school -LRB- awful in South/LOCATION Louisiana/LOCATION -RRB- or you pay out the wazoo for private schools which provide better educations academically . However , in the last 5-10 years they have rolled out these new charter\/magnet schools that have a higher quality of education and require testing in order to get into the school . The child will have to score within the 85th to 99th percentile in order to be considered . There are other factors such as proximity to the school and a few other factors . However , I am constantly reading to my daughter , but now she is 3 and we will be testing in November\/December of this year for the pre school programs . I want to make sure she can do whatever they ask of her , therefore I am wondering what sort of things to they test on a 4 year old and what else will she need to know in order to get ahead of the very large crowd trying to get into these schools ?</content><suggestions>south/LOCATION louisiana/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403189904000">The screening they use can vary a great deal . You 'd have to see the website of the school you are interested in to know what they do . Some do a fairly simple screening looking at things like : Enthusiasm Toward Learning `` I look for those qualities that prime children to be successful in school , '' says Kim/PERSON Hughes/PERSON . Does the child approach learning enthusiastically ? Is she eager to explore and discover ? Does she ask questions , take initiative , and persist when tasks are difficult ? Solid Oral-Language Skills Research shows that one of the best predictors of later reading success is a well-developed oral vocabulary in kindergarten . `` PreK kids are learning vocabulary at the rate of five to six words a day , '' says Waite-Stupiansky . `` It 's just amazing how they will retain words if you use them several times in context and conversation . '' The Ability to Listen Children 's literature is a rich resource for expanding language . `` We expect parents to be reading to kids every day , '' says Jayne/PERSON C./PERSON Isaacs/PERSON . `` I can tell which children have been glued to the TV or computer for hours at a time . When we read them a story and ask them to tell us in their own words what they liked or remembered , they 're unable to do so . '' Besides fostering vocabulary and comprehension , reading develops the attention skills necessary in a kindergarten classroom . `` Listening is a key part of school behavior , '' Isaacs/PERSON notes . Students must be able to concentrate on what the teacher is saying , listen carefully for directions , and tune in to the sounds in letters and words . The Desire to Be Independent Encouraging self-help skills is an important step to preparing your child for kindergarten . `` It 's amazing how many kids come to kindergarten not knowing how to hang up a jacket , '' says Argandona/PERSON . It might be quicker for you to do it , but `` independence is critical for helping your child adjust to school , '' he emphasizes . The Ability to Play Well with Others Your child will need your assistance refining essential social skills such as sharing , compromising , turn-taking , and problem-solving . `` Children are naturally egocentric at this age , and we do n't expect them to be able to share everything , '' says Waite-Stupiansky . `` But by the time they reach kindergarten , they should be able to express their feelings in words and begin to understand that two people can use the same thing at the same time . '' Strong Fine-Motor Skills Your child 's hands must be strong enough to master coloring , cutting , pasting , and holding a pencil -- fine-motor tasks that kids use every day in kindergarten . `` By week one , we 're already writing a letter of the alphabet , '' says Argandona/PERSON . `` If kids ca n't hold the pencil correctly , they will fall behind . '' Basic Letter and Number Recognition Kindergarten teachers believe that it is their responsibility to teach kids letter sounds and how to write , but they do hope incoming students can recognize most letters by sight . They also hope children can count to 10 , identify numbers 1 to 5 , and know some shapes and colors . Some may actually administer a test of cognitive abilities . Some just allow entry by lottery and no testing or screening at all . The most important thing may be you and your child 's interest in whatever the theme or focus of the school is -LRB- science , the arts , etc. . -RRB-</answer><suggestions>kim/PERSON hughes/PERSON jayne/PERSON c./PERSON isaacs/PERSON isaacs/PERSON argandona/PERSON argandona/PERSON</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140605115942AAHijoB">
	<title>Trustworthy companies to teach English abroad ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>Lately , I 've been wanting something bigger than myself . I have considered teaching English in another country . I only have an Associates degree in General Studies . Does anyone know of any trustworthy companies to get certified through ? I recently went to an Oxford seminar and I noticed online that a few reviews think they are a scam . If anyone has any insight , I would really appreciate it .</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402017283000">For most jobs , you have to have a 4 year college degree and at least a certificate in TESL\/TEFL - preferably the CELTA . Go to eslcafe.com and look at the job list . That will give you an idea of the jobs available and the requirements .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140608090153AAQx192">
	<title>maths question help ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>\* 6x + 2y = -3</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>Solve the Simultaneous Equation 6x + 2 = -3 4x - 3y = 11 thanks</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402243495000">6x +2 = -3 -2 . -2 6x = -5 6x . 6x x = THIS IS WRONG I JUST SAW YOUR EDIT . - .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402243723000">6x = -5 x = -0.83 first find the X 4x - 3y = 11 4x-0 .83 = 3.17 so ... 3.17 - 3y = 11 -3 y = 7.83 y = 4.83 you have to check the number because i 'm using those simple calculator</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402244957000">Substitution Method 6x + 2y = -3 ------- -LRB- 1 -RRB- 4x - 3y = 11 ------- -LRB- 2 -RRB- From -LRB- 1 -RRB- , 6x = -2 y-3 x = -LRB- -2 y-3 -RRB- \/ 6 --------- -LRB- 3 -RRB- Sub -LRB- 3 -RRB- , into -LRB- 2 -RRB- 4 -LSB- -LRB- -2 y-3 -RRB- \/ 6 -RSB- -3 y = 11 4 -LRB- -2 y-3 -RRB- -18 y = 66 -8 y-12-18y = 66 -26 y = 78 y = -3 -LRB- ans -RRB- When y = 3 , into -LRB- 3 -RRB- x = -LSB- -2 -LRB- -3 -RRB- -3 -RSB- \/ 6 x = -LRB- 6-3 -RRB- \/ 6 x = 0.5 -LRB- ans -RRB- Or Elimination Method 6x + 2y = -3 ---------- -LRB- 1 -RRB- 4x - 3y = 11 ---------- -LRB- 2 -RRB- From -LRB- 1 -RRB- x3 , 18x + 6y = -9 --------- -LRB- 3 -RRB- From -LRB- 2 -RRB- x2 , 8x - 6y = 22 ---------- -LRB- 4 -RRB- -LRB- 3 -RRB- + -LRB- 4 -RRB- , 26x = 13 x = 0.5 -LRB- ans -RRB- When x = 0.5 , into -LRB- 1 -RRB- 6 -LRB- 0.5 -RRB- + 2y = -3 2y = -6 Y = -3 -LRB- ans -RRB-</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402245384000">6x + 2y = -3 4x - 3y = 11 multiply first equation by 3 , second equation by 2 , add : 18x + 6y = -9 8x - 6y = 22 ________________ 26x = 13 x = 13\/26 = 1\/2 using first equation : 6x + 2y = -3 6 -LRB- 1\/2 -RRB- + 2y = -3 3 + 2y = -3 2y = -6 y = -6 \/ 2 = -3 check using second equation : 4x - 3y = 11 4 -LRB- 1\/2 -RRB- - 3 -LRB- -3 -RRB- = 11 2 + 9 = 11 checks x = 1\/2 , y = -3</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140617152905AAraW4N">
	<title>SPANISH FINAL ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>Ok I failed Spanish 2 freshman year and retook it last year , barely passing . I was forced to take Spanish 3 junior year and I was barely passing the whole year . My teacher told me if I do n't get a 65 + on my final that I will fail for the year . PLEASE HELP ME !!! I NEED to pass but I do n't know what to do to prepare ! It 's so difficult and boring I lose interest in it within minutes of studying . I have only 6 more days before the test but I could really appreciate any help anyone has to offer . Please be very detailed . Thanks a lot !</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403044339000">Hey if it makes you feel any better , you 're not the only one who loses interest in studying in minutes . It happens buddy , but you have to if you want to pass the school year . Close the TV , shut down your laptop -LRB- unless you need it to study -RRB- , close and hide all your electronic devices , go take a shower , relax for 2 minutes , grab a snack if you want and sit down and study . You have to pass this exam or else you will fail . Good luck !</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403044665000">I took Spanish 3 this past school year -LRB- my sophomore year -RRB- . I do n't know what you covered in your class , but my final included us having to read a short story in Spanish and then answer questions about it , answer various questions concerning all of the verb tenses and forms as well as conjugation and more . I would suggest looking over all of the material you learned this year -LRB- handouts , notes , etc -RRB- and looking through your textbook also .</answer><suggestions>us/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403044906000">If Spanish is boring then there are two reasons : Either you dislike the subject so much that you choose it to be boring and that will never change until you change your mind set , or your teacher is making it boring which I highly doubt . I have taken Spanish since I was in the 7th grade until 12th year of High School and then a total of 6 more years in College . That makes 12 years of Spanish and I must say that it has never once been boring to me . I have had , for the most part , teachers from one or another region in Spain/LOCATION . This is language that you will need in any work situation you choose as it will be the main language spoken in the US in the near future . I would suggest that you study as much as you possibly can to pass this test and possibly switch to another language if you have to have more language credits . I also so n't get why you were forced to take it again . Who forced you ? your parents ? the school ? or did you choose it to keep the peace ? .</answer><suggestions>spain/LOCATION us/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403056387000">I learned Spanish as a child . -- you know , that `` inferior '' Latin American Spanish ;--RRB- You know our English is considered inferior by some to proper British English . It is n't . It 's just different , as is Australian or Canadian English . I took Spanish in high school for an easy A and to have a background in the grammar and literature I did n't have through my spoken Spanish . I took it through college -LRB- Literature -RRB- for the same reason , but I majored in another area . It 's boring because of the way it 's presented . Conjugate this verb . Have this canned conversation . Some people thrive on that rote because they really have to just memorize , not learn , the language . But it does n't work : sorry , to those who think they have a fine background in it after several years , but nobody becomes bilingual in any language in a classroom . They become bilingual by actually having real , unscripted conversations . And not a crutched one with the local shop keeper . They become bilingual by living where the language is dominant . You understand the nuances of the language when you read literature \* originally \* written in the language . I read `` Love in the Time of Cholera '' and LOVED it -- in Spanish . The English translation is great too , but it is n't Spanish . Your situation now is a perfect example of studying something simply because you have to . Sorry , but the real world does n't care that you do n't enjoy it . I do n't enjoy calculus , but I had to take it for my major . Study up . Conjugate the verbs . Practice those forced conversations . A 65 is a relatively low bar . You can do it .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140617102632AAPzLAI">
	<title>When should I start putting in college applications ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>Junior year just ended yesterday and my dad 's already bugging me about college apps , but I 'm not sure if I should start applying this summer or wait until senior year officially starts . Most of my friends that graduated this year were working on applications around Christmastime , but I 'm just not sure when to start .</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403026362000">Most colleges wo n't even make their applications available until roughly August . For now , just narrow down where exactly you 'll be applying and take the ACT and\/or SAT and send your scores to these schools . Do not wait until Christmas to work on your applications . You 'll want to put in your applications ASAP after they become available . I was told to get all of them in before Thanksgiving .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403029301000">Most applications for Fall 2015 will open up beginning of September . Deadline dates are usually 1\/1 . Some can be eariler . Where are you apply to ? Do you have a list of schools you have researched You should be going on college visits right now . Meet with admissions , take a tour of the campus , eat in the dining hall . You should be writing your college essay over the summer</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140603131617AAsXYRf">
	<title>What does LP mean on instagram/ORGANIZATION ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I 've been noticing on instagram/ORGANIZATION that people are uploading pics and writing down LP next to it . What does this mean ? . It been confusing me for the past few days . Please help</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401829878000">Until you post a sample of these pictures , I can only speculate , but ... A popular meaning of ` LP ' is Let 's Play . It refers to the practice of making videos of yourself playing a game , usually uploaded to YouTube/ORGANIZATION , for the purpose of showing others how the game works and possibly to help people who are stuck at certain parts of the game .</answer><suggestions>youtube/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140626114755AAx0yWm">
	<title>Algebra questions !?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>On # 14 , I believe I have the correct answer , yet I am Now doubting myself ... Btw , x is the line that has no curves or squiggles . On number 15 , I do not know how to simplify it to be at least similar to any of the provided answers Number sixteen , I broke it down to : 7x = 5x +12 Now I am stuck , which number do I dived seven by ? Please help !</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403821610000">If you have 7x = 5x +12 -5 x -5 x 2x = 12 , then divide 2x and 12 by two which will result in x = 6</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140622011040AAZ0TjA">
	<title>Is Howstuffworks accurate with their information ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>Im not trying to cite anything , im listing possible websites I can use as research for my creative stories .</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403439067000">Yes . You 've posted this several times , and it has been reported .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140615190614AAf5U3D">
	<title>Do I HAVE to transfer my dual credits ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>So , I took English Dual Credit Junior and Senior years , and , unfortunately , I did n't do so well . In fact , my high school grades were n't so hot either . I had an A - GPA . I want to be a doctor , so I 'm planning on trying super hard in college for med school . Anyways , I was wondering if Dual Credits HAVE to be transferred . It would greatly alter my chances of getting into medical school if I had a C in somewhere factored in . I 've already talked to my parents about it , and they 're okay with paying for me to take English in college , if it would mean a totally clean slate .</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402890748000">Ask your school advisor .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403493640000">try google/ORGANIZATION it also</answer><suggestions>google/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140611180906AAGf9fM">
	<title>is stone mountain high safe ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I wish I could move after finishing this 2nd year , but it seems like my school is just not safe at all I know it 's hard to say goodbye to friends I grew up with , but the importance here is a good education , and safety .</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402535551000">I dont think anyone here knows where stone mountain high is . I would say just bring a gun to school . It ca n't hurt if no one can see it , and if there comes a time where you do use it , you 'll look like a hero !</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140607140550AAYTiFo">
	<title>How to become an obstetrician in australia/LOCATION ?</title><suggestions>australia/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>Hi everyone , I was just wondering how I can become an obstetrician . I just had a few questions to ask about the profession First off , What classes do you need to take in high school ? What ATAR Score will I need ? What University course do you need to take , and how long does it take to complete ? Are there easier or quicker ways to get into the profession if I am currently a midwife ? Overall how long will it take to become fully qualified without the midwifery degree ? Overall how long will it take to become fully qualified with the midwifery degree ? Do you need to do any kind of practical -LRB- after University -RRB- training to become an obstetrician ? If so , how long will it take and will I get payed and how much -LRB- weekly and rate -RRB- ? They are all the questions I can think of at the moment , if you can think of any thing important I forgot to ask about could you please provide me with some information about it . Thank you for the help .</content><suggestions>atar/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402178719000">An obstetrician is not a uni degree it 's a college fellowship DRANSCOG . . You need to be a doctor first and work in the hospital and then get a series of 6 month jobs in o and g departments where you can study for the fellowship exams . Nursing will not help you at all</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402182814000">An obstetrician is a medical doctor . No , becoming a midwife does n't help you become a doctor . You need to visit university websites to view the admission requirements for medical school</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402332043000">More info please</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140622090620AAuLdft">
	<title>Idea for an English essay ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>Hey I 'm a 14 year old and I 've got an English essay coming up that I really want to do well on . I 'm not the bets creatively and the best idea I came up with was about a family with 2 teenage boys going on a trip -LRB- jet skis ? -RRB- and they go and get a little excited and break away from the group they end up in a cave -LRB- ? -RRB- and not sure what else Can someone help me</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403455838000">Do n't make your plot too complicated by putting too many characters in it . I would go with just the two boys who decided to take their jet skis out for spin on the harbor . They came upon a pod of whales and lost track of time ... E-mail me and I will write something up for you . tell me what grade you are in and what time the essay id due . markpark3199@yahoo.ca</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403465267000">Not pointing any fingers , but ... one of the answers to this question so far is really dull -LRB- and it 's not mine -RRB- . Also do n't trust the person above for homework help , they spelt `` is '' wrong . I say , the boys find a cursed medallion in the cave . A demon appears to them and tells them that they can have all the riches , and jet skis , they could ever want . But , in return , the boys must swim back to shore without the help of their trusty jet skis . The catch is , they have to do so smothered in tuna ! On the return journey , they are attacked by a pod of killer whales who mistake them for a tasty snack . They soon lose track of time , and their lives ! No more jet skis for them ! Good luck ! -LRB- Do n't be a cheat , write it yourself ! -RRB-</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140601014139AA5Szo2">
	<title>from which universities in usa/LOCATION we can get phd admission for electrical engineering easily . . and also finishing phd is easy ?</title><suggestions>usa/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>And also scholarships available ??</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401629929000">Getting into Graduate school for a Doctorate is not easy . Doing the requirements to complete a Doctorate in any field is not easy . I do n't know why you would assume it could be . Do your own research into Graduate schools with an EE http:\/\/grad-schools.usnews.rankingsandreviews.com\/best-graduate-schools\/top-engineering-schools\/electrical-engineering-rankings?int=9a0108</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140610200245AA2KzDf">
	<title>Can I still get into college after getting a D in Chemistry ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>Or do I have to take summer school ???? - . -</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402456353000">You can because D is n't a failing grade . If I were you , I would go to summer school and at least get a B because you ca n't go to a good college if you have a D especially in Chemistry .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402540946000">You do n't have to go to summer school but I would recommend you re-take the course online over the summer or however you can do it , so that you do better and increase your GPA .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140611132742AAU8vAK">
	<title>Anyone willing to edit my personal statement ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>life of the orphanage as a whole . That is what I distinctly remember - aiding in the reconstruction of playgrounds and engaging with children who are __ ? __ ly undisguised . I was uncertain whether they would be able to recapture their innocence and hopefulness that most undeveloped children maintain until an appropriate age . And sure enough , these children had no other choice but to grow numb to the challenges life had in store for them and became sheltered from the outside world .</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I recall more than the unwashed bed sheets , broken picture frames and barred windows that consisted of the orphanage building located in an area where there were merely patches of grass on the ground , consisting mainly of dust and pebbles , on which children occasionally played what they liked to call ` football ' as a pastime , and where I , on my first missions trip , would find myself alongside a group of individuals playing a pivotal role in reshaping not only the lives of young children , but the</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>-LSB- It was obvious that their quality of life and health was inadequate and substandard in comparison to mine . -RSB- And even with the language barrier and the very little English that they spoke , the older children , in particular , were understandably hesitant to reveal or discuss the adversities they faced when I opened up to them . Throughout , I , uncharacteristically , found myself on the outside looking in . However , this time , I was able to -LSB- make something happen -RSB- in probably the most humbling ,</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I often stare outside my window late at night while laying in bed , on my stomach , placed right in front of the curtainless window that my concerned mother occasionally complains about . My mind roams freely at times like this when I submit myself to the alluring , ever-present , silver glow of the moon that seems to keep me up at night ; never quite failing to illuminate the enclosed space I 've always called my room and welcoming me , like an old friend , to yet another midnight stroll adventure - except in my head . A personality quirk that , understood by not too many , can be explained by my fertile , unquiet imagination that , in a way , makes me view what astronomers call stars as intangible , tiny , shimmery diamonds up in the sky that contribute to the overall effect and attractiveness of midnight . I seem to recall more than the bleak image nature created four years ago of a small community in Costa/LOCATION Rica/LOCATION , after the lives of many , including children as young as 8 and as old as 12 who were to become orphans , were lost or subjected to ridicule after a natural disaster . I recall more than the decimated village on a hill that a relentless tornado plowed through and had left abandoned - serving as sheer evidence of how the invisible , blunt , uncaring , crooked monster actually does exist and propagates disharmony in the world ; almost acting as a reminder of our finite existences .</content><suggestions>costa/LOCATION rica/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>defining moment of my life where intimate thoughts of life purpose , possibilities , and my group experience would , once again , creep in and cause me to aspire for something that transcends me and others . -LRB- to be continued ... . . -RRB- Stuff if brackets are what I do n't like in particular ... but i need some tweaking of the whole thing</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>\*\*\* stuff in brackets</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402519146000">\*\*\* Update : engaging with children who WERE</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140611114023AAQ6gKU">
	<title>What clothes do you take for a shower in a communal bathroom ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I 'm going into my sophomore year of college and freshman year , I had my own bathroom but hated the dorm I lived in , so I 'm moving to one that has a communal bathroom . There 's a shower with a curtain and a small space right outside of the shower that 's also curtained with shelves for putting stuff down . I ca n't seem to figure out what exactly people wear after showers there though , like do I just wear a towel or robe or what ? I have to walk back through the common area of my floor to get to my room , so I 'm not sure what to do and I 'm pretty shy . Also , if you have any other tips for communal showers , I 'd appreciate it ! I 'm definitely taking at least 5 pairs of flip flops already .</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I guess it 's not obviously stated anywhere in my question , but I 'm a girl , so the ` guys ' thing is n't especially applicable !</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402512106000">wear a bathing suit and tell people you were at the beach My advice applies to girls though ; -RRB-</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402512119000">use a robe until you see what the others are wearing</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402512405000">In the Army I just wrapped a towel around Myself . Being naked was no big deal since all the other Guy 's are also doing the same thing . Just do n't stare at the other guy 's junk because word will get out that You are Gay and that 's not as good thing in some places .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402512649000">Most guys will wear a robe , or shorts , or even just a towel . But wearing a robe would be good for most shy people , and completely acceptable . A terry cloth robe is probably the most covering .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402513305000">I do not</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402514312000">Well , I lived in a co-ed dorm . Girls generally wore full-length bathrobes to\/from .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402514677000">Wear a robe , street clothes , or opaque swimsuit coverup . Whatever makes you comfortable .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402518301000">I second the robe . That is what I always did for communal bathrooms and it was no big deal . Much more comfortable than putting on clothes when you 're still half wet -LRB- even the though makes me cringe -RRB- .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402581314000">That is what I always did for communal bathrooms and it was no big deal .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140611112422AAvMvFi">
	<title>How many milliliters do i give my patient ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>patient is to receive 25 mg of furosemide daily . available is 40 mg in 4 ml . So how many mL do i give the patient ? Answer is 205 mL but i keep getting 2.5 mL Was my teacher wrong ?</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402516733000">Yes your teacher was wrong .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402520269000">You are correct - 4ml \/ 40mg = 0.1 mg per ml 0.1 mg per ml x 25mg = 2.5 ml Now go correct your maths teacher !</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140608005945AABaB4R">
	<title>what the conditional form of -LRB- I 'm sorry I distyrbed you.I did n't know you were busy . -RRB- ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>My question is about conditional sentences.I do n't know how make it conditional.please help me .</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>My question is about conditional sentences.I do n't know how make it conditional.please help me .</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402249354000">I 'm sorry -LRB- if -RRB- I disturbed you . I did n't know -LRB- if -RRB- you were busy or not .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140607065516AACPRcP">
	<title>Why are earthen pots generally wrapped with a wet cloth ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>please give me a nice answer ... homework</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402154456000">http:\/\/wiki.answers.com\/Q\/Why_are_earthen_pots_wrapped_with_a_wet_cloth_during_summers?#slide=1</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402200222000">Explain in more detail please .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>

