<question id="20140610222206AAaaj3T">
	<title>Oil pipeline alternatives ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I 'm doing a project on pipelines and I ca n't seem to find many pipeline alternatives . More specifically alternatives to the proposed Kinder Morgan pipeline running from Alberta/LOCATION into British/LOCATION Columbia/LOCATION .</content><suggestions>alberta/LOCATION british/LOCATION columbia/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402464371000">I do n't know much about oil pipelines in the UK/LOCATION . But here in the USA/LOCATION -LRB- specifically the state of AZ/LOCATION -RRB- as an alternative to a pipeline , we are currently transporting oil by train . A pipeline would be prefered but it would be super expensive to build .</answer><suggestions>uk/LOCATION usa/LOCATION az/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402464550000">Kinder Morgan already has a pipeline running from AB to BC . Has been without incident for 50 years . This pipeline enables Canada to export one single tanker of oil per week . Otherwise , and in effect , Canada/LOCATION is a satellite , captive supplier to US and therefore must sell oil to US 15 % below market value . Canada/LOCATION makes transfer , welfare , payments to poorer provinces , most notably socialist ON and secondly socialist QC . By choosing to be a captive supplier , satellite , Canada/LOCATION makes a $ 20 Billion annual transfer \/ welfare payment to US and imports OPEC oil for most residents of Canada/LOCATION in ON , QC and maritimes at market cost . Alternative is to continue to transport oil by rail which has an exponentially higher risk of accident than the safest way , by pipeline .</answer><suggestions>kinder/PERSON morgan/PERSON canada/LOCATION canada/LOCATION canada/LOCATION canada/LOCATION canada/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402480541000">people should use Algae fuel which can be grown and produced locally . http:\/\/en.wikipedia.org\/wiki\/Algae_fuel</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402595757000">The alternative to get the Oil from Inland to the coast . Is barge up the Mackenzie/LOCATION River/LOCATION in summer . Truck on the highway or trains . Accidents do happen . Not very many happen with Pipelines . You never hear about all the days and thousands of pipelines in place for many years that have not had issues . Quebec/ORGANIZATION apposed a pipeline from Alberta/LOCATION too . So they send Money out of Canada/LOCATION to buy Foreign Oil at a higher price . We all know what happened to the train there and it was just an hours worth of oil in a pipeline . The alternative Pipeline routes all have the same issues . Run the pipeline just not in my back yard .</answer><suggestions>mackenzie/LOCATION river/LOCATION quebec/ORGANIZATION alberta/LOCATION canada/LOCATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140616152825AABP2iB">
	<title>Could Elliot/PERSON Rodger/PERSON have been helped , or was it inevitable ?</title><suggestions>elliot/PERSON rodger/PERSON</suggestions>
	<content>Going through a phase of intrigue at the moment about the Isla Vista 2014 killings . Just interested to hear your opinions .</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402982665000">Women today wo n't just have their boyfriend kick sand in a nerd 's face like back in the day . They want to make it about `` male entitlement '' crap . Probably it 's because jocks could care less what feminists think , so they 're starting to attack Aspies , etc. . In the old days , nerds were less medicated than today also . Nobody knew what autism even was in the 80s . They just thought that some guys were awkward like the Nutty Professor and laughed at the nerds . Now with nerds all overmedicated , you 're seeing kids who traditionally were non violent snapping . So the medical and psychiatric establishment blames it on something they call `` male entitlement '' which ca n't be defined well .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402983730000">He had a long history of mental illness and treatment for it . Certainly his family tried hard to get him the help he needed . But he was in very bad shape before the killing spree . His parents knew it and notified police . But the police could not find a reason to take him into custody . Laws make it extremely difficult to detain a mentally ill person against his will , even if he is obviously a danger to himself or others . Having said this , I do believe that this tragedy could have been prevented , and Rodger/LOCATION could have been helped , if certain conditions had been in place . If it better resources to monitor the welfare of the mentally ill , maybe he could have been persuaded to accept help of some kind before he put his plan into action . Also , if it were not so difficult to detain a dangerous mentally ill person , he might have been detained , and both he and his victims would be unharmed . I can not say whether he would ever have lived a normal life ; but it could have been better than it was .</answer><suggestions>rodger/PERSON</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140612075720AAmNq58">
	<title>Can you sue the news for not telling the whole story ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>For example , during the Bundy ranch situation , the news reported that he had made some racist comments about blacks and other minorities . However , there was n't any evidence to suggest that he was racist . In fact , there were videos of him talking positive about blacks and other people . The news left out this info . So my question is , can you sue them for leaving out truthful information ? Because I think this is the reason why stereotypes and misinformation gets spread around .</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402585124000">No , they only have so much show time to air , and other news stories to cover and the weather and sports .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402585278000">Of course not . Even if the story was about you , you could n't sue them . And if someone made racist comments , it would n't even matter if he had made other positive comments . That does n't cancel out the racist comments .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402585499000">It is not possible to sue a news organization unless they commit libel . And this is difficult to prove in the U.S./LOCATION , because a lot of what we might call `` news '' is actually couched in editorial opinion . The Supreme/ORGANIZATION Court/ORGANIZATION has said just within the past few month that it 's OK to lie about political issues because it is a First Amendment free-speech right to do so . Several years ago , the company that produced a Hillary/PERSON Clinton/PERSON documentary was given the green light even though a lot of it was untrue . Same thing about the Swiftboat anti-Karry campaign in 2004 and the egregiously false anti-Sea-World pseudo-documentary `` Blackfish '' . In addition , in order to sue , you have to prove that you are a party to the harm caused by the misinformation , which anyone but Bundy/PERSON 's family is probably not qualified .</answer><suggestions>u.s./LOCATION supreme/ORGANIZATION court/ORGANIZATION hillary/PERSON clinton/PERSON bundy/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402588087000">Nope .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402588455000">He literally said : ` Blacks were happier during slavery ' , that 's racist , that 's literally questioning a group of people 's rights , and ability of self-determination . So maybe you need to revise your opinion first , because you 're doing what you 're accusing the news of doing .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402590371000">You could only sue if it were slander . Reporting facts is n't slander .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402592411000">First , you ca n't sue a news station for omitting facts . Second , Bundy/PERSON was recorded saying pretty stupid things . And yes , they were racist . You can disagree with the assessment . But that does n't mean Bundy did n't say them , nor does it give you a right to sue for what the courts would label `` hurt feelings '' . That 's not meant to be a derogatory statement , there is a concept that you ca n't sue because you feel slighted or insulted and seek damages .</answer><suggestions>bundy/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402594416000">No</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140601022841AAeBUfq">
	<title>Syrian crisis - have more died from disease than other causes ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>Hi , I have found an article suggesting that more children have died from explosives than anything else in the current syrian crisis . in total , though , have more people died from disease or from other causes ?</content><suggestions>syrian/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401627520000">Still war casualties bullet , bomb , or plague .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401631606000">The barrel bombs must be taking quite a toll of children but last winter 's epidemics and lack of medicine would have contributed to an overall high number of dead kiddies</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140616154757AA3uubn">
	<title>in this lifetime , will britain ever be invaded by islamic terrorists ?</title><suggestions>britain/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>i just saw a question earlier with somebody reporting that islamic terrorists have threatened britain/LOCATION recently ? as i man in my late 30s this made me worry a bit ... . . what does anyone think ? will islam or muslim terrorist ever control britain/LOCATION within the next 10 years ?</content><suggestions>britain/LOCATION britain/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402959165000">Yes definitely bro . They said they would do it on facebook/ORGANIZATION so it 's inevitable . apparently they 're going to 911 part2 it 's going to be peak 4 man .</answer><suggestions>facebook/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402959526000">All muslims are n't terrorists , but their numbers are increasing every year , in every country they have immigrated to . It is only a matter of time before some want a career in politics , but it is unlikely they would have sufficient numbers to `` control '' Britain/LOCATION within a short space of time .</answer><suggestions>britain/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402960603000">They are already here in droves ! The ones under the name of moderate muslims are supporting the fanatical ones ! It 's one messed up religion ! Not sure if religion is the right word though .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402961427000">It 's Possible Our Armed/ORGANIZATION Forces/ORGANIZATION are being cut into nothing more than a tiny Defense Force , the lowest numbers they 've been at for well over 100 years , not that it was that big in the first place . Meanwhile , Islam/ORGANIZATION is the fastest growing Religion in the UK/LOCATION and Europe/LOCATION ... . . Mainly through Immigration and High Birth Rates , with those numbers , so increases the likelihood of Extremism . @Alan ; Looking at the Middle/LOCATION East/LOCATION for the past 10 + years , including recent events in Iraq , it looks to me like Islamic Militants are ` organised ' enough to take over whole countries , kill up to 3,000 people in a single incident and subvert from within - Trojan Horse ? `` Muslim Areas '' ? The US/LOCATION and UK/LOCATION sent Soldiers to fight these people in their own `` back yards '' in Iraq/LOCATION and Afghanistan/LOCATION , because if we ignore the problem and pretend everyone who says otherwise is a `` Right-Wing Racist '' , it will come to our own shores , eventually . -LRB- Marxists would like that -RRB- Objection to Islam is nothing to do with Race , many Muslims are ` White ' , so stick that card elsewhere ...</answer><suggestions>islam/ORGANIZATION uk/LOCATION europe/LOCATION middle/LOCATION east/LOCATION iraq/LOCATION us/LOCATION uk/LOCATION iraq/LOCATION afghanistan/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402964662000">I want to be kind here . So ... we have more chance of being ` invaded ' by ` The Mysterons ' than we do by any cohesive force of ` terrorists ' . Terrorism is a threat . It is nasty , dangerous and fundamentally evil ... but it is not an organised army capable of taking over Aldershot/LOCATION ... let alone the whole country . One clue is that we are not all speaking in Irish accents and drinking guiness for breakfast . The worst threat that terrorism poses for this country , is that we might all become the frightened bedwetters the right wing are . Fortunately , the British are historically brave , sensible and educated . The very qualities that the right wingers claim to value ... are the very qualities that they so conspicuously lack . It 's not so long ago that a British generation sacrificed so much in the fight against racist thugs ... do n't let the new ` brown shirts ' scare you into thinking they know anything . They are just as pointless , stupid and manipulative as their filthy predecessors . Luckily , most of us are n't so easily frightened into Frankenstein 's peasant type panic . Least of all by ` thumbs ' .</answer><suggestions>aldershot/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402964688000">anything 's possible , just pray they dont</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402981613000">Islamist terrorists will attack the UK/LOCATION within the next 10 years , but the odds are that they will not gain control .</answer><suggestions>uk/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402988457000">It would be interesting having a society based on hate .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402995176000">Making contact with a ore advanced civilization from another planet will shatter the foundations of all religious beliefs . People will then realize that our God concepts was a misinterpretation by ancient people who had extremely limited knowledge .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402996429000">Not an invasion , NO , but , there may well be more terrorism , because , like the Irish before them , the English will use and abuse Muslims and expect them to just take it without doing anything ...</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403001633000">No . Do n't think so .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403008825000">They will have their speradic attacks , but will never have control . They are inferior , their extremist ideology is pathetic , and when they start a war . . they lose . They think all their ` sacrifices ' will send them to a better place , in reality , they 'll just rot in the ground . Where they belong .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403072421000">Apparently , it 's something you 're looking forward to .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403098504000">Wake up dufus they are already here .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140617033632AAaS0SQ">
	<title>this is why people hate cyrus/PERSON and bieber/PERSON ?</title><suggestions>cyrus/PERSON bieber/PERSON</suggestions>
	<content>their eyes are close together under big brows . . see they look stupid and evil . its not necessatily true its just that we have a evolutionary instict to look out for some things . . like frogs scaring predators with fake eyes . . dont underestimate the impression of looks . . britney/PERSON spears/PERSON or lindsay/PERSON lohan/PERSON have normal eyes :-RRB- they get in trouble but nobody hates them</content><suggestions>britney/PERSON spears/PERSON lindsay/PERSON lohan/PERSON</suggestions>
	<content>making fun of peoples eyes is the worst i know . .</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403001573000">I just do n't like their music . Sorry to burst your bubble man .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403002974000">We love it because they have many good things as well .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403009219000">They 're douchebags and make some of the most ear bleeding , horrific music known to man .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403011301000">You are 100 % correct -- > it 's all about the eyes . Please click on the link below to find out more : http:\/\/vigilantcitizen.com\/category\/pics-of-the-month\/</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403021505000">Maybe but there are lots of other reasons . Old people who do n't relate to any young singers Jealous young people who feel like they 've accomplished nothing despite being older than Miley/PERSON or Justin/PERSON . Parents who are afraid their teens will copy Miley/PERSON or Justin/PERSON 's behavior . Amatuer music critics who thinks everybody stinks except who they personally think is worthy -LRB- yawn -RRB- . Morals police who do n't like how Miley/PERSON or Justin/PERSON act and think they are in any position to judge -LRB- yawn -RRB- . People who do n't like their eyes but I wonder , have they looked at their toes , too ?</answer><suggestions>miley/PERSON justin/PERSON miley/PERSON justin/PERSON miley/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403195517000">They are arrogant , conceited , and self-centred exhibitionists . They both show the evil effect of having too much money without the ability to handle it .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403291934000">nobody cares . . apparently those who go on endlessly about them have a crush in denial . now , find something purposeful to keep yourself occupied so you stop bugging us about these douchebags .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403294318000">GOD BLESS YOU ... ... ... \/ \/ .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403294677000">The same things have happened to them ! They 've fallen apart because of early childhood fame ! Sense they are pressured by society and media they tend to break loose and say `` f \*\*\* you '' to the paparazzi . Then they end up popping molly , smoking weed , and drinking , and partying . Only to be on TMZ the next day .</answer><suggestions>molly/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403294751000">The media keeps ramming them down our throats .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140607104637AASvvKI">
	<title>Whats the difference between a thatcherite and a tory eurosceptic ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>All all Thatcherites in the Conservative Party Euro Sceptic and are all Euro sceptics Thatcherite .</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402163597000">No , and No , , wash yer mouth out !</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402164122000">no no it 's Thatcherite and wet \/ \/ the wets are mostly dead along with left wing dinosaurs , lets not see their like again . . and you can do that by voting UKIP .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402165115000">Hmm , no difference . It is all fun . As long as they create a good story .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402174994000">Margaret/PERSON Thatcher/PERSON was herself what many would call a Eurosceptic , so it would follow to suggest that Thatcherites -LRB- those who admire\/d her -RRB- are Eurosceptics as well . Although I do n't think it follows to suggest that all Eurosceptics within the Conservative Party are Thatcherites .</answer><suggestions>margaret/PERSON thatcher/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402214165000">One has small boobs and the other big boobs . Otherwise , both do boobs a lots .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402226709000">There is a big difference . The EU/LOCATION today is nothing like that of twenty years ago .</answer><suggestions>eu/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402230396000">You should hang one by the ankles and the other by the throat , but I keep confusing the method ...</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140611114113AAerEfG">
	<title>how do the social know whats going on in the world ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I have a very serious question . say like a single mother in her own house with a one month old baby and decides to drown the baby in the bathtub on purpose . She doesnt call the cops or nothing . How can the news reporters know that crime happened ? How they actually find out that happened in that house ?</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402514422000">Sometimes they do n't . There are probably millions of these types of things happening everyday that go unreported . Normally , however , it might be a neighbor or a friend that finds out or the baby 's father . Sometimes the person might become cocky and just brag about whatever it is they did to the wrong person . The people tell the police and they go to arrest this person . If its a big enough deal the media might get wind of it and put it up . Of course some news people are very good at doing their own research . They may find criminal records or they may talk to people that knew the person as the story unfolds .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140626120744AAMAD0e">
	<title>Crimea/LOCATION incident ?</title><suggestions>crimea/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>Is it all over ? Someone summarize the aftermath ?</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403814282000">No . Vladimir/PERSON Putin/PERSON is cunning and uses trickery to his advantage . This thing is n't over . He wants us to think it is</answer><suggestions>vladimir/PERSON putin/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403816878000">the Crimean people begged to join The Russian federation and I bet they are so glad they did - look at the way the Poreshenco/LOCATION is bombing Ukraine citizens including children</answer><suggestions>poreshenco/LOCATION ukraine/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403825802000">Yes , it 's over for now . Russia/LOCATION 's ` got it ' now by 30,000 Russian troops on the ground in military occupation and a ` pro Russian referendum ' -LRB- at gun point -RRB- . On all earth only Zimbabwe/LOCATION , North/LOCATION Korea/LOCATION , and Russia/LOCATION recognize the Russian takeover of Crimea/LOCATION , every one of the other of 172 world countries and the hole UN rejects it . I 'll expect the Ukraine/LOCATION and world to be back and retake it in the future .</answer><suggestions>russia/LOCATION russian/LOCATION zimbabwe/LOCATION north/LOCATION korea/LOCATION russia/LOCATION russian/LOCATION crimea/LOCATION ukraine/LOCATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140613111831AABRhzn">
	<title>Did n't 0bozo say al/ORGANIZATION quada/ORGANIZATION was ` decimated ' ?</title><suggestions>al/PERSON quada/PERSON</suggestions>
	<content>http:\/\/www.dailymail.co.uk\/news\/article-2655977\/ISIS-militants-march-Baghdad-trademark-bullet-head-gets-way-control-north.html</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402684892000">Yes , during a campaign debate in 2012 , Obama/PERSON said al/ORGANIZATION Queda/ORGANIZATION in Pakistan/LOCATION had been decimated . The link you posted references events in Iraq/LOCATION and Syria/LOCATION . These are different countries than Pakistan/LOCATION and Obama/PERSON has not used the word decimated to describe groups in either of those countries . My point , al/ORGANIZATION Queda/ORGANIZATION is not one group like you seem to think , it is n't COBRA/ORGANIZATION . It 's more an umbrella term used by groups that think the answer to modern day problems lie in the solutions people found useful in the middle/LOCATION east/LOCATION around the year 800 .</answer><suggestions>obama/PERSON al/PERSON queda/PERSON pakistan/LOCATION iraq/LOCATION syria/LOCATION pakistan/LOCATION obama/PERSON al/PERSON queda/PERSON middle/LOCATION east/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402701250000">Obama/PERSON has said a lot of things that are n't true .</answer><suggestions>obama/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402731261000">`` Obozo '' . How cute . You made a silly with the presidents name . You are so clever .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402803680000">Libs/LOCATION must have forgot how they thought they were clever referring to Bush/PERSON as ` Shrub ' . Now they 're annoyed , especially since he is such a Bozo .</answer><suggestions>libs/PERSON bush/PERSON</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140623230739AA9pP9C">
	<title>How long before BBC/ORGANIZATION journalists are arrested for recruiting for ISIS ?</title><suggestions>bbc/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<content>The BBC/ORGANIZATION has seen fit to show photographs , ad infinitum , of British young men , who have chosen to fight for the group in Syria/LOCATION . Asked with the jail sentences handed down to the al Jazeera journalists in mind . .</content><suggestions>bbc/ORGANIZATION syria/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403623945000">Doubt if they will be but Sky News is just as bad .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140609103954AAB6LY5">
	<title>Moslems changing last names to Hispanic last names ... mmmm , I WONDER why ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I 'm sure they have no nefarious intent . To think so would brand me a racist . Lawsie , lawsie , do n't wan na be no racist . http:\/\/www.jihadwatch.org\/2014\/06\/texas-jttf-warned-that-middle-eastern-men-are-getting-drivers-licenses-with-hispanic-names#</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402336318000">Sorry but I still find it extremely amusing when I see your link is to something called ` jihadwatch ' `` To think so would brand me a racist '' That 's never stopped you before has it ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402337525000">After getting his butt kicked several times , all he has left is one drop . Those people do not want to be recognized as Moslims anymore . Who wants to belong to such an evil religion ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402338126000">To claim asylum ? To pretend not to be Muslim ? We have plenty in Britain/LOCATION claiming to be Italian or Greek .</answer><suggestions>muslim/PERSON britain/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402338491000">Having been to New/LOCATION York/LOCATION , Chicago/LOCATION and San/LOCATION Francisco/LOCATION in the last year , I can tell you that you need to speak Spanish in order to get a cup of coffee there . Maybe they are just trying to ` blend ' in ?</answer><suggestions>new/LOCATION york/LOCATION chicago/LOCATION san/LOCATION francisco/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402339449000">Probably the same reason Jews changed their names in droves to sneak into America/LOCATION & Europe/LOCATION , they are of course ` the chosen people ' however and free from condemnation by people who site a site created by a far-right Zionist/ORGANIZATION sociopath/ORGANIZATION</answer><suggestions>america/LOCATION europe/LOCATION zionist/ORGANIZATION sociopath/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402340995000">Many try to hide their madness , but it shows . Fifth column , , sneaky b ` stards . Supported by enablers , birds of a feather , and traitors .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402341268000">If this happens , then my guess would be to get jobs .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402342324000">Because Allah wills it ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402343429000">in my country they legally change their names to get jobs . For whatever reason , people are skeptical towards muslims .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140601100338AAUfBLz">
	<title>White flight from London/LOCATION ?</title><suggestions>london/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>Has multiculturalism done what the Luftwaffe could not ?</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401642686000">Really ? There 's still plenty where I live ! I 'm inclined to wonder if you actually live in London/LOCATION or have any first hand experience of its residents !</answer><suggestions>london/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401642891000">what write hitler/PERSON 's name in white smoke in the sky , ... the census does show a lot of native people have left the city i think it may be worth asking them why , there maybe a problem lefties are keeping secret , and their secrets are never good .</answer><suggestions>hitler/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401642941000">Well in the East End give it another 20 years or less . Bombed to b \* ggery in WW2 but not bowed or beaten , now being b \* ggered by a Bangladeshi mayor and council ! South/LOCATION London/LOCATION is seeing the flight of many immigrants as house prices have gone through the roof and they are selling up having made a huge profit on their properties .</answer><suggestions>south/LOCATION london/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401643730000">Well I 've bucked the trend and moved to London/LOCATION . And I know a lot of other Northerners Welsh , Scots etc who have done the same . You do wonder why these surveys never look at those moving to London/LOCATION , just those moving out . Because there are plenty of us . I may cash in on the property prices down here and move out , but for now I am staying .</answer><suggestions>london/LOCATION london/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401643788000">Have you been to London is the last few years , I take it you have not as if you have there would be no need to ask such a question . When ever I get the tube around London/LOCATION I am quite often the only white person out of 40-50 people . To see the effect of `` diversity '' look at the schools in London/LOCATION I would be surprised if in a class of 30 , 5 of them where white .</answer><suggestions>london/LOCATION london/LOCATION london/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401644177000">Yes , I left . Too much like North/LOCATION Africa/LOCATION crossed with Pakistan/LOCATION . Sold up , good profit , and headed South .</answer><suggestions>north/LOCATION africa/LOCATION pakistan/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401644595000">Are you sure it 's a `` white flight '' and not the simple fact it 's so expensive down there that drives people on really low incomes out if they can ? There are quite a few Londoners in the Midlands , but they 're not all white , I 'm pretty sure some Londoners have been housed by the social outside of London/LOCATION for cost purposes too .</answer><suggestions>london/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401646058000">multiculturalism is a huge failure and White Brits are now a minority in London/LOCATION and the lib\/lab\/con are not listening and I 'm quite lucky as I live in the North east and it 's really indigenous but I feel sorry for the people down South who feel like they live in a total different country . This is why I 'm voting UKIP in the general election . The last time I went to London/LOCATION was in 2009 and my mother kept on asking people for directions and they talked to us in a different language plus there was a lot of immigrants there because you could just tell and now in 2014 it 's probably worse . I see that there is 5 stupid lefty idiots who disliked my answer which is 100 % fact .</answer><suggestions>london/LOCATION london/LOCATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140609103348AAf8tZ6">
	<title>UK/LOCATION School teaches moslem students to call White women White Prostitutes . BTBloodyF ?</title><suggestions>uk/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>What is going on in Britain/LOCATION 's school system these days . Moslems are taking over schools and teaching them terrorism and hatred . All at the expense of the British taxpayer . This is a sorry state for a nation which once proudly sang that `` Britons never would be slaves '' ! Your grandparents , who beat the Germans , must be rolling over in their graves as you peacefully surrender your country to the moslem invaders . http:\/\/www.dailymail.co.uk\/news\/article-2651700\/Hellfire-Muslim-teachers-Trojan-Horse-school-warned-six-year-olds-white-prostitutes.html</content><suggestions>britain/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402336586000">The Muslim schools are in Birmingham/LOCATION and it does not surprise me because Birmingham has been swamped with immigrants . There are NO indigenous people in Birmingham/LOCATION anymore it 's like a total different country and it 's ashame because Birmingham/LOCATION used to be so nice but now it 's like Pakistan/LOCATION .</answer><suggestions>birmingham/LOCATION birmingham/LOCATION birmingham/LOCATION birmingham/LOCATION pakistan/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402337706000">Of course it is not true . Muslims treat non Muslims with respect . Women are valued . White women are therefore treated with double respect . Something must have been lost in translation . Wonder what the apologists will say ... deny the claims I suppose . My friend works in a neighbor school - close to the ` Trojan horse schools ' , she , like many if the white staff , are being driven out . One of the Muslim staff she works with announces that Allah/PERSON is the one true God and the governors want Muslim teachers to ` celebrate ' diversity . She tells me that subjects not touched all year are now being tagged in to the curriculum ... RE not Islam and an end to assemblies where children are shipped into a frenzy praising Allah and Mohammed . A six year old told her all Christians go to hell and ` dirty Christians ' is a form of gig played by the children . Just yesterday she had to report a six year old girl for threatening to behead another child . Someone somewhere us poisoning the minds of children and the apologists are in denial .</answer><suggestions>muslim/PERSON allah/PERSON muslim/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402341194000">Islam is , was , and always will be The Enemy . Proof has been available , and ignored , covered up , and denied , for decades .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402438387000">Britain/LOCATION 's school system ? There 's no such thing . Britain/LOCATION is a multi-nation state with more than one education system . `` This is a sorry state for a nation ... '' What nation ? You do n't say ? Do you even know ?</answer><suggestions>britain/LOCATION britain/LOCATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140612233000AAOudfw">
	<title>my period did n't come on yesterday it comes on every month on the 12 what should i do its a day late ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>Every month on the 12th</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402641276000">There are `` Exceptions '' to Every Rule ... So I 'd wait until Sunday to `` worry '' about it . - UNLESS there 's something ELSE You 're worried about - here ... : o</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402647107000">Give yourself a day or two . This is not unusual .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402647315000">you can call 911 so they can bring you your periods</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402655866000">if it comes on the 12th every month that means you dont have a regular 28 day cycle , or indeed a regular cycle at all as each month the days vary so you can not be late at all if it came 12th feb then 12th march , that was a 22 day cycle 12th march to 12th April would be a 31 day cycle 9 days of a difference so how can you possibly know you are late with such an erratic cycle ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402670342000">The 12th of each month can fall anywhere between 28 and 31 days apart so you 're regular within a window of 4 days each month . Give it three more days at least before you call 911 .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140612211617AAE6Bis">
	<title>can someone tell me who ISIS are in iraq/LOCATION ?</title><suggestions>iraq/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>after the news anouncing some terorist group is launching a insurgency in iraq/LOCATION im varey curious are they somehow related to al-qaida ? or are they diferent all together ?</content><suggestions>iraq/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402633253000">It 's like another form of Al/ORGANIZATION Qaeda/ORGANIZATION .</answer><suggestions>al/PERSON qaeda/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402635452000">The Islamic State of Iraq/LOCATION and Syria/LOCATION -- the Sunni jihadi organization that was once part of Al/ORGANIZATION Qaeda/ORGANIZATION -- has effectively gained control of large swaths of Iraq/LOCATION and Syria/LOCATION over the past year .</answer><suggestions>iraq/LOCATION syria/LOCATION sunni/ORGANIZATION jihadi/ORGANIZATION organization/ORGANIZATION al/PERSON qaeda/PERSON iraq/LOCATION syria/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402645884000">Just another manufactured excuse for muslims to kill . They really are equal ops murderers . This is apparently a sunni shia squabble . PEACE be upon them ??? What a massive LIE .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402655391000">Google/ORGANIZATION is your friend .</answer><suggestions>google/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402673682000">They need a taste of Templar justice . I would give the Kurds a nation cut our of Iraq/LOCATION , after all it was created in that manner by the victorious Ottoman Turks in the 13th century , and was not always this way . The Kurds are the onlypeoples in that nation that have shown they will gladly give their lives for freedom , so start backing them , not the morons in Bagdad/LOCATION .</answer><suggestions>iraq/LOCATION bagdad/LOCATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140605150717AAmRFk6">
	<title>Why do people say the Koch/ORGANIZATION brothers/ORGANIZATION are evil ?</title><suggestions>koch/ORGANIZATION brothers/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<content>A guy at my job was going off on the Koch/ORGANIZATION brothers/ORGANIZATION today . To be honest , I do n't know much about them . This guy was saying that they want to destroy the United/LOCATION States/LOCATION . He said they support the Tea Party . But George/PERSON Soros/PERSON gives millions of dollars to liberal organizations . Is he evil also ? I have a feeling liberals will say the Koch brothers are evil , and George/PERSON Soros/PERSON is good . Conservatives will say the George/PERSON Soros/PERSON is evil and the Koch brothers are good . Who should I believe ?</content><suggestions>united/LOCATION states/LOCATION george/PERSON soros/PERSON koch/ORGANIZATION brothers/ORGANIZATION george/PERSON soros/PERSON george/PERSON soros/PERSON koch/ORGANIZATION brothers/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402007240000">If you ca n't sort out why people are against the Koch/ORGANIZATION brothers/ORGANIZATION and their attempts to hijack the American government , then there is no sense in trying to explain it . Start with Citizens United/ORGANIZATION Supreme/ORGANIZATION Court/ORGANIZATION decision and go from there .</answer><suggestions>koch/ORGANIZATION brothers/ORGANIZATION american/LOCATION united/ORGANIZATION supreme/ORGANIZATION court/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402018049000">The people that complain about the Koch brothers are gullible , weak minded brain dead liberals and they worship rich communist America/LOCATION haters , such as George/PERSON Soros/PERSON and Michael/PERSON Nanny/PERSON Bloomberg/PERSON .</answer><suggestions>koch/ORGANIZATION brothers/ORGANIZATION america/LOCATION george/PERSON soros/PERSON michael/PERSON nanny/PERSON bloomberg/PERSON</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140620051059AAvmrsV">
	<title>How did John/PERONS Coates/PERSON become the vice president of the IOC ?</title><suggestions>john/PERSON coates/PERSON ioc/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<content>Doing an assignment , need to find out ASAP . Thanks in advance !</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403282205000">He was anointed by the members of the society .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140618215915AAruZzF">
	<title>Why did the white man become such a pussy ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>After years of being verbally abused by my wife , last week she finally punched me in the face . I told my father and he said my stepmother has been hitting him for years . We both laughed and bonded a little from this moment . If a black guy cuts me off in line I say `` No , no , go ahead I can wait , you go first . '' Why not stand up for myself you ask ? Because I have been raised to allow women and minorities to beat me down and push me around , for I am a white sexist , devil . Is it the media were I see black men always portrayed as 6 ' 5 300 pound men with large penises and white men as small , weak , geeky and with small penises who are always afraid of there own shadows . TV shows like Everybody Loves Raymond shows Raymond on the floor curled up in the fetal position as his wife stands over him waving her clenched fist and yelling at him as the studio audience laughs and laughs . Why it is `` the trend '' in the world now is to bash white men for being white and if it is this bad now , how bad is it going to be 50 years from now ?</content><suggestions>raymond/PERSON raymond/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403154357000">What goes around , comes around ! There was a time -LSB- the 1700 s - 1900s -RSB- when the blacks were ill-treated by the whites . Today , the Kala-chakra is turning . The blacks are showing up as BIG , black hulks who spit invectives around and dominate the snivelling white men . Do n't worry . The Wheel-of-Fortune will turn again , and 50 years from now things will again be different . This is the Law of Nature .</answer><suggestions>kala-chakra/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403155128000">It 's not a trend . Bashing is primitive and pathetic . Portrayals in all media vary . Plenty of white action movie stars . Plenty of white porn stars . Many T.V. comedies rely\/have relied on a henpecked husband for cheap laughs . I ca n't imagine feeling pushed around simply because I let someone in front me in a line . Small potatoes , man . In the big scheme , meaningless .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403155211000">So white men should be forced onto reservations or into concentration camps ? And maybe we should line our white women in rows up and down the streets in the black ghettos naked and in the doggystyle position , so black men can mount them when they please . And when they begin to hump on our white women from behind the girls can read from a script that says `` Sorry white men were cruel to blacks 500 years ago . I give you my vagina and butt-hole as a way to say sorry for all we have done . '' Is that what comes around goes around means ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403156227000">well said GI and its true but thats all society and entertainment the real story lies in your spirit who you are what you think any one who judges you or stereotypes dont give a moments thought itt 'll give you a migrain thinking down at their level your wife matbe you should be more kind to and give the respect she deserves i mean where would you be without her ? and courtesy thats not being beat down you shoud be thankful you have that quality its a gift if more would show it the world would be a lot better place i commend your ability to put the other man first as for the shows on tv they target -LRB- profile -RRB- thier audience and write a script to uplift the fan base and all others are victimized its fantasy laugh when its funny or shut it off your not forced to watch it just rethink your outlook you got the rest peace your welcome -LRB- in advance -RRB-</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403156542000">If a big duded wanted to treat me or any other person even if white , I would just disappear , and never look or talk to them ever , as to me they would not be good enough , why would they be my friend anyway . Toughness does not get my friendship . And what man hits a woman , no man , and if she hits me , I will be gone , who needs a boxer for a woman , no Thankyou .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403157244000">his a good guy</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403162448000">Life does n't happen in isolation from history , everything we experience happens because of historical perceptions . The white races have benefited disproportionately from the world 's resources , and from the political and social organization of it 's richest societies . Men have always held dominant positions over women , in every aspect of life . Owning property , having a vote , employment and even base physical strength . None of the above excuses abuse . Indeed we have laws against such abuse for good reasons , but these laws often seem to be in conflict with what people perceive as the historical ` norm ' . Your good manners in giving way in a queue , are being distorted in your perception ... and turned into weakness on your part . Your feeling of powerlessness in the face of your wife 's aggression is probably as much to do with you 're not being a wife beating thug as anything else . The fact is , you sound like a decent and moral person . ` Doing the right thing ' is always difficult . It is frustrating , and it can even be painful at times . The one thing it most definitely is not ... is weak . Telling your Dad must have been difficult , but again ... you did exactly the right thing . It takes moral courage to ` stand up ' to a situation without resorting to the behaviors that created them in the first place . If being decent is being a ` pussy ' ... then I am a ` pussy ' as well . I hope you find a way to confront your wife 's ` problem ' -LRB- I 'm not saying simply accept it -RRB- ... but I think you already know that resorting in kind is not only wrong ... it is dumb . As for being polite and well mannered , yes . Sometimes it can make you feel like a ` doormat ' ... but being ill mannered , boorish or selfish is not going to make you sleep better at night . Get over it . Your a decent bloke !</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403165854000">I do n't think all white guys have become weak . It may somewhat correlate with ethnicity . Remember , not all white people are the same . Some people in some parts of the country are more `` followers '' than others and have tuned them into the way society and liberalism tells them they should be . Others are still more natural and not following of such trends .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403166162000">Perhaps Jesus was a mixed bag . Ya know , both good and bad .</answer><suggestions>jesus/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403166516000">You take the abuse , that makes you a sissy . Your dad had an influence on you that made you that way . You grew up with Ray Romano , I grew up with Clint Eastwood . Nobody cuts in line on me .</answer><suggestions>ray/PERSON romano/PERSON clint/PERSON eastwood/PERSON</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140615161422AAiDhFt">
	<title>What 's the best radio station here in California ?</title><suggestions>california/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>DJs also talk about Interesting topics \*\*</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>Or any state really . A station where , aside from playing music , the DJs also talk about interesting music</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402884845000">You ought to know better , but you 're doing it anyway . KPIG/ORGANIZATION , Freedom/ORGANIZATION , California/ORGANIZATION</answer><suggestions>kpig/PERSON california/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402911299000">I think it 's K-Earth/ORGANIZATION 101 FM -LRB- KRTH/ORGANIZATION -RRB- in Los/LOCATION Angeles/LOCATION. , as far as music is concerned .</answer><suggestions>krth/ORGANIZATION los/LOCATION angeles/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403486062000">I saw an article the other day about this , let me check my history real fast and I will get back with the link</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140609053527AAHPrln">
	<title>Why the ` different tone ' adopted for convicted killer Louise/PERSON Woodward/PERSON ?</title><suggestions>louise/PERSON woodward/PERSON</suggestions>
	<content>http:\/\/www.dailymail.co.uk\/news\/article-2652334\/Woodward-devoted-mum-Former-nanny-smiles-proudly-five-month-old-daughter-mothers-wedding.html I find it strange that they are so positive towards her when she was convicted of the manslaughter of a defenceless baby . I mean yuck , I 'd rather not have to see her enjoying herself , although people have a right to move on after serving punishments . I notice though , that they still hate Maxine/PERSON Carr/PERSON , despite her not killing anyone .</content><suggestions>maxine/PERSON carr/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402318719000">Oh look it 's the Mail stirring things up again . I think they choose to portray Louise/PERSON Woodward/PERSON as an innocent young victim of nasty foreigners -LRB- those evil Americans -RRB- whereas Maxine/PERSON Carr/PERSON , being home convicted , is a criminal .</answer><suggestions>louise/PERSON woodward/PERSON maxine/PERSON carr/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402320372000">I remember at the time the media portrayed a poor little English girl abuse by the nasty Americans , a bit like the Americans did with Amanda/PERSON Knox/PERSON</answer><suggestions>amanda/PERSON knox/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402321372000">Not only that ... but the comments are almost in ` love ' with her , growling at the DM , asking why this ' ... is news ? ' All in all , such stories are made to have humourless and ignorant people to rush onto free-for-all sites and spew their comments . There was one who reminded all that Ms./PERSON Woodward/PERSON was convicted of manslaughter ... and for his troubles , was given 310 thumbs down ... and only ninety thumbs up . Of course ... as it went , people were more interested in what she looked like today , snarling at ' ... how she had aged ' . Dat/PERSON 's yer Mail ... obviously WAG 's are not rising to bait so near to the World Cup , so the Mail are rolling out an old stormer . They may be good at winding up Britons -LRB- as is their wont ... especially working class - as was -RRB- , but Carr/PERSON was up for a shorter sentence ... and all the scuzzy section of the media at the time was trying to find out where she was going to end up on release - did they not terrify her side of the family . She was charged with perverting the course of justice , was it not - having not been with Ian/PERSON Huntley/PERSON when he murdered the girls . He lied to her and she believed he had nothing to do with the murders . Obviously the tabs wanted her to be ` lifed ' up also !</answer><suggestions>woodward/PERSON dat/PERSON carr/PERSON ian/PERSON huntley/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402322012000">The prejudices and biases of The Daily Fail -LRB- and it 's readers -RRB- are impossible to fathom - so I dont bother The Fail is glorified toilet paper .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402327513000">You really must try harder to stop yourself from reading that newspaper . I wonder how many people go and top themselves after their morning fill of it ? Manslaughter is different to Murder and collusion in Murder . Granted the last thing you want is a child minder who just loses it .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140621045509AAck6mP">
	<title>With glorious hindsight how many ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>Iraqis now long for the days of the rule of Saddam/PERSON . How in God 's name can we claim to have given these poor people a better democratic life ?</content><suggestions>saddam/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403352475000">that is the fundamental flaw of the right wing remember globalisation ? capitalism does not do humanity nor society ask thatchers son , mark , why was he involved with regime change ? to benefit the people ? remove the rule of law from the uk/LOCATION and you still have british values remove greed and money from the right wing and all you have left is a hollow vessel</answer><suggestions>mark/PERSON uk/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403355516000">Saddam has always been held in high regard by rank-and-file Iraqis . The conservative perspective that the US would be hailed as liberators was always a lie .</answer><suggestions>saddam/PERSON us/LOCATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140611214724AASfT7e">
	<title>Do you agree with this gentleman that Obama/PERSON works out like a sissy ?</title><suggestions>obama/PERSON</suggestions>
	<content>https:\/\/www.youtube.com\/watch?v=mYdSp6u9TYo</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402548646000">Name calling wo n't help the GOP/ORGANIZATION win elections . First they have to end their civil war with the Tea Party .</answer><suggestions>gop/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140606223938AAjsrL7">
	<title>Sports News - Pro Football - The/ORGANIZATION New/ORGANIZATION York/ORGANIZATION Times/ORGANIZATION ?</title><suggestions>new/LOCATION york/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>http:\/\/www.wholesalesoccerjerseyser.com\/ Find breaking NFL/ORGANIZATION news , multimedia , injury reports , trades and signings , the AFC/ORGANIZATION and NFC/ORGANIZATION , the football draft , the coaches and the players and team standings .</content><suggestions>nfl/ORGANIZATION nfc/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402122104000">futball</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140614113251AA3Y1WB">
	<title>I wish i was a girl ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>The clothes the them being friendlier than guys to each other the being able to be emotionals . I would honestly strive to be a model if I was a girl just blows being a guy</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402771796000">In my experience it is n't always plain sailing . That apparent friendliness of `` Sisterhood '' can all too often come laced with the same sort of toxicity that taints the relationships between men . The health problems can be a bit of a pain too . I agree about the clothes . Men 's clothes are often boring . However we are spared that issue of deciding what to wear . Men can slap a suit on , look fine and will be accepted at just about any event . Women have to choose from a myriad of dresses , skirts , etc. . If they get it wrong -LRB- even in their head -RRB- then the event is spoiled for them . I 'm glad I 'm a dull gray bloke , with a few friends , who I can just be me with .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402772153000">What , have you ever tried wearing stilletto heals , tights which itch , tops which show it all when you lean forward and skirts which are always the wrong length ?? Give me boyish jeans and t shirt -LRB- even though I can never find a pair of decent fitting jeans , all too big at the waist or too small in the hip -RRB- any day of the week !</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402772475000">Perpetual competition , comparing , posing , and regretting ?? No thanks , I 'll enjoy the results of the competition , without the stress of entering it .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402772754000">Wow Err , the football 's on , get yourself a beer and tune in</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402773386000">yes so do i ... i would have my hand down my knickers all day ... lol ...</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402774116000">You have no idea how hard it is being female . We are not nice people ... especially if there is someone who is prettier , better dressed , smarter , or skinnier than us . . and can turn into the most spiteful vindictive witches ever . There is always a sense of never being good enough , pretty enough , thin enough , smart enough -- and all it takes is one cute guy to turn us into an even bigger mess . We never know what to wear , what to say , or how to act around boys . And then there is the whole period thing , and having babies , and menopause ... all of which are hormonal based situations that have us females acting even crazier than we already are . We have to shave our legs , underarms and spend an awful lot of time trying to remove unwanted hair from our chins , necks and chest areas . You should try waxing your eyebrows or bikini area ... owie !!!!!! We can never decide whether our hair should be long or short , and are always unhappy with it 's texture , length , fullness , and color no matter what we have been born with , do we wear it up or down or curl it or straighten it . So you see -- being a girl is not easy ...</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402777847000">You mean like the British woman who went for a medical and the doctor told her , `` your pulse , blood pressure and heart are fine , now let me see the part that get you women into all sorts of trouble '' . The woman starts to take her knickers off and the doctor said , `` no , no leave your knickers on , I want to see your tongue '' . Oops sorry girls !</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402782281000">Women are n't always that friendly to each other ... ! They can be vindictive to each other when they fall out , and they hold Grudges for a long time , when we just forget the Next Day or something , or they just hate each other for no reason ... But at least they 're -LRB- usually -RRB- Nice to Men ... God help you if you ca n't work out how they 're Feeling when they 're being as Vague and Difficult as humanely possible ...</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402782766000">I agee with u Mr/PERSON , Tom/PERSON do whatever u want ! and I still be one even with child birth because that would mean I could still have kids : -RRB-</answer><suggestions>tom/PERSON</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140613180332AA3jCxr">
	<title>ISIS/ORGANIZATION and Al/ORGANIZATION Qaeda/ORGANIZATION ?</title><suggestions>isis/ORGANIZATION al/PERSON qaeda/PERSON</suggestions>
	<content>I 've been watching the news all day with all of the chaos that is going on with Iraq/LOCATION -LRB- praying that USA/LOCATION does not get involved AGAIN and that other countries will -RRB- . Anyways , I was curious to know more about ISIS/ORGANIZATION and Al/ORGANIZATION Qaeda/ORGANIZATION . Are they really enemies with each other ? Also , I hear that ISIS/ORGANIZATION wants to take over Iran/LOCATION too ? That ca n't possibly happen , right !?!</content><suggestions>iraq/LOCATION usa/LOCATION isis/ORGANIZATION al/PERSON qaeda/PERSON isis/ORGANIZATION iran/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402710402000">infowars.com</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402713427000">God has to start getting involved with religion . After all , who are they based on ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402733040000">Google/ORGANIZATION is your friend .</answer><suggestions>google/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402789803000">We in the US/LOCATION are so uniformed by our media -LRB- me included -RRB- I want to cry . Today on US/LOCATION media news are reports of such things like the ` Stanley Hockey Cup Finals ' , and Lindsay/PERSON Lohan/PERSON 's bra breaking , usual US/LOCATION tabloid ` junk ' like that . As far as I can piece together from ` real news ' foreign sources like ... BBC/ORGANIZATION America/ORGANIZATION ... AL/ORGANIZATION Jazeera/ORGANIZATION America/ORGANIZATION ... The ISISL/ORGANIZATION are ... Sunni ... 1 . -RRB- From Wahhabi/LOCATION Arabia/LOCATION . 2 . -RRB- They ` are ' Al/ORGANIZATION Qaeda/ORGANIZATION but just changed their name and now Saudi/LOCATION Arabia/LOCATION says they are a different group . 3 . -RRB- The ISISL/ORGANIZATION and Al/ORGANIZATION Qaeda/ORGANIZATION are not enemies but apparently ` allies ' . 4 . -RRB- Iran/LOCATION is ` Shia ' and is fighting the ` Sunni 's ' like crazy for Iraq and Syria/LOCATION too . 2 . -RRB- It 's been reported ISISL/ORGANIZATION are the ` jihadist ' fighters in Syria who have been fighting in Syria in the civil war 4 years now , now they are moving on to Iraq . 2 . -RRB- It has been reported from these two media sources -LRB- above given -RRB- ISISL have cut off 1700 human heads of men women and children in Iraq . 3 . -RRB- That they have taken Iraq/LOCATION 's cities of ` Mosul ' and ` Kirkuk ' . 4 . -RRB- They are now marching on Baghdad for final victory they claim .</answer><suggestions>us/LOCATION us/LOCATION lindsay/PERSON lohan/PERSON bbc/ORGANIZATION america/LOCATION al/PERSON jazeera/PERSON america/LOCATION wahhabi/LOCATION arabia/LOCATION al/ORGANIZATION qaeda/ORGANIZATION saudi/LOCATION arabia/LOCATION al/PERSON qaeda/PERSON iran/LOCATION iraq/LOCATION syria/LOCATION syria/LOCATION syria/LOCATION iraq/LOCATION iraq/LOCATION iraq/LOCATION mosul/LOCATION kirkuk/LOCATION baghdad/LOCATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140620214550AA74tKP">
	<title>Wtf was that incident between Kanye west and George/PERSON W./PERSON Bush/PERSON ?</title><suggestions>kanye/LOCATION west/LOCATION george/PERSON w./PERSON bush/PERSON</suggestions>
	<content>I saw a videos wich Kanye said : `` George/PERSON Bush/PERSON does n't care about black people '' that was true ? he said that on live tv ? when happened this ?</content><suggestions>george/PERSON bush/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403332077000">Yes it 's true , Kanye/PERSON said that . It was just after Katrina hit , and FEMA was no where to be found . In fact , Bush/PERSON was `` on vacation '' and was n't even aware that the hurricane had hit New/LOCATION Orleans/LOCATION . Definitely a low point in a presidency full of low points .</answer><suggestions>kanye/PERSON fema/ORGANIZATION bush/PERSON new/LOCATION orleans/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403379697000">The look on Mike/PERSON Myers/PERSON ' face on that telethon was just absolutely priceless . However , Kanye/PERSON has proven to be a whiny crybaby throughout his career . I remember his throwing a tantrum when Gretchen/PERSON Wilson/PERSON beat him out for New Artist at the American Music Awards .</answer><suggestions>mike/PERSON myers/PERSON kanye/PERSON gretchen/PERSON wilson/PERSON</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140615131345AAW89pT">
	<title>Price for Fault In Our Stars ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>The movie ` The Fault In Our Stars ' comes out in UK/LOCATION cinemas tomorrow , me and a few friends want to watch it - I am unaware how much it would cost for a childrens ' ticket . I am assuming it would be more expensive to watch as I am watching it the day it comes out . Any ideas how much it would be ?</content><suggestions>uk/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402868423000">Each cinema sets their own price and some do special two for one deals . Best contact your local cinema and ask them .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402906217000">Best to call and ask . Prices depend on the day of the week you go and the time .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140625210906AATgayM">
	<title>Naming my school newspaper help !?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>So my school mascot is the Knights , and I need help naming my school newspaper . I ca n't figure out a catchy name ! And it ca n't be the Knightly News because we have online video news called that . Thank you !</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403755916000">The Commons ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403756197000">Does it have to have the word `` Knight -LRB- s -RRB- '' in it ? What about -LRB- School Name -RRB- Gazette or Times ? What about using words like Chronicle or Journal ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403803650000">How about `` The Round Table '' ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403830568000">`` Knight & Day ''</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140617191218AAiEBHA">
	<title>Democrats and republicans : agree or disagree ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>The news we should trust is on NBC/ORGANIZATION , CBS/ORGANIZATION and ABC/ORGANIZATION . Not FOX/ORGANIZATION or MSNBC/ORGANIZATION . Those two are both just opinions</content><suggestions>nbc/ORGANIZATION cbs/ORGANIZATION abc/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403057702000">I do n't trust anything on the news .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403059676000">Disagree ... NBC/ORGANIZATION , CBS/ORGANIZATION and ABC/ORGANIZATION and all owned and operated by Democrat donors . Can you name one anchor on any of those 3 networks who is NOT a Democrat ? Fox News is run by moderates ... They just seem right-wing to the low-information voter because all the other networks are so extremely left-wing . Most Fox interviews include a host , one Republican and one Democrat . I rarely see any real Conservative on any network other than Fox .</answer><suggestions>nbc/ORGANIZATION cbs/ORGANIZATION abc/ORGANIZATION fox/ORGANIZATION news/ORGANIZATION fox/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403061859000">Disagree , FOX/ORGANIZATION News/ORGANIZATION actually presents fair and balanced news . While it 's talking heads are primarily conservative , FOX/ORGANIZATION clearly identifies which programing is news and which is opinion . The other news sources do not , and MSNBC/ORGANIZATION is the worst offender . They present their twisted views as fact , and ignorant liberals actually believe them , regardless of the truth .</answer><suggestions>fox/ORGANIZATION news/ORGANIZATION fox/PERSON msnbc/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403062793000">They all give you BS . Cancer is now the No. 1 killer in the US/LOCATION . Who is telling them not to report on it ?</answer><suggestions>us/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403063127000">There is no NEWS NETWORK anywhere , it is all opinion.Look at fox/ORGANIZATION news/ORGANIZATION , there are 3 clowns sitting there.All you get is opinion , a man on the right and a man on the left and in the middle we have a chick exposing her legs.That is what we call news .</answer><suggestions>fox/ORGANIZATION news/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403085571000">presents fair and balanced news</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403092377000">...</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403220530000">wegwgwrgwrge</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>

