<question id="20140611011232AAoHyfn">
	<title>is anyonw else getting weirded out by how similar this years Finals is to last ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I mean right down to the game 3 blowout</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402475734000">yup , I expect the same result as last year</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402475938000">except this time surely Leonard/PERSON will hit the foul shots and and if he does n't surely Miami/LOCATION wo n't make that big play with Bosh/PERSON and Allen/PERSON</answer><suggestions>leonard/PERSON miami/LOCATION bosh/PERSON allen/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402488965000">That 's right . There are interesting coincidences . The difference is that the Spurs/ORGANIZATION have home court advantage . I 'm not sure if they can take advantage of it though .</answer><suggestions>spurs/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402501349000">Despite losing , Spurs/ORGANIZATION outplayed Heat last year and again this year . But unlike last year , odds are Allen/PERSON wo n't hit `` the shot '' and Spurs/ORGANIZATION wo n't let it slip through their fingers . The Spurs/ORGANIZATION wo n't shoot as well as they did in game 3 and Lebron/PERSON wo n't be turning it over every other possession but if the Spurs keep it up , it should be Spurs in 6 .</answer><suggestions>allen/PERSON spurs/ORGANIZATION spurs/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140625083610AAU2r7X">
	<title>why are players accompanied by children in international matches ? 10 points ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>well i know FIFA/ORGANIZATION has a tie up with Mcdonalds/ORGANIZATION ! but why do cricket players bring the children !?</content><suggestions>fifa/ORGANIZATION mcdonalds/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403777611000">This is the soccer section not the cricket section .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140615190410AAmWDg3">
	<title>mfs in all honesty what is something you really want to buy ?</title><suggestions>mfs/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<content>i hope @rolando/PERSON can answer this</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>if i had the money id buy a house with a huge garage and have speakers strobes and lazers bumping house and trance music in the garage and inside the house loud ! bq : mexico vs brasil bets ? no weenie bets</content><suggestions>mexico/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402884373000">Dude , if I had the money i would buy a garage that pops up out of the ground and have a hidden area with cars .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402884663000">If I had the money I 'll buy a car</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402884782000">If I had money I would live in another country .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402885218000">I would probably go with a Patek/PERSON Philippe/PERSON wristwatch/PERSON . A world clock cloisonne to be exact .</answer><suggestions>philippe/PERSON wristwatch/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402886918000">I will buy muchas putas and a big red truck</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402892691000">Super Smash Bros 4 Wii U & 3ds</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140606003853AAp4Kid">
	<title>Full Metal and customizable M4 Airsoft AEG ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>- Metal R.I.S System - Metal Body -LRB- Upper Receiver & Lower Receiver -RRB- - Metal Fixed Stock - Metal Barrel - Metal Gearbox - Metal Pistol Grip - Metal Trigger & Trigger Guard -400 FPS -LRB- With The Change Of One Item -RRB- -350 FPS -LRB- With The Change Of One Item -RRB- -300 FPS -LRB- With The Change Of One Item -RRB-</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402074651000">No gun comes with a metal pistol grip and very few come with metal stocks , there are no metal full stocks . That does not exist . It does n't make the gun hardly any stronger and makes it dramatically more uncomfortable , expensive , and heavy . All airsoft AEGs can change their fps by changing one part . Quick change spring systems allow this part to be more easily accessed .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402100053000">All you have to do is go to a airsoft website and search m4 I 'm sure you will find one you like . http:\/\/www.airsplat.com\/items\/ER-XL-AK47-0507.htm this is the gun I 'm about to get but the website is pretty good and might have what you want</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140601162630AAuDjDG">
	<title>` Help get Pepe/ORGANIZATION laid/ORGANIZATION foundation/ORGANIZATION ' , would you like to donate ?</title><suggestions>pepe/PERSON</suggestions>
	<content>just # 2 a month should do , the more people the better . We need to find him a wag as soon as possible , he 's taking obsession to a whole new level , Mert/PERSON > Ramos/PERSON</content><suggestions>mert/PERSON ramos/PERSON</suggestions>
	<content>you have the nerve to answer my question after blocking me @you know who you are . . cheeky</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401665459000">Where can I sign up ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401665680000">That sounds a great charity GROOVY !! NICE !!!</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401665791000">just cos i am on here on a Sunday evening stating my opinions , and you are on here on a Sunday evening sucking up and disagreeing with me , doesnt negate the fact we are both in the same place on a Sunday evening if anythin u need to get laid since u are looking for allies and company on YA by asking this lmao , how sad is that , why couldnt u talk to me alone even tho its just the net . . ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401665917000">Read the Sun .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401668104000">I always give Blood to blood banks does that count ???</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401668491000">My uncle is a congressman , I could get him a pardon or two that he could take to the womans prison . . Maybe he could get some there</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401668822000">i 've said it before i 'll say it again anyone who uses the word laid has themselves never had any p \* ssy , anyone who attacks someone else 's sex life does so because they are insecure about their own , otherwise they wouldn ; t even see it as an insult i would bet that pepe/PERSON has been laid many times , he 's a cool funny guy</answer><suggestions>ssy/PERSON pepe/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401668951000">I always love to give lol .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401683531000">take more than # 2 a month</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401709979000">I would be willing to help get Pepe/ORGANIZATION laid/ORGANIZATION .</answer><suggestions>pepe/PERSON</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140612160340AAE8W0E">
	<title>Why do you always lie KW ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>GET OFF MY QUESTION KW !!! AND GET OFF YOU FAKE ASS BITCH !!!! DUMBA$ $</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>Everything you say is a lie KW . Why are you such a phony . If you fought me in real life I 'd show you that traditional arts are better than your shit fucking BJJ . pussy .</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402614897000">Wow , one of the many kw accounts I have blocked flipped to my name . Why are you so despite kw that you have to use my name now ? Your such a loser , trying to discredit me this way . And by the way dumba $ $ I train in bjj , I 'm just more open minded then you . My account is older then yours , Mine came first . perhaps you should have used an older account kw you dumba $ $ . You must really be despite kw , what an ego you have to sooth Edit - Im not the troll kw you are , you have over 20 accounts including the one asking the question , you know full well you just changed the name today on that account . Wow all my blocked kw accounts are changing names and answer this question . This is too funny . What an ego kw has to ask and answer his own question , How despite he is for our attention .</answer><suggestions>bjj/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402615251000">Are you really trying to copy my name ? I do n't know who you are ? But I 'm blocking you , fake \*\*\*\*\* . You 're probably KW , you fucking liar . Get off my question . edit - You 're such a liar . Your profile is one of the many blocked accounts I have . why do you keep changing your name ? tell me your address you pussy . ill fight you any day of the week . your such a dumba $ $</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402615401000">Jesus/PERSON , this is a hornets nest of trolls . Do you guys really have nothing better to do ? It looks like the troll 's are turning on one another though ... Whoever either of you are , you 're all f \* cking stupid . This is a waste of everyone 's time .</answer><suggestions>jesus/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402616377000">KW do you have some butt hurt or what . What 's wrong , is it there is n't enough questions about you that you have to change your troll account names . What a fuc \* ing idiot you are that you think we are fooled by this sh \* t. Edit Thanks for blocking me kw . In response to your comment : : It seems to me YOU should stop renaming your accounts after other trolls . I have those trolls blocked I also have your alts blocks and a little while ago your other accounts changed their names . You are a complete and total fool if you think we do n't realize what you are doing</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402616773000">KW IS A FAKE , THIS IS ALL FAKE . EVERYONE IN HERE IS FAKE BUT ME ! I BET IT 'S ALL KW . THAT LOSER HAS NOTHING BETTER TO DO .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140605104442AAFzzy2">
	<title>Professional Wrestling : How would Bray/PERSON Wyatt/PERSON being involved in The Money In The Bank match make sense ?</title><suggestions>wyatt/PERSON</suggestions>
	<content>People are saying that Bray/PERSON Wyatt/PERSON should be in the Money In The Bank match and win the whole match . But how would that make sense , I mean John/PERSON Cena/PERSON Vs Bray/PERSON Wyatt/PERSON at Payback showed Bray/PERSON Wyatt/PERSON can keep comin ' but would winning Money In The Bank make sense for his character ? It would have to be a cash in on the champion on the same night like Kane situation would n't it , you ca n't really see Bray/PERSON Wyatt/PERSON carrying the Money In The Bank briefcase around . Then again , more then likely Daniel/PERSON Bryan/PERSON wo n't be ready for Money In The Bank . So , The Money In The Bank match becomes a WWE World Heavyweight Champion Six-Man Ladder Match ; now that I can see Bray/PERSON Wyatt/PERSON winning .</content><suggestions>bray/PERSON wyatt/PERSON john/PERSON cena/PERSON wyatt/PERSON bray/PERSON wyatt/PERSON kane/PERSON wyatt/PERSON daniel/PERSON bryan/PERSON wyatt/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401990585000">I think you asked and answered your own question . Bray/PERSON Wyatt/PERSON can win a Money In The Bank Qualifying Match and qualify for the match . The most recent Last Man Standing Match showed that Bray/PERSON Wyatt/PERSON can dish out punishment and take punishment . I do n't realistically think Daniel/PERSON Bryan/PERSON 's Neck would be fully healed by July , so I could see Daniel/PERSON Bryan/PERSON being stripped of The Tihe WWE World Heavyweight Title and The 2014 WWE Money In The Bank Match Winner would be Th eNew WWE World HEavyweight Champion .</answer><suggestions>bray/PERSON wyatt/PERSON bray/PERSON wyatt/PERSON daniel/PERSON bryan/PERSON daniel/PERSON bryan/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401990817000">I disagree ... It could work . Maybe they could have Luke Harper or Eric/PERSON Rowen/PERSON carry the briefcase around for him ? I do n't think it would look that weird . But I do n't think Daniel/PERSON Bryan/PERSON 's neck injury will be fully healed by Money in The Bank , at which case it will be a Championship match . Personally I would rather see Cesaro/PERSON or Seth/PERSON Rollins/PERSON win the Title , but Wyatt/PERSON should definitely get a shot somewhere down the road . Besides Wyatt is young so he 's got plenty of time left for a World Title .</answer><suggestions>luke/PERSON harper/PERSON eric/PERSON rowen/PERSON daniel/PERSON bryan/PERSON seth/PERSON rollins/PERSON wyatt/PERSON wyatt/PERSON</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140620105746AAnOLsk">
	<title>What are some good single action only handguns that are n't revolvers ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>Something like the Beretta Billennium .</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403288318000">Colt 1911 , Browning P-35 to name a couple</answer><suggestions>browning/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403289062000">1911 Browning Hi-Power</answer><suggestions>browning/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403289605000">Thompson Contender .</answer><suggestions>thompson/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403289931000">Hmmm ... Luger ? Since the Walther guys came up with DA autos , the market has moved that way . Other than the 1911 & Hi power ; there really are no mass market SA autos . Desert Eagle maybe ?</answer><suggestions>luger/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403290589000">.</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403291262000">AutoMag , Smith & Wesson Model 52-1 ... oh wait , you said GOOD single action autos ... How about the Wildey ?</answer><suggestions>smith/ORGANIZATION &/ORGANIZATION wesson/ORGANIZATION model/ORGANIZATION wildey/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403291989000">1911 's</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403293034000">CZ 75B SA</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403293275000">Sig Sauer P220 Carry SAO</answer><suggestions>sig/PERSON sauer/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403296049000">The Ruger MK series are a pretty great SAO pistol .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403296597000">Springfield XD</answer><suggestions>springfield/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403299240000">the beretta billennium ...</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403300082000">any 1911</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403320719000">Nearly all semi-automatic pistols made in the past 100 years are single action . The double action models never really ` took off ' . From the 1911 to FN FiveSeveN , to the XD ... ... most all your top semi auto pistol are single action . Instead of having everyone list 100 's and 100 's of single action pistols - a much , much shorter list would be double action pistols that are not revolvers .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140626150225AAeTpqG">
	<title>What lakes or ponds are there around victoria/LOCATION tx ?</title><suggestions>victoria/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>I moved to Cuero/LOCATION , TX which is close to Victoria/LOCATION and I want to know some local fishin spots for Bass specifically .</content><suggestions>cuero/LOCATION tx/LOCATION victoria/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403822009000">google/ORGANIZATION map is your friend , all that blue stuff is water .</answer><suggestions>google/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140615215028AAGmoaM">
	<title>Who to start for pitchers , fantasy baseball ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I have 10 pitchers and 12 total starts . I am projected to have 16 total starts and I do n't know who to bench and when . I have : Hisashi/PERSON Iwakuma/PERSON : June 20 @ KC Max/PERSON Scherzer/PERSON : June 17 vs KC & June 22 @ CLE Jered/PERSON Weaver/PERSON : June 16 @ CLE & June 22 vs TEX Johnny/PERSON Cueto/PERSON June 17 @ PIT & TOR Cole/PERSON Hamels/PERSON : June 16 @ ATL & June 21 @ STL Hyun-Jin/PERSON Ryu/PERSON : June 16 vs COL & June 22 @ SD Anibal/PERSON Sanchez/PERSON : June 19 vs KC Andrew/PERSON Cashner/PERSON : June 18 vs SEA Gio/PERSON Gonzalez/PERSON : June 18 vs HOU ? Justin/PERSON Verlander/PERSON : June 16 vs KC & June 21 @ CLE I was thinking of benching Justin/PERSON Verlander/PERSON twice , Anibal/PERSON Sanchez/PERSON for his start , along with Andrew/PERSON Cashner/PERSON .</content><suggestions>hisashi/PERSON iwakuma/PERSON max/PERSON scherzer/PERSON jered/PERSON weaver/PERSON johnny/PERSON cueto/PERSON cole/PERSON hamels/PERSON anibal/PERSON sanchez/PERSON andrew/PERSON cashner/PERSON gio/PERSON gonzalez/PERSON justin/PERSON verlander/PERSON justin/PERSON verlander/PERSON anibal/PERSON sanchez/PERSON andrew/PERSON cashner/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403007019000">Leave/PERSON Casner/PERSON in - his home\/away splits are insane . Verlander/PERSON you ca n't trust at all right now - so that 's 2 -LRB- if you benched him yesterday -RRB- . I 'd also sit Weaver for 2 -- but if you started either Weaver/PERSON or Verlander/PERSON yesterday I 'd sit Hamels/PERSON v. the Cards .</answer><suggestions>casner/PERSON verlander/PERSON weaver/PERSON verlander/PERSON hamels/PERSON</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140623155342AAYpGzf">
	<title>Are there any silent basketballs ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I 'm wondering if there are such things as silent basketballs or if they are possible at all . For example I 've seen the superball commercial from last year by bridgestone/ORGANIZATION where they had an absolute silent basketball . You can see the commercial here : https:\/\/www.youtube.com\/watch?v=LB94Xee7ED4 I did some research and found out that you can buy it here : http:\/\/performanceballandpuck.com\/ Do you think it would work ? I 'm sure it would n't be as in the video , but as long as it pretty silent I 'm happy . Are there any other options on the market or is it simply do n't possible ? Thanks in advanced !</content><suggestions>bridgestone/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403565126000">But why ? Unless you have a hoop in your third floor apartment I do n't see why this would be necessary . It will change the game if adopted or NCAA/ORGANIZATION or NBA/ORGANIZATION ; and not to it 's betterment .</answer><suggestions>ncaa/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403566401000">No</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140617223537AAdlxEL">
	<title>Why oh kind sir why cricket is the sport of peace , love and broterhood , what 's your say ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>Peace and love rules ~</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403069996000">Yes its a gentleman 's game ... love and peace ~</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403071364000">Because it is the best sport ever . Crickets play with honor footballers fight like animals with each other for a ball</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403072040000">it has less fights than other sports</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403073453000">Snow , Lillee , Marshal , Croft , Larwood et al.l</answer><suggestions>lillee/PERSON croft/PERSON larwood/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403081097000">Because it is the best and also gentlemen 's game</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403086535000">It 's the gentleman 's Game .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403100569000">less fights than other sport</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403180880000">methinks this is standers game than any other game . The system of playing and impress anyone and for this we all love cricket very much .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140611135954AABR99L">
	<title>Is it possible to start by the team that drafts you in nba2k14 current gen ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I been playing for the bobcats for a long time and I 'm still not starting will I be able to start on this team or should i ask for a trade ?</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402525532000">The story is scripted . No matter how good you are you 'll have to wait to be a starter . My guy was a 98 rated SF and I sat on pine for about 15 games waiting for real minutes</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402529167000">I thought that was only for next gen</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140620150504AApqU99">
	<title>Scammed on FIFA/ORGANIZATION 14 ! What do I do !?</title><suggestions>fifa/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<content>I got scammed today and where do I go for advise ?!?!</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403302540000">How did it happened ? Well I got scammed too about two months and I came on here to ask for help so they gave me this old man 's email contact which I did and he did a spell for me and the person returned my money within 7 days . You can reach him too eledasanumi@gmail.com I 'm sure he will be ready to help you as well .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140618180738AANfMh9">
	<title>USA/LOCATION WINS : WHAT DO YOU THINK ?</title><suggestions>usa/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>2014 World Cup Soccer Cheap Jerseys Wholesale , Big discount for sale include cheap nfl nike jerseys , nba/ORGANIZATION\/mlb/ORGANIZATION\/nhl/ORGANIZATION cheap jerseys , cheap snapbacks free shipping from china/LOCATION . if you want to buy the soccer football jerseys , you can see the site : http:\/\/www.cheapsoccerjerseyser.com\/</content><suggestions>cheap/ORGANIZATION nfl/ORGANIZATION nike/ORGANIZATION china/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403264079000">I have dealt with this amazing seller for some time without any problems . They are competent and fast response . Very glad to deal with them .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403472303000">of course this one http:\/\/www.mlbjerseyoutlet.com</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403530932000">I actually have bought from this excellent seller for a long time and never have any problems . They are competent and quick response . Quite glad to deal with them .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140611211016AAM5YLk">
	<title>Is a 5.2 forty yard dash decent ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I am a sophomore in high school and I play TE\/LB and I am 5 ' 9 '' 174 pounds</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402555618000">Yeah . Too bad you ca n't do it fat boy .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402591427000">its not that great to be honest .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402595001000">For your size no for my size yes</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402614271000">Stop lying , you fat phony . You are n't even a football team . Poser . Loser .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402685607000">No it 's not good I 'm a -LRB- SS -RRB- I 'm 6ft and weigh 175 I 'm about to be a junior and I run a 4.72 and that still sucks</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402754282000">Give us some more information .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140604025700AAoSHAT">
	<title>arabs enter race to sign boyd ?</title><suggestions>boyd/PERSON</suggestions>
	<content>with the arabs now joining the sheep and the zombies for boyds signature who do you see as favorite to sign the goal scoring sloth</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401878801000">If he was smart Aberdeen/PERSON ... He will not go near greyskull/LOCATION thats for sure , he was glad to see the back of it . .</answer><suggestions>greyskull/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401902867000">sloth you say he 's still putting them where the count , is this not why yo employ strikers , wit do want someone who runs around like a mad bastart for 90 minutes then score 4 goals a season ... Rabbit & Toirtoise ...</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140617195809AA0PD6g">
	<title>Truly deep down , do you actually care about Spanish club football or is it just one team ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>Does the location of the club you support actually mean anything to you whatsoever ? Do you support the players from your club when they are playing at international level ? Do you have any knowledge of your opponents in the league apart from Real , Atleti/ORGANIZATION and Barcelona/ORGANIZATION ?</content><suggestions>barcelona/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403060721000">This is a glory hunting question .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403066078000">All I care about is Ronaldo/PERSON : -RRB-</answer><suggestions>ronaldo/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403074229000">I care about spanish league but mainly because of RM .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403125493000">The location yes . But i support both Real/ORGANIZATION Madrid/ORGANIZATION and Spain/LOCATION and will continue to do so . I watch , but do n't support , the players from Madrid/ORGANIZATION in their respective national team , like CR7 's Portugal/LOCATION , Khedira 's Germany/LOCATION , Di Maria 's Argentina/LOCATION , etc. . . and i do n't know much of other players that play for spanish clubs . Most are either Spanish players who are not deemed good enough to play for Spain/LOCATION or the same but for other countries .</answer><suggestions>madrid/LOCATION spain/LOCATION madrid/LOCATION portugal/LOCATION khedira/PERSON germany/LOCATION di/PERSON maria/PERSON argentina/LOCATION spain/LOCATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140601130859AAHxybZ">
	<title>MFS : Who 's going to win next weekend -LRB- Boxing Fans -RRB- ?</title><suggestions>boxing/ORGANIZATION fans/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<content>Between Miguel/PERSON Cotto/PERSON y Sergio/PERSON Martinez/PERSON ? If Cotto/PERSON is aggressive & does n't get tired like he did when he fought Margarito/PERSON , Pacquiao/PERSON & Mayateweather/PERSON I give Cotto/PERSON a good chance to win . I would love to see Cotto/PERSON or Martinez/PERSON & Canelo/PERSON fight in November after Canelo/PERSON beats the Cuban/PERSON Mayate/PERSON he 's fighting in July .</content><suggestions>miguel/PERSON cotto/PERSON sergio/PERSON martinez/PERSON margarito/PERSON pacquiao/PERSON cotto/PERSON martinez/ORGANIZATION &/ORGANIZATION canelo/ORGANIZATION canelo/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401653569000">I do n't really care who wins between Cotto/PERSON and Martinez/PERSON , but Cotto/PERSON is slow so I think Martinez/PERSON will pick him apart and KO him . . As for Canelo/PERSON he will beat the shit out of the Cuban . Canelo/PERSON is the p4p best fighter in the world .</answer><suggestions>cotto/PERSON martinez/PERSON cotto/PERSON martinez/PERSON canelo/PERSON canelo/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401654251000">I think martinez/PERSON wins by a brutal KO in the 9th round</answer><suggestions>martinez/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401654635000">I think Cotto/PERSON wins UD maybe even TKO . Sergio is up there and his last fight he was n't moving around like he used to . Maybe because of the surgeries he had , but I think its age . I got Cotto/PERSON .</answer><suggestions>sergio/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401656030000">Martinez/PERSON will win . Mark/PERSON my word . -LRB- ;</answer><suggestions>martinez/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401656117000">Soccer foo</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1401663861000">Martinez/PERSON . Experienced , fast , used to fighting at 160 . Cotto/PERSON is new to the division and might not handle the weight well</answer><suggestions>martinez/PERSON cotto/PERSON</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140626152929AAvb2mt">
	<title>SFS/ORGANIZATION world cup predictor forgot to say ... ?</title><suggestions>sfs/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<content>It occurred in Wossys predictions where he predicted a penalty shootout win , I 'll only be taking into account the first 90 minutes no matter what the outcome . Funnily enough Eck/PERSON said I should have mentioned that beforehand and I forgot , its came back to bite me on the arse now .</content><suggestions>eck/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403822009000">Afraid a member of the Wolf Pack will win your poxy predictor , are we ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403822171000">What is it that you are talking about . There is not even a question .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403822827000">I assumed it would be the 90 mins anyway .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140607094147AAMHfCN">
	<title>Where can I watch the Cotto/PERSON vs Martinez/PERSON fight toonighy ?</title><suggestions>martinez/PERSON</suggestions>
	<content>Restaurants or bars</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402159970000">Hey Friend Jimmy/PERSON Here ! Watch Live Coverage Here http:\/\/www.watchtheboxing.net\/ Cotto/PERSON vs Martinez/PERSON Live Boxing Live IN HD</answer><suggestions>jimmy/PERSON cotto/PERSON martinez/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402161845000">What 's your location ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402162638000">Watch Cotto/PERSON vs Martinez/PERSON Live Streaming No Ads Live At http:\/\/www.watchxboxing.com\/</answer><suggestions>watch/PERSON cotto/PERSON martinez/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402208885000">Give us some more information .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140614220006AA90c02">
	<title>Norinco m14 ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>Was recentley offered a Norinco M14 new for $ 525 . I do not know alot about this rifle , so any info on it is much appreciated . Accuracy , reliability , wheight ????? I really like this rifle because it is `` non-restricted '' meaning I can shoot it anywhere not just in the range like most semi-auto rifles here in canada . I plan to use it for coyotes and just shooting out to 400 or so yards . Do you think this rifle is suitable for this or should I buy a Weatherby Vangaurd S2 for $ 599 ? Thanks again : -RRB-</content><suggestions>norinco/ORGANIZATION canada/LOCATION weatherby/ORGANIZATION vangaurd/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402811102000">You said you know a lot about the rifle . How much do you know about the Weatherby Vanguard ? Personally I do n't think you can go wrong with a bolt action rifle . Yes , the M14 has been proven as a rifle in the service of the US/LOCATION Armed Forces from Nam to now but did Norinco do it justice with their model ? On the other hand , it could end up being beneficial to stick with what you know . I 'm a shooter but I have a bad habit of being stingy . And lazy . At least with the M14 you have iron sights , which I will give you the benefit of the doubt and say you can handle a 400 yard shot with , and do n't have to buy and zero and optics . Either way , I love the feeling of a new gun purchase . It 's like being a little kid on Christmas morning again .</answer><suggestions>vanguard/ORGANIZATION us/LOCATION nam/ORGANIZATION norinco/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402811261000">Chinese made Semi auto copy of the Late '50s US/LOCATION Service Rifle . You can buy a better quality version From Springfield Armory . Overly big & heavy for hunting use .</answer><suggestions>springfield/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402829033000">The Norinco M14 is a good gun . Quality is good and it is fun to shoot . Norinco is one of the worlds largest arms manufactures in the world so when people say it is Chinese and it is s@#t they have no idea what they are talking about . The only thing is if it comes with a wooden stock change it .</answer><suggestions>norinco/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402839186000">Quality on the Norinco rifles including the M-14 -LRB- actually an M1A -RRB- is\/was hit or miss . I knew of a few riflesmiths who liked them enough to use them in builds after they disassembled them and heat treated the receivers . Unlike a lot of the anything Norinco cheerleaders I 've owned and worked on the products from them , sometimes they -LRB- Norinco -RRB- get it right and sometimes they screw it up with shoddy work\/quality control . For what it 's worth I 've had NIB S&W Revolvers I 've sent back to the factory because of a lack of quality control so it 's not just Norinco . The rifle itself is heavier than I 'd prefer for walking around hunting but that 's me . The price you quote is fair enough that 's I 'd sure as heck buy it if offered to me , if you do n't like the rifle I do n't think you 'll lose money if you decide to sell it later .</answer><suggestions>norinco/ORGANIZATION norinco/ORGANIZATION norinco/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402842330000">At some point in history , US/LOCATION gave their M14 machines to various countries around the world . One such country is China/LOCATION . It 's built to somewhat of spec or near spec to GI . Problem is material and craftsmanship of the rifle in whole . You 're looking at a hit or miss with mostly hits on a Norinco . The problem is since the importation ban in the US/LOCATION , the gun is getting to be somewhat of a `` collectors '' item in the US/LOCATION . In Canada/LOCATION they are still being imported for now but who knows what will happen in the future . That 's the reason why a lot of folks think Norinco is the `` best '' because it 's rare and sold at somewhat of a premium . It 's still a Chinese piece of junk to me and anyone else who wants a US/LOCATION made rifle made by US/LOCATION company . However some people think the M1A is too pricey by Springfield/LOCATION , Fulton Armory , etc so they go the cheap route . In the end , you get what you pay for .</answer><suggestions>us/LOCATION china/LOCATION norinco/ORGANIZATION us/LOCATION us/LOCATION canada/LOCATION norinco/ORGANIZATION us/LOCATION us/LOCATION springfield/LOCATION fulton/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402846761000">Short answer ? get the Weatherby or some other similar rifle from one of the others . All Canadian centerfire semi-autos are limited to 5 rounds -LRB- which is why I sold all of mine -RRB- The Norinco M-14 will not perform like a varmint rifle ... so PLEASE do n't consider `` pimping that ride '' like kids do with their M\/N 's . If you simply want to plink and have fun ... get an SKS ... for $ 200 online or at a store near you . -LRB- they also come with the integral -LRB- non-pinnable -RRB- 10 round mag ... nudge-nudge ... wink-wink . -RRB- Cheapeast and easiest gun \/ ammo combo to get . Try Canada/LOCATION Ammo and see what their package is selling for . My local store had a package deal of gun and 1440 rounds for less than $ 500 total ... out the door .</answer><suggestions>cheapeast/LOCATION canada/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402932515000">Springfield/LOCATION M1A 's , New , are still available . If you look long enough and hard enough . Last year at a gun show in Reno I found one new in the box NM M1A . For that level rifle I could n't count out the $ 2000 fast enough . Good Luck</answer><suggestions>springfield/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403250434000">I went on a site on this topic but ca n't remember the name , If I 'll remember I will let you know .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140611153858AAK05v1">
	<title>is Climbing Roofs Easy ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>Can you easily climb roofs -LRB- ex . Walmart/ORGANIZATION , house -RRB- ? Is it safe or dangerous ? Can you get in trouble from it too ? Are roofs meant to be climbed on or no ? Do people climb on peoples roofs for fun , Or they do n't ? Thanks , Pete/LOCATION</content><suggestions>walmart/ORGANIZATION pete/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402526708000">it 's not that hard , and no it 's not safe , and yes you can get in trouble because it 's privet property , no their not , and no ppl do n't climb roofs for fun .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402543634000">I 've been paid to service rooftops day and night in all weather . I used what are called CORKERS in icy conditions and state law requires roof employment employ workers trained in use of fall-arrest systems . I 've seen work terminated by the state for threat to life and other employee abuse . Feel free to dine in cockroach infested restaurants if you want to ignore work laws . The work made me fit and skilled enough to obtain public sector hire and I retired after more than two decades . I 've also enjoyed BUILDERING . I like sculpture . You find that in urban parks .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402609184000">More info please</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140623022611AAddTaJ">
	<title>WWE/ORGANIZATION VS UFC/ORGANIZATION 6 MAN TAG ?</title><suggestions>ufc/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<content>WWE/ORGANIZATION : Kurt/PERSON Angle/PERSON , Undertaker/PERSON , Big/PERSON Show/PERSON UFC/ORGANIZATION : Brock/PERSON Lesnar/PERSON , Frank/PERSON Mir/PERSON , Benson/PERSON Henderson/PERSON</content><suggestions>kurt/PERSON angle/PERSON brock/PERSON lesnar/PERSON frank/PERSON mir/PERSON benson/PERSON henderson/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403516252000">Am I , the only person here that does n't give a single solitary ... about Ultimate/ORGANIZATION Fighting/ORGANIZATION Championships/ORGANIZATION ?</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403516548000">I do n't watch ufc/ORGANIZATION so I only know brock/PERSON lesnar/PERSON , but I do know those 3 wrestlers & I think besides kurt/PERSON angle/PERSON , the wwe side would get bullied .</answer><suggestions>brock/PERSON lesnar/PERSON kurt/PERSON angle/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403522586000">Brock/PERSON Lesanr/PERSON was overrated . Frank/PERSON Mir/PERSON was overrated . How about Cain/PERSON Velasquez/PERSON , Jon/PERSON Bones/PERSON Jones/PERSON and Benson/PERSON Henderson/PERSON destroy Kurt/PERSON Angle/PERSON , The/PERSON Undertaker/PERSON and The/PERSON Big/PERSON Show/PERSON in The Octagon ? How about the fact that Kurt/PERSON Angle/PERSON is the only Professional Wrestling in your grouping with an Amateur Wrestling Background .</answer><suggestions>brock/PERSON lesanr/PERSON frank/PERSON mir/PERSON cain/PERSON velasquez/PERSON jon/PERSON bones/PERSON jones/PERSON benson/PERSON henderson/PERSON kurt/PERSON angle/PERSON kurt/PERSON angle/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403531020000">In WWE Angle/PERSON , Undertaker/PERSON and Bigshow/PERSON would have a better chance of winning .</answer><suggestions>bigshow/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403532538000">WWE easily , especially since Big/PERSON Show/PERSON is on WWE 's team .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140616120632AA6Yeah">
	<title>How long does it take to get called up to the MLB/ORGANIZATION in MLB/ORGANIZATION The Show ?</title><suggestions>mlb/ORGANIZATION mlb/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<content>I am a shortstop in the Angels organization . I lead the league in average as a double A starter with a .389 average and 4 HRs and 62 RBIs . I got called up in June and in AAA , i hit for over .400 with 11 HRs and 80 RBIs . Now in the next season , I get sent down to AA while the people worse than me are in AAA . It is super frustrating and I want to know how much longer I have to wait !</content><suggestions>aaa/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402954181000">Until hell freezes over . Or at least until you exist whichever comes first . The only AA player with the Angels to post those numbers in the last five years was some guy named Trout and I think he has been called up .</answer><suggestions>angels/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140613182418AAAZN2I">
	<title>Why is Zeb/PERSON Colter/PERSON saying negative things about Big E. and him waving the American flag , yet chooses to ignore Rusev who hates America/LOCATION ?</title><suggestions>zeb/PERSON colter/PERSON american/LOCATION rusev/PERSON america/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>Makes no sense whatsoever . None . I really do n't get it . Does he not watch the product ? Does he not see what Rusev and Lana say about America/LOCATION and everything Zeb/PERSON Colter/PERSON and Jack/PERSON Swagger/PERSON stand for .</content><suggestions>rusev/PERSON lana/PERSON america/LOCATION zeb/PERSON colter/PERSON jack/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402709430000">Lol , that 's a good point , WWE/ORGANIZATION does n't make sense sometimes , I guess he does n't mind them being here .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402709455000">He might say negative things about Rusev now that Lana made Swagger lose .</answer><suggestions>rusev/PERSON lana/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402753756000">Because Big E lost to Rusev and Zeb/PERSON Colter/PERSON will use that to say Big E is a disgrace to the U S of A.</answer><suggestions>rusev/LOCATION zeb/PERSON colter/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403077844000">Explain in more detail please .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140618123245AAiwouS">
	<title>what games are the ones to watch ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>What are you looking forward to : -RRB- Also whos your team and why : -RRB-</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403121024000">Looking forward to England/LOCATION and Uruguay/LOCATION to see you bounces back from defeat , Germany/LOCATION\/Ghana/LOCATION to and USA/LOCATION\/Portugal/LOCATION since I am an American and I want our American\/German hybrid team to do well .</answer><suggestions>england/LOCATION uruguay/LOCATION</suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140615120927AAPeVv5">
	<title>New/LOCATION Jersey/LOCATION hunting questions ?</title><suggestions>new/LOCATION jersey/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<content>I am 16 , if that makes a difference . I want to go hunting with my dad this year . I will be using my own gun , which is a 1968 12ga Browning A5 . This will be my first time hunting and I have some questions When is the deer season in NJ ? What rounds should I use ? -LRB- Buckshot , Slugs , etc -RRB- Do you really need camo clothes ? Thank you</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402860074000">If your dad is a hunter you need to talk to him . If not you both need to go to hunters ed and get a copy of the hunting regualtions . Question # 1 . Look at your regs . Question # 2 Slugs as long as they are legal according to your states hunting regs Question # 3 Depending on the states hunting regs , you might be required to wear hunter orange . Some states -LRB- AZ -RRB- do n't require it , some do .</answer><suggestions>ed/PERSON az/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402860278000">You do not need camo clothing . Most states require you to wear certain amount of square inches of hunter safety orange . Archery hunters are the ones who need to get in close and they use camo quite often . When you buy your 2014 hunting license and deer tag you will get a copy of the regulations - or - you can download them from your official state web site . Since hunting can be opened or closed by emergency order - you really should download them and book mark the website . This way you can check for any changes in the regulations . You need to take your shotgun to the local range and ` paper it ' . If you are very accurate with slugs - then that is the ticket . But if you gun shoots slugs all over the place and buckshot gives you a sweet pattern then you would want those . Me - I bring both . It 's not a case of cake or pie and you can only have one slice . I load slug , buckshot , slug , buckshot for open areas and buckshot , slug , buckshot , slug , buckshot for close in areas . Some people will load two slugs and then one buckshot - the ` idea ' being they can get fairly precise shots off and if they miss and the deer is running or just wounded the buckshot makes it easier to hit the thing on the run that with a slug . This is most definitely where doing practice at the range alternating between the two to see how good you are with pays off . Practice . And remember - it is 10,000 times better to practice a ton of time for just a few rounds - then only a few times shooting a ton of rounds . Getting a deer means your first shot of the day is what counts - so - when you show up at the range and your first shot sucks - that means you are not ready . Deer are not gon na let you fire half a box of ammo to warm up . You need to practice so your first shot of the day is a good shot - that is what matters . Good Luck !</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402861057000">All that info will be in the copy of your regs ... that you get when you buy a Hunting licence ... however , just google/ORGANIZATION your State and download a copy ...</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140619060021AAhU4hr">
	<title>Excruciating pain after throwing ball ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>I 've played softball since I was 8 . Just over the last year or so every time I throw the ball I have excruciating pain in the shoulder , mainly on the back side . Also my arm gets a shooting pins and needles feeling and my arm feels numb for a couple seconds . Any clue on what it could be ? Thanks</content><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403183832000">That 's not good u should see a doctor</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403183864000">You probably either strained or tore something in your shoulder or rotator cuff . I would see a docter about it though to make sure it is nothing serious , otherwise you wont be able to throw a ball for about 5-8 month . Hope this helps .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403183901000">Your story has been forwarded to Dr. Yahoo/ORGANIZATION . Please have a seat in the waiting room . The doctor will see you in due time .</answer><suggestions>yahoo/ORGANIZATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1403191590000">I have no idea what 's wrong with your arm . Best leave that to medical experts . I 'd also perhaps get your head looked at - anyone who waits a year before seeking help and then does so by going to a baseball q & a forum to help diagnose an injury must be suffering from sort of mental disability as well .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
</question>
<question id="20140615224306AASdmOX">
	<title>Is kawhi/PERSON Leornard/PERSON the most underrated MVP ever ?</title><suggestions></suggestions>
	<content>He was n't an all star , and he did n't even make the all-NBA 3rd team . And he plays for the Spurs/ORGANIZATION , so he does n't get the media attention outside of San/PERSON Antonio/PERSON .</content><suggestions>spurs/ORGANIZATION san/LOCATION antonio/LOCATION</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402897823000">Well to be honest with you he shouldnt be . . i can name 3 other players in his position who is better than he is . His season stats were not great he just had a amazing finals . He is a pretty suprising mvp . . danny/PERSON green/PERSON last year might have got it if they won . But he isnt gon na be in the all nba team ... Kawhi/PERSON should only b mentioned in the All defensive teams not All NbA/ORGANIZATION ... he made shots and his a tought guy . But how well would he do if he had to carry a team , He didnt have anyone to turn to too take pressue off . He would not of performed that way . Same wat on the defense teams that play them dont focus on him . Try to make a game plan for Kawhi . But under the radar player he is great .</answer><suggestions>danny/PERSON green/PERSON nba/ORGANIZATION kawhi/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402898265000">yes</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402898694000">Yes , but he wo n't be for long .</answer><suggestions></suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402899341000">No , he is not underrated . 2011-2012 , he got only 5 points average games . But now , especially in the final , he took 16 . X -LRB- sorry , I do n't remember the accurate number -RRB- points average . He is not underrated , he is now progressing . But he needs to say thanks to TD , Paker , Manu , they build a good example for him . Especially he needs to say thanks to Popovich ! He changes Kawai a lot !</answer><suggestions>manu/PERSON popovich/PERSON kawai/PERSON</suggestions>
	<answer epoch="1402904058000">i do n't think anybody could just suddenly start playng great in the finals , chances are popovich/PERSON kept him low score on regular season on purpose just for making him Miami/LOCATION 's biggest surprise did you see he was 1 on 1 on Lebron the whole time and he had average 2 steals off him on each game , that is very impressive defense playing against king james/PERSON</answer><suggestions>popovich/PERSON miami/LOCATION james/PERSON</suggestions>
</question>

